[{"Q.No":1,"Question":"___________________ is performed with the target\u2019s permission in a professional setting.","Option A":"Ethical hacking","Option B":"Social engineering","Option C":"System Engineering","Option D":"Software Testing","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":2,"Question":"Log scales are linear in ______________________.","Option A":"Addition","Option B":"Subtraction","Option C":"Multiplication","Option D":"Division","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":3,"Question":"Which one of the following is not commonly used aesthetics in data visualization?","Option A":"Image","Option B":"Color","Option C":"Position","Option D":"Shape","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":4,"Question":"___________________________ can be useful for data of a periodic nature, such that data values at one end of the scale can be logically joined to data values at the other end.","Option A":"Cartesian coordinates","Option B":"Polar coordinates","Option C":"Non-linear axes","Option D":"Linear scale","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":5,"Question":"Which of the following statements describes a discrete variable?","Option A":"It can take on any value within a range of values","Option B":"It can only take on whole number values","Option C":"It is continuous and can take on any value","Option D":"It is a categorical variable that represents groups or categories","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":6,"Question":"_____________________is a branch of science that deals with programming the systems in such a way that they automatically learn and improve with experience.","Option A":"Machine Learning","Option B":"Deep learning","Option C":"Neural Network","Option D":"IoT","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":7,"Question":"____________is a subfield of machine learning.","Option A":"Deep Learning","Option B":"Artificial Intelligence","Option C":"Shallow Learning","Option D":"Artificial Neural Network","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":8,"Question":"____________________ algorithms are inspired by the structure and function of the brain called artificial neural networks.","Option A":"Machine Learning","Option B":"Artificial Intelligence","Option C":"Shallow Learning","Option D":"Deep Learning","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":9,"Question":"_______________________ makes sense of unlabeled data without having any predefined dataset for its training.","Option A":"Supervised Learning","Option B":"Unsupervised Learning","Option C":"Reinforcement learning","Option D":"Semi-Supervised Learning","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":10,"Question":"Which type of AI is commonly used for speech recognition and image recognition?","Option A":"Narrow AI","Option B":"General AI","Option C":"Super AI","Option D":"Strong AI","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":11,"Question":"___________________ is one of the best examples of Limited Memory systems.","Option A":"Self-driving car","Option B":"IBM's Deep Blue system","Option C":"Google's AlphaGo","Option D":"Apple Siri","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":12,"Question":"The X dimension of AI philosophy is ________________.","Option A":"Reasoning","Option B":"Cognition","Option C":"Interface","Option D":"Knowledge","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":13,"Question":"The core components and constituents of AI are derived from the concept of __________________.","Option A":"Logic","Option B":"Cognition","Option C":"Computation","Option D":"All of the above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":14,"Question":"What test did ELIZA successfully pass?","Option A":"Medical Diagnosis Test","Option B":"Customer Service Test","Option C":"Turing Test","Option D":"Financial Advisor Test","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":15,"Question":"_____________ is a rule of thumb, strategy, trick, simplification, or any other kind of device which drastically limits search for solutions in large problem spaces.","Option A":"Heuristic","Option B":"Critical","Option C":"Value based","Option D":"Analytical","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":16,"Question":"Quantitative data deals with _________________ .","Option A":"Numbers","Option B":"Characteristics","Option C":"Images","Option D":"Sketches","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":17,"Question":"-------------------- is a polar coordinate system?","Option A":"A system for measuring temperature","Option B":"A system to specify positions via an angle and a radial distance from the origin","Option C":"A system for measuring weight","Option D":"A system for measuring time","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":18,"Question":"802.3 is the standard for 10BASE5 Ethernet that uses _______________ as a shared medium.","Option A":"Twisted pair cable","Option B":"Coaxial cable","Option C":"Fiber optic cable","Option D":"Copper wire","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":19,"Question":"__________________ is an actuator that creates motion in a straight line.","Option A":"Relay","Option B":"Solenoid","Option C":"Linear Actuator","Option D":"DC Motor","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":20,"Question":"IEEE 802.11 is a collection of ___________________ communication standards.","Option A":"Wireless local area network","Option B":"Mobile","Option C":"Ethernet","Option D":"Wireless broadband","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":21,"Question":"___________________ uses 128-bit address scheme that allows total of 2128 or 3.4 x 1038 addresses.","Option A":"IPv4","Option B":"IPv6","Option C":"6LOWPAN","Option D":"None of these","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":22,"Question":"________________standards form the basis of specifications for high level communication protocols such as ZigBee.","Option A":802.3,"Option B":802.11,"Option C":802.16,"Option D":"802.15.4","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":23,"Question":"The actuators used as an electromagnet is -----------------------.","Option A":"Solenoid","Option B":"Relay","Option C":"DC Motors","Option D":"Stepper Motor","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":24,"Question":"___________________wireless technology is used to deliver higher multi-Gbps peak data speeds.","Option A":"2G","Option B":"3G","Option C":"4G","Option D":"5G","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":25,"Question":"In telecommunication networks, NGN stands for __________________________.","Option A":"Next Generation Network","Option B":"Network Growth Nucleus","Option C":"Network Generation Nexus","Option D":"New Global Network","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":26,"Question":"Number of layers in NGN architecture is _______.","Option A":7,"Option B":6,"Option C":5,"Option D":4,"Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":27,"Question":"Layers of NGN are ______________________________.","Option A":"Access, Transport, Control, Service Layer","Option B":"Physical, Data Link, Network, Session Layer","Option C":"Application, Session, Transport, Network","Option D":"Network, Application Layer","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":28,"Question":"Wi Max, Wi-Fi, LTE Technology is used in ___mobile network.","Option A":"2G","Option B":"3G","Option C":"4G","Option D":"5G","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":29,"Question":"What is the primary function of a Label Switch Router?","Option A":"To forward packets based on their IP addresses","Option B":"To forward packets based on their labels","Option C":"To perform security functions on network traffic","Option D":"To provide Quality of Service (QoS) for network traffic","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":30,"Question":"Which of the following is an example of a 5G application for the agriculture industry?","Option A":"Virtual reality gaming","Option B":"Online shopping","Option C":"Remote monitoring of crops and livestock","Option D":"Social media","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":31,"Question":"Which of the following industries can benefit from NGN applications?","Option A":"Transportation","Option B":"Agriculture","Option C":"Manufacturing","Option D":"All of the above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":32,"Question":"In Digital Forensic, Planning, Transport of Evidence and Presentation of hypothesis are phases of ____model.","Option A":"ADFM","Option B":"EMCI","Option C":"IDIP","Option D":"None of these","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":33,"Question":"The digital evidence are used to establish a credible link between____________.","Option A":"Attacker and Information","Option B":"Victim and the crime scene","Option C":"Attacker, victim and the crime scene","Option D":"Attacker and the crime scene","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":34,"Question":"Dried blood, fingerprint, DNA samples are examples of ___?","Option A":"Documented Evidence","Option B":"Substantial Evidence","Option C":"Testimonial Evidence","Option D":"Explainable Evidence","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":35,"Question":"In ADFM, Which phase is used to provide summary and explanation of conclusion?","Option A":"Approach Strategy","Option B":"Presentation","Option C":"Preservation","Option D":"Analysis","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":36,"Question":"Ethical norms for investigator is ----------------------------.","Option A":"Should avoid harm to others","Option B":"Should be honest and trustworthy","Option C":"should contribute to the society","Option D":"All of above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":37,"Question":"-------------------is Unethical norms for Digital Forensic Investigation?","Option A":"Display bias or prejudice in findings or observation","Option B":"Honor confidentiality","Option C":"Respect privacy of others","Option D":"Being honest and trustworthy","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":38,"Question":"What do the Cyberterrorists do?","Option A":"They are skilled criminal experts who write some of the hacking tools, including the scripts and other programs that the script kiddies and security professionals use.","Option B":"They are highly technical and publicly known security experts who not only monitor and track computer, network, and application vulnerabilities but also write the tools and other code to exploit them.","Option C":"attack corporate or government computers and public utility infrastructures, such as power grids and air-traffic control towers.","Option D":"They are computer novices who take advantage of the exploit tools, vulnerability scanners, and documentation available free on the Internet but who don\u2019t have any real knowledge of what\u2019s really","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":39,"Question":"The EMCI follows \u2026\u2026\u2026\u2026 model?","Option A":"Waterfall","Option B":"Incremental","Option C":"V-model","Option D":"Data Flow","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":40,"Question":"__________ indicates collection, sequence of control, transfer and analysis. It also documents each person who handled the evidence, the date\/time it was collected or transferred and the purpose for the transfer.","Option A":"Best Evidence","Option B":"Locard's exchange principle","Option C":"Chain of Custody","Option D":"None of these","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":41,"Question":"In the case study of Illegal money transfer where the accused transferred huge amount of money from different accounts to fake accounts using cyber cafe, which digital evidences can be found out by Investigators?","Option A":"System server logs","Option B":"IP addresses of machines in cyber cafe","Option C":"E-mail IDs of accused","Option D":"All of above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":42,"Question":"Which phase of IDIP model includes Detection & Notification Phase?","Option A":"Deployment Phase","Option B":"Physical Crime Investigation","Option C":"Readiness","Option D":"Review phase","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":43,"Question":"How many layers are there in Blockchain architecture?","Option A":3,"Option B":4,"Option C":5,"Option D":7,"Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":44,"Question":"Which layer is called as logical layer of Blockchain architecture?","Option A":"Consensus Layer","Option B":"Semantic Layer","Option C":"Data Link layer","Option D":"Application Layer","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":45,"Question":"Which of the following statement is true about Blockchain?","Option A":"Blockchain is peer to peer system with no third parties in between.","Option B":"Blockchain is shared, decentralized and open ledger of transactions.","Option C":"Blockchain technology was designed to enable true decentralization.","Option D":"All of these","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":46,"Question":"--------------------- is a common, unchallengeable, digital ledger that allows the process of recording transactions and tracking assets in a business network.","Option A":"Blockchain","Option B":"Cryptography","Option C":"Client Server Network","Option D":"Centralized system","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":47,"Question":"In 2008_______developed system which contains secure history of data exchange.","Option A":"Merkle","Option B":"Binary","Option C":"Satoshi Nakamoto","Option D":"All of above","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":48,"Question":"Exploiting weaknesses in network transport mechanisms, such as TCP\/IP is an example of _________________.","Option A":"Operating system attack","Option B":"Network infrastructure attacks","Option C":"Non technical attack","Option D":"Application attack","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":49,"Question":"Respecting privacy is a --------------------.","Option A":"data hiding principle","Option B":"security assessment principle","Option C":"testing process principle","Option D":"network security principle","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":50,"Question":"In ethical hacking Reading online help files for the given tool. Study the user\u2019s manual guide for given commercial tool.","Option A":"Executing the plan","Option B":"Formulating the plan","Option C":"Evaluating results","Option D":"using the Selected tool","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":51,"Question":"Classify the following attack in the suitable category: John floods a network with too many requests and creates a denial of service (DoS) for legitimate requests.","Option A":"Operating system attack","Option B":"Network infrastructure attack","Option C":"Non-technical attack","Option D":"Application attack","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":52,"Question":"Built in authentication system of a College exam portal is broken down and passwords are cracked to gain access- this attack comes under _________________________.","Option A":"Operating system attack","Option B":"Network infrastructure attack","Option C":"nontechnical attack","Option D":"application attack","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":53,"Question":"GDPR is a legal standard that protects the data of ____________________.","Option A":"European Union citizens","Option B":"Asian citizen","Option C":"American Citizens","Option D":"African citizens","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":54,"Question":"Vulnerability scanning in ethical hacking finds -------------------.","Option A":"Strengths","Option B":"Weaknesses","Option C":"opportunities","Option D":"Threats","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":55,"Question":"Global information assurance certification (GIAC), Certified Information Systems Security Professional (CISSP) are examples of -------------.","Option A":"System testing certification","Option B":"Network testing Certification","Option C":"Datawarehousing testing certification","Option D":"Security testing certification","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":56,"Question":"To catch a thief, think like a thief. That\u2019s the basis for _______________.","Option A":"Security testing","Option B":"ethical hacking","Option C":"configuration testing","Option D":"performance testing","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":57,"Question":"In Blockchain,----------------------------- layer is used in the peer-to-peer communications between the nodes that allow them to discover each other.","Option A":"Application Layer","Option B":"Propagation Layer","Option C":"Consensus Layer","Option D":"Execution Layer","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":58,"Question":"____________ meaning a rogue employee, contractor, intern, or other user who abuses his or her trusted privileges.","Option A":"A malicious user","Option B":"A tester","Option C":"A Design engineer","Option D":"An interpreter","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":59,"Question":"Buffer overflow attacks are _____________________.","Option A":"often how the hacker can get in to modify system files, read database files, and more.","Option B":"often how the hacker can get in to modify network files and crack password.","Option C":"often how the hacker can get in to modify the IP address","Option D":"often how the hacker can get in to network to disable the functionalities.","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":60,"Question":"What is traffic analysis or social network analysis?","Option A":"Crashing servers and Transmitting malware","Option B":"Gathering messaging-trend information via log files or a network analyzer that can tip off the attacker about conversations between people and organizations","Option C":"Capturing information while it travels across the network and Perusing e-mails stored on servers and workstations","Option D":"Gathering internal network configuration information, such as host-names and IP addresses","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":61,"Question":"E-mail bombs attack is ---------------------------------.","Option A":"creating an attachment-overload attack by sending hundreds or thousands of e-mails with very large attachments to one or more recipients on your network.","Option B":"creating denial of service (DoS) conditions against your e-mail software and even your network and Internet connection by taking up a large amount of bandwidth and, sometimes, requiring large amounts of storage space.","Option C":"when attacker can crash your e-mail service or bring it to a crawl by filling the incoming Internet connection with junk.","Option D":"denies large attachments from being written to disk.","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":62,"Question":"An attacker can create an ___________________ by sending hundreds or thousands of e-mails with very large attachments to one or more recipients on your network.","Option A":"attachment-overload attack","Option B":"email","Option C":"spreadsheet","Option D":"document","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":63,"Question":"What is Bandwidth blocking?","Option A":"Multiple large messages can quickly fill the total storage capacity of an e-mail server.","Option B":"An attacker can crash e-mail service or bring it to a crawl by filling the incoming Internet connection with junk.","Option C":"An attack using a flood of e-mails is often carried out in spam attacks and other denial of service attempts.","Option D":"An attacker blocks the internet services on the PC and in the network.","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":64,"Question":"To prevent attachment-overload attacks what should be done?","Option A":"Limit the size of operating system files","Option B":"Limit the size of either e-mails or e-mail attachments.","Option C":"Limit the number of users in the network","Option D":"Limit the number of emails.","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":65,"Question":"Using ______________ on web-based e-mail forms can help minimize the impact of automated attacks and lessen your chances of e-mail flooding and denial of service.","Option A":"CAPTCHA","Option B":"Password","Option C":"MESSAGE","Option D":"OTP","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":66,"Question":"What is function of SMTP Relay?","Option A":"SMTP relay lets users send e-mails through internal servers.","Option B":"SMTP relay lets users send e-mails through external servers.","Option C":"SMTP relay lets people send emails in normal fashion.","Option D":"SMTP relay lets users change the authorities in the networking.","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":67,"Question":"The function of Google dork intitle operator is -------------------------.","Option A":"To allows a hacker to develop the pages with specific text in their HTML title.","Option B":"To allows a hacker to delete for pages with specific text in their HTML title.","Option C":"To allows a hacker to search for pages with specific text in their HTML title.","Option D":"To allows a hacker to change for pages with specific text in their HTML title.","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":68,"Question":"Which layer of blockchain assures that all the nodes must get approve on a common state of the shared ledger and also deals with safety and security of the blockchain?","Option A":"Application Layer","Option B":"Semantic Layer","Option C":"Consensus Layer","Option D":"Propagation Layer","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":69,"Question":"Bitcoin and Ethereum are examples of _____?","Option A":"Currency","Option B":"Cryptocurrency","Option C":"Cryptography","Option D":"Algorithm","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":70,"Question":"Categorize the following attack: Entire databases being corrupted or deleted when insecure Windows-based systems are attacked causing serious problems to a tremendous number of computers around the world.","Option A":"Network infrastructure attack","Option B":"Technical attack","Option C":"Operating system attack","Option D":"Application attack","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":71,"Question":"A buffer overflow attack can be -------------------------------.","Option A":"Stack-based or buffer-based","Option B":"Stack based or RAM based","Option C":"Heap-based or buffer based","Option D":"Stack-based or Heap-based","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":72,"Question":"What do you understand by Stack based buffer overflow attack?","Option A":"Hacker corrupts data within the heap, and that code change forces your system to overwrite important data.","Option B":"Attacker corrupts the data of program, and that transmission is stored somewhere.","Option C":"Attacker sends data to a program, and that transmission is stored in a too-small stack buffer.","Option D":"Attacker requests for the data, and that transmits that data back to sender.","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":73,"Question":"When the hacker corrupts data within the heap, and that code change forces your system to overwrite important data, it is called as ------------------.","Option A":"scan based buffer overflow","Option B":"sweep based buffer overflow","Option C":"heap based buffer overflow","Option D":"stack based buffer overflow","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":74,"Question":"Transmitting malware, Crashing servers, Obtaining remote control of workstations, Capturing and modifying confidential information as it travels across the network can be understood as -----------------------.","Option A":"hacker attacks against messaging systems","Option B":"hacker attacks against email systems","Option C":"hacker attacks against operating systems","Option D":"hacker attacks against network systems","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":75,"Question":"Perusing e-mails in e-mail databases on servers and workstations can be understood as --------------.","Option A":"hacker attacks against network systems","Option B":"hacker attacks against messaging systems","Option C":"hacker attacks against email systems","Option D":"hacker attacks against operating systems","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":76,"Question":"An email bomb is also known as a ---------------------.","Option A":"lattar bomb","Option B":"later bomb","Option C":"latter bomb","Option D":"letter bomb","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":77,"Question":"____________ is a form of Internet abuse which is perpetrated through the sending of massive volumes of email to a specific email address with the goal of overflowing the mailbox and overwhelming the mail server hosting the address, making it into some form of denial of service attack.","Option A":"Google dorking","Option B":"Port sweeping","Option C":"An email bomb","Option D":"MAC address spoofing","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":78,"Question":"Attachment overloading attack, connection attack, autoresponder attack are understood as -----------------.","Option A":"email bomb attack","Option B":"Heap based buffer overflow attack","Option C":"stack based buffer overflow attack","Option D":"message system attack","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":79,"Question":"Application of connection attack is done by --------------.","Option A":"crashing e-mail service or bring it to a crawl by filling the incoming Internet connection with junk.","Option B":"creating an attachment-overloading attack by sending hundreds or thousands of e-mails with very large attachments.","Option C":"multiple large messages are sent by hacker that can quickly fill the total storage capacity of an e-mail server.","Option D":"a hacker sending a huge amount of e-mails simultaneously to addresses on the network.","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":80,"Question":"Use new operating systems, Watch the language, Lean on developers, Apply your patches are performed as countermeasures for ------------------------.","Option A":"Operating system attack","Option B":"Network infrastructure attack","Option C":"Application attack","Option D":"Technical attack","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":81,"Question":"Windows attack leads to ----------------------.","Option A":"Transmitting malware, Crashing servers, Obtaining remote control of workstations, Capturing and modifying confidential information as it travels across the network","Option B":"secured networks-secured passwords-obtaining more patches for OS -No DoS attacks","Option C":"No Transmitting malware, No Crashing servers, Not Obtaining remote control of workstations, Non Capturing and non-modifying confidential information as it travels across the network","Option D":"Leakage of confidential information, including files being copied and credit card numbers being stolen, Passwords being cracked and used to carry out other attacks, Systems taken completely offline by DoS attacks","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":82,"Question":"Sequential steps hackers uses are: __, ___, __, __.             A) Maintaining Access, B) Reconnaissance C) Scanning D) Gaining Access","Option A":"B, C, D, A","Option B":"B, A, C, D","Option C":"A, B, C, D","Option D":"D, C, B, A","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":83,"Question":"_____system has a centralized control with all administrative rights.","Option A":"Blockchain","Option B":"Cryptography","Option C":"Decentralized","Option D":"Centralized","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":84,"Question":"Identify system shown in given figure?","Option A":"Centralized System","Option B":"Decentralized System","Option C":"Decentralized and peer to peer system","Option D":"None of these","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":85,"Question":"_________system does not have a centralized control and every node has equal authority.","Option A":"Centralized","Option B":"Decentralized","Option C":"Client server","Option D":"Star Network","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":86,"Question":"In ----------------- layer in Blockchain, the node gets Synchronized with another node in network and when a transaction is done, then node gets broadcasted to all other nodes in the network.","Option A":"Execution Layer","Option B":"Application Layer","Option C":"Semantic Layer","Option D":"Propagation Layer","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":87,"Question":"Which Technology can help contract management and audit the origin of a product?","Option A":"Centralized Technology","Option B":"Blockchain Technology","Option C":"Exchange","Option D":"Product to Product","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":88,"Question":"In Blockchain, when a transaction is recorded, it cannot be modified. This feature is called as______?","Option A":"Immutability","Option B":"Cryptocurrency","Option C":"VPN","Option D":"Bitcoin","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":89,"Question":"ADFM stands for ___?","Option A":"Analog Digital Forensic Model","Option B":"Abstract Digital Forensic Model","Option C":"Abstract Discrete Forensic Model","Option D":"Analog Discrete Forensic Model","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":90,"Question":"In ADFM model, The preparation of tools, techniques, search warrants are functions of which phase?","Option A":"Collection","Option B":"Preservation","Option C":"Examination","Option D":"Preparation","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":91,"Question":"In IDIP Model, Which phase is used to put the pieces of digital puzzle together and developing investigative hypotheses?","Option A":"Review phase","Option B":"Presentation phase","Option C":"Reconstruction phase","Option D":"Notification phase","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":92,"Question":"In digital Forensics, while doing Investigation, the investigator should follow?","Option A":"Honesty towards the Investigation","Option B":"Carefully Handling the digital evidences","Option C":"Compliance with the law and professional Norms","Option D":"All of above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":93,"Question":"Why it is important to maintain the Chain of Custody?","Option A":"To preserve the integrity of the evidence","Option B":"To prevent it from contamination","Option C":"To maintain the state of evidence","Option D":"All of the above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":94,"Question":"What is\/are the procedural steps to establish chain of Custody?","Option A":"Work with original evidence","Option B":"Perform a hash test analysis","Option C":"Alter the state of evidence","Option D":"Declare the confidential matters","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":95,"Question":"Identify Forensic Model in given fig?","Option A":"IDIP","Option B":"EMCI","Option C":"Waterfall","Option D":"ADFM","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":96,"Question":"The general ethical norms for Investigator is ----------------------.","Option A":"to discriminate","Option B":"to work on original media","Option C":"to honor property rights, copyrights and patents","Option D":"to display bias or prejudice in findings or observation","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":97,"Question":"Which of the following are sources of digital evidences?","Option A":"Internet based files","Option B":"Stand-alone computers or devices","Option C":"Mobile devices","Option D":"All of the above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":98,"Question":"Which of these schools was not among the early leaders in AI research?","Option A":"Dartmouth University","Option B":"Harvard University","Option C":"Massachusetts Institute of Technology","Option D":"Stanford University","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":99,"Question":"DARPA, the agency that has funded a great deal of American AI research, is part of the Department of:","Option A":"Defense","Option B":"Energy","Option C":"Education","Option D":"Justice","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":100,"Question":"The conference that launched the AI revolution in 1956 was held at:","Option A":"Dartmouth","Option B":"Harvard","Option C":"New York","Option D":"Stanford","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":101,"Question":"What is the term used for describing the judgmental or commonsense part of problem solving?","Option A":"Heuristic","Option B":"Critical","Option C":"Value based","Option D":"Analytical","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":102,"Question":"What of the following is considered to be a pivotal event in the history of AI.","Option A":"1949, Donald O, The organization of Behavior.","Option B":"1950, Computing Machinery and Intelligence.","Option C":"1956, Dartmouth University Conference Organized by John McCarthy.","Option D":"1961, Computer and Computer Sense.","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":103,"Question":"A certain Professor at the Stanford University coined the word 'artificial intelligence' in 1956 at a conference held at Dartmouth College. Can you name the Professor?","Option A":"David Levy","Option B":"John McCarthy","Option C":"Joseph Weizenbaum","Option D":"Hans Berliner","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":104,"Question":"The field that investigates the mechanics of human intelligence is:","Option A":"History","Option B":"Cognitive science","Option C":"Psychology","Option D":"Sociology","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":105,"Question":"A.M. Turing developed a technique for determining whether a computer could or could not demonstrate artificial intelligence. Presently, this technique is called","Option A":"Turing Test","Option B":"Algorithm","Option C":"Boolean Algebra","Option D":"Logarithm","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":106,"Question":"The first AI programming language was called:","Option A":"BASIC","Option B":"FORTRAN","Option C":"IPL","Option D":"LISP","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":107,"Question":"What is Artificial intelligence?","Option A":"Putting your intelligence into Computer","Option B":"Programming with your own intelligence","Option C":"Making a Machine intelligent","Option D":"Putting more memory into Computer","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":108,"Question":"Who is the father of AI?","Option A":"Alain Colmerauer","Option B":"John McCarthy","Option C":"Nicklaus Wirth","Option D":"Seymour Papert","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":109,"Question":"Artificial Intelligence has its expansion in the following application.","Option A":"Planning and Scheduling","Option B":"Game Playing","Option C":"Robotics","Option D":"All of the above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":110,"Question":"The characteristics of the computer system capable of thinking, reasoning and learning is known as","Option A":"Machine intelligence","Option B":"Human intelligence","Option C":"Artificial intelligence","Option D":"Virtual intelligence","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":111,"Question":"The first AI programming language was called:","Option A":"BASIC","Option B":"FORTRAN","Option C":"IPL","Option D":"LISP","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":112,"Question":"The first widely used commercial form of Artificial Intelligence (AI) is being used in many popular products like microwave ovens, automobiles and plug in circuit boards for desktop PCs. What is the name of AI?","Option A":"Boolean logic","Option B":"Human logic","Option C":"Fuzzy logic","Option D":"Functional logic","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":113,"Question":"What is the term used for describing the judgmental or commonsense part of problem solving?","Option A":"Heuristic","Option B":"Critical","Option C":"Value based","Option D":"Analytical","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":114,"Question":"______ is a branch of computer science which deals with helping machines finds solutions to complex problems in a more human like fashion","Option A":"Artificial Intelligence","Option B":"Internet of Things","Option C":"Embedded System","Option D":"Cyber Security","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":115,"Question":"In ____ the goal is for the software to use what it has learned in one area to solve problems in other areas.","Option A":"Machine Learning","Option B":"Deep Learning","Option C":"Neural Networks","Option D":"None of these","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":116,"Question":"Computer programs that mimic the way the human brain processes information is called as","Option A":"Machine Learning","Option B":"Deep Learning","Option C":"Neural Networks","Option D":"None of these","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":117,"Question":"A ____ is a rule of thumb, strategy, trick, simplification, or any other kind of device which drastically limits search for solutions in large problem spaces.","Option A":"Heuristic","Option B":"Critical","Option C":"Value based","Option D":"Analytical","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":118,"Question":"______ do not guarantee optimal\/any solutions","Option A":"Heuristic","Option B":"Critical","Option C":"Value based","Option D":"Analytical","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":119,"Question":"Cognitive science related with _____","Option A":"Act like human","Option B":"ELIZA","Option C":"Think like human","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":120,"Question":"_____ Model should reflect how results were obtained.","Option A":"Design model","Option B":"Logic model","Option C":"Computational model","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":121,"Question":"Communication between man and machine is related with ______","Option A":"LISP","Option B":"ELIZA","Option C":"All of above","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":122,"Question":"ELIZA created by _____","Option A":"John McCarthy","Option B":"Steve Russell","Option C":"Alain Colmerauer","Option D":"Joseph Weizenbaum","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":123,"Question":"The concept derived from ________ level are propositional logic, tautology, predicate calculus, model, temporal logic.","Option A":"Cognition level","Option B":"Logic level","Option C":"Functional level","Option D":"All of above","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":124,"Question":"PROLOG is an AI programming language which solves problems with a form of symbolic logic known as ______.","Option A":"Propositional logic","Option B":"Tautology","Option C":"Predicate calculus","Option D":"Temporal logic","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":125,"Question":"The ____ level contains constituents at the third level which are knowledge-based system, heuristic search, automatic theorem proving, multi-agent system.","Option A":"Cognition level","Option B":"Gross level","Option C":"Functional level","Option D":"All of above","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":126,"Question":"PROLOG, LISP, NLP are the language of ____","Option A":"Artificial Intelligence","Option B":"Machine Learning","Option C":"Internet of Things","Option D":"Deep Learning","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":127,"Question":"______ is used for AI because it supports the implementation of software that computes with symbols very well.","Option A":"LISP","Option B":"ELIZA","Option C":"PROLOG","Option D":"NLP","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":128,"Question":"Symbols, symbolic expressions and computing with those is at the core of ______","Option A":"LISP","Option B":"ELIZA","Option C":"PROLOG","Option D":"NLP","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":129,"Question":"______ that deals with the interaction between computers and humans using the natural language","Option A":"LISP","Option B":"ELIZA","Option C":"PROLOG","Option D":"NLP","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":130,"Question":"The core components are constituents of AI are derived from","Option A":"Concept of logic","Option B":"Cognition","Option C":"Computation","Option D":"All of above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":131,"Question":"Aristotle\u2019s theory of syllogism and Descartes and Kant\u2019s critique of pure reasoning made knowledge on _____.","Option A":"Logic","Option B":"Computation logic","Option C":"Cognition logic","Option D":"All of above","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":132,"Question":"Charles Babbage and Boole who demonstrate the power of _______","Option A":"Logic","Option B":"Computation logic","Option C":"Cognition logic","Option D":"All of above","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":133,"Question":"In 1960s, _____ pushed the logical formalism to integrate reasoning with knowledge.","Option A":"Marvin Minsky","Option B":"Alain Colmerauer","Option C":"John McCarthy","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":134,"Question":"Sensing organs as input, mechanical movement organs as output and central nervous system (CNS) in brain as control and computing devices is known as _____ of human being","Option A":"Information Control Paradigm","Option B":"Information Processing Paradigm","Option C":"Information Processing Control","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":135,"Question":"_____ model were developed and incorporated in machines which mimicked the functionalities of human origin.","Option A":"Functional model","Option B":"Neural model","Option C":"Computational model","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":136,"Question":"Chomsky\u2019s linguistic computational theory generated a model for syntactic analysis through __________","Option A":"Regular Grammar","Option B":"Regular Expression","Option C":"Regular Word","Option D":"None of these","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":137,"Question":"Human to Machine is _____ and Machine to Machine is ______.","Option A":"Process, Process","Option B":"Process, Program","Option C":"Program, Hardware","Option D":"Program, Program","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":138,"Question":"Weak AI is also known as ____","Option A":"Narrow AI","Option B":"General AI","Option C":"Neural AI","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":139,"Question":"_____ AI is able to perform dedicated tasks.","Option A":"Narrow AI","Option B":"General AI","Option C":"Neural AI","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":140,"Question":"Narrow AI performs multiple tasks at a time.","Option A":true,"Option B":false,"Option C":null,"Option D":null,"Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":141,"Question":"Weak AI is____________","Option A":"The embodiment of human intellectual capabilities within a computer.","Option B":"A set of computer programs that produce output that would be considered to reflect intelligence if it were generated by humans.","Option C":"The study of mental faculties through the use of mental models implemented on a computer","Option D":"All of the above","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":142,"Question":"Strong AI is__________","Option A":"The embodiment of human intellectual capabilities within a computer.","Option B":"A set of computer programs that produce output that would be considered to reflect intelligence if it were generated by humans.","Option C":"The study of mental faculties through the use of mental models implemented on a computer","Option D":"All of the above","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":143,"Question":"Artificial intelligence is___________","Option A":"The embodiment of human intellectual capabilities within a computer.","Option B":"A set of computer programs that produce output that would be considered to reflect intelligence if it were generated by humans.","Option C":"The study of mental faculties through the use of mental models implemented on a computer","Option D":"All of the above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":144,"Question":"Apple Siri is a good example of ______ AI.","Option A":"Narrow AI","Option B":"General AI","Option C":"Neural AI","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":145,"Question":"IBM Watson supercomputer comes under ____ AI.","Option A":"Narrow AI","Option B":"General AI","Option C":"Neural AI","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":146,"Question":"____ AI is a type of intelligence which could perform any intellectual task with efficiency like human.","Option A":"Narrow AI","Option B":"General AI","Option C":"Super AI","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":147,"Question":"The idea behind _________AI is to make such a system which could be smarter and think like a human by its own.","Option A":"Narrow AI","Option B":"General AI","Option C":"Super AI","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":148,"Question":"The worldwide researchers are now focusing on developing machines with ___ AI.","Option A":"Narrow AI","Option B":"General AI","Option C":"Super AI","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":149,"Question":"Playing chess, purchasing suggestions on e-commerce site, self-driving cars, speech recognition, and image recognition are the example of ____.","Option A":"Narrow AI","Option B":"General AI","Option C":"Super AI","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":150,"Question":"Machine can perform any task better than human with cognitive properties is known as ___ AI.","Option A":"Narrow AI","Option B":"General AI","Option C":"Super AI","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":151,"Question":"Ability to think, puzzle, make judgments, plan, learn, communication by its own is known as ___ AI.","Option A":"Narrow AI","Option B":"General AI","Option C":"Super AI","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":152,"Question":"____ AI is hypothetical concept of AI.","Option A":"Narrow AI","Option B":"General AI","Option C":"Super AI","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":153,"Question":"Which AI system not store memories or past experiences for future actions.","Option A":"Reactive machine","Option B":"Limited memory","Option C":"Theory of mind","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":154,"Question":"Which machines only focus on current scenarios and react on it as per as possible best action.","Option A":"Reactive machine","Option B":"Limited memory","Option C":"Theory of mind","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":155,"Question":"IBM\u2019s deep blue system is example of ___.","Option A":"Reactive machine","Option B":"Limited memory","Option C":"Theory of mind","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":156,"Question":"Google Alpha Go is example of ____.","Option A":"Reactive machine","Option B":"Limited memory","Option C":"Theory of mind","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":157,"Question":"Which can stores past experiences or some data for short period time.","Option A":"Reactive machine","Option B":"Limited memory","Option C":"Theory of mind","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":158,"Question":"Self-driving car is example of ____.","Option A":"Reactive machine","Option B":"Limited memory","Option C":"Theory of mind","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":159,"Question":"Which AI should understand the human emotions, people, and beliefs and be able to interact socially like humans.","Option A":"Reactive machine","Option B":"Limited memory","Option C":"Theory of mind","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":160,"Question":"Which machines will be smarter than human mind?","Option A":"Reactive machine","Option B":"Limited memory","Option C":"Theory of mind","Option D":"Self-Awareness","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":161,"Question":"_________machines will have their own consciousness and sentiments","Option A":"Reactive machine","Option B":"Theory of mind","Option C":"Self-Awareness","Option D":"Both B & C","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":162,"Question":"Which is not the commonly used programming language for AI?","Option A":"PROLOG","Option B":"LISP","Option C":"Perl","Option D":"Java script","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":163,"Question":"What is Machine learning?","Option A":"The autonomous acquisition of knowledge through the use of computer programs","Option B":"The autonomous acquisition of knowledge through the use of manual programs","Option C":"The selective acquisition of knowledge through the use of computer programs","Option D":"The selective acquisition of knowledge through the use of manual programs","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":164,"Question":"______________ is a branch of science that deals with programming the systems in such a way that they automatically learn and improve with experience.","Option A":"Machine Learning","Option B":"Deep Learning","Option C":"Neural Networks","Option D":"None of these","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":165,"Question":"Classifying email as a spam, labeling webpages based on their content, voice recognition are the example of _____.","Option A":"Supervised learning","Option B":"Unsupervised learning","Option C":"Machine learning","Option D":"Deep learning","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":166,"Question":"K-means, self-organizing maps, hierarchical clustering are the example of _____.","Option A":"Supervised learning","Option B":"Unsupervised learning","Option C":"Machine learning","Option D":"Deep learning","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":167,"Question":"Deep learning is a subfield of machine learning where concerned algorithms are inspired by the structure and function of the brain called _____.","Option A":"Machine learning","Option B":"Artificial neural networks","Option C":"Deep learning","Option D":"Robotics","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":168,"Question":"Machine learning invented by _____.","Option A":"John McCarthy","Option B":"Nicklaus Wirth","Option C":"Joseph Weizenbaum","Option D":"Arthur Samuel","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":169,"Question":"Embedded systems are_____","Option A":"A. General purpose","Option B":"B. Special purpose","Option C":"-","Option D":"-","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":170,"Question":"Embedded system is______","Option A":"A. An electronic system","Option B":"B. A pure mechanical system","Option C":"C. An electro-mechanical system","Option D":"D. (A) or (C)","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":171,"Question":"Which of the following is not true about embedded systems?","Option A":"A. Built around specialized hardware","Option B":"B. Always contain an operating system","Option C":"C. Execution behavior may be deterministic","Option D":"D. All of these","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":172,"Question":"Which of the following is not an example of a \u201csmall-scale embedded system\u201d?","Option A":"A. Electronic Barbie doll","Option B":"B. Simple calculator","Option C":"C. Cell phone","Option D":"D. Electronic toy car","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":173,"Question":"The first recognized modern embedded system is","Option A":"A. Apple computer","Option B":"B. Apollo Guidance Computer (AGC)","Option C":"C. Calculator","Option D":"D. Radio navigation system","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":174,"Question":"The first mass produced embedded system is","Option A":"A. Minuteman-I","Option B":"B. Minuteman-II","Option C":"C. Autonetics D-17","Option D":"D. Apollo Guidance Computer (AGC)","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":175,"Question":"Which of the following is an (are) intended purpose(s) of embedded systems?","Option A":"A. Data collection","Option B":"B. Data processing","Option C":"C. Data communication","Option D":"D. All of these","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":176,"Question":"Which of the following is (are) example(s) of embedded system for data communication?","Option A":"A. USB Mass Storage device","Option B":"B. Network router","Option C":"C. Digital camera","Option D":"D. Music player","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":177,"Question":"What are the essential tight constraint\/s related to the design metrics of an embedded system?","Option A":"A. Ability to fit on a single chip","Option B":"B. Low power consumption","Option C":"C. Fast data processing for real-time operations","Option D":"D. All of the above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":178,"Question":"A digital multi meter is an example of an embedded system for","Option A":"A. Data communication","Option B":"B. Monitoring","Option C":"C. Control","Option D":"D. All of these","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":179,"Question":"Which of the following is an (are) example(s) of an embedded system for signal processing?","Option A":"A. Apple iPOD (media player device)","Option B":"B. SanDisk USB mass storage device","Option C":"C. Both (A) and (B)","Option D":"D. None of these","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":180,"Question":"The instruction set of RISC processor is","Option A":"A. Simple and lesser in number","Option B":"B. Complex and lesser in number","Option C":"C. Simple and larger in number","Option D":"D. Complex and larger in number","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":181,"Question":"Which of the following is true about CISC processors?","Option A":"A. The instruction set is non-orthogonal","Option B":"B. The number of general purpose registers is limited","Option C":"C. Instructions are like macros in c language","Option D":"D. Variable length instructions","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":182,"Question":"Main processor chip in computers is_______","Option A":"A. ASIC","Option B":"B. ASSP","Option C":"C. CPU","Option D":"D. CPLD","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":183,"Question":"Processors used in many microcontroller products need to be______","Option A":"A. high power","Option B":"B. low power","Option C":"C. low interrupt response","Option D":"D. low code density","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":184,"Question":"In microcontrollers, UART is acronym of_____","Option A":"A. Universal Applied Receiver\/Transmitter","Option B":"B. Universal Asynchronous Rectified Transmitter","Option C":"C. Universal Asynchronous Receiver\/Transmitter","Option D":"D. United Asynchronous Receiver\/Transmitter","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":185,"Question":"Which architecture is followed by general purpose microprocessors?","Option A":"A. Harvard architecture","Option B":"B. Von Neumann architecture","Option C":"C. None of the mentioned","Option D":"D. All of the mentioned","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":186,"Question":"Which architecture involves both the volatile and the non-volatile memory?","Option A":"A. Harvard architecture","Option B":"B. Von Neumann architecture","Option C":"C. None of the mentioned","Option D":"D. All of the mentioned","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":187,"Question":"Which architecture provides separate buses for program and data memory?","Option A":"A. Harvard architecture","Option B":"B. Von Neumann architecture","Option C":"C. None of the mentioned","Option D":"D. All of the mentioned","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":188,"Question":"Harvard architecture allows:","Option A":"A. Separate program and data memory","Option B":"B. Pipelining","Option C":"C. Complex architecture","Option D":"D. All of the mentioned","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":189,"Question":"Which of the following processor architecture supports easier instruction pipelining?","Option A":"A. Harvard","Option B":"B. Von Neumann","Option C":"C. Both of them","Option D":"D. None of these","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":190,"Question":"Which of the following is an example for wireless communication interface?","Option A":"A. RS-232C","Option B":"B. Wi-Fi","Option C":"C. Bluetooth","Option D":"Both (B) and (C)","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":191,"Question":"ARM stands for _________","Option A":"A. Advanced RISC Machine","Option B":"B. Advanced RISC Methodology","Option C":"C. Advanced Reduced Machine","Option D":"D. Advanced Reduced Methodology","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":192,"Question":"What is the processor used by ARM7?","Option A":"A. 8-bit CISC","Option B":"B. 8-bit RISC","Option C":"C. 32-bit CISC","Option D":"D. 32-bit RISC","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":193,"Question":"The main importance of ARM micro-processors is providing operation with ______","Option A":"A. Low cost and low power consumption","Option B":"B. Higher degree of multi-tasking","Option C":"C. Lower error or glitches","Option D":"D. Efficient memory management","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":194,"Question":"ARM processors where basically designed for _______","Option A":"A. Main frame systems","Option B":"B. Distributed systems","Option C":"C. Mobile systems","Option D":"D. Super computers","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":195,"Question":"ASIC chip is","Option A":"A. Simple in design.","Option B":"B. Manufacturing time is less.","Option C":"C. It is faster.","Option D":"D. Both A&C.","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":196,"Question":"ASIC stands for","Option A":"A. Application-System Integrated Circuits","Option B":"B. Application-Specific Integrated Circuits","Option C":"C. Application-System Internal Circuits","Option D":"D. Application-Specific Internal Circuits","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":197,"Question":"In microcontrollers, I2C stands for","Option A":"A. Inter-Integrated Clock","Option B":"B. Initial-Integrated Clock","Option C":"C. Intel-Integrated Circuit","Option D":"D. Inter-Integrated Circuit","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":198,"Question":"______________ is the smallest microcontrollers which can be programmed to perform a large range of tasks.","Option A":"A. PIC microcontrollers","Option B":"B. ARM microcontrollers","Option C":"C. AVR microcontrollers","Option D":"D. ASIC microcontrollers","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":199,"Question":"_______________ was developed in the year 1996 by ATMEL Corporation","Option A":"A. PIC","Option B":"B. AVR","Option C":"C. ARM","Option D":"D. ASIC","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":200,"Question":"AVR stands for_____________________.","Option A":"A. Advanced Virtual RISC.","Option B":"B. Alf-Egil Bogen and Vegard Wollan RISC","Option C":"C. Both A & B","Option D":"D. None of the above","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":201,"Question":"AVR microcontroller executes most of the instruction in _________________.","Option A":"A. Single execution cycle.","Option B":"B. Double execution cycle.","Option C":"C. Both A& B","Option D":"D. None of the above.","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":202,"Question":"Term \"the Internet of things\" was coined by","Option A":"A. Edward L. Schneider","Option B":"B. Kevin Ashton","Option C":"C. John H.","Option D":"D. Charles Anthony","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":203,"Question":"The huge numbers of devices connected to the Internet of Things have to communicate automatically, not via humans, what is this called?","Option A":"A. Bot to Bot(B2B)","Option B":"B. Machine to Machine(M2M)","Option C":"C. InterCloud","Option D":"D. Skynet","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":204,"Question":"What does \u201cThings\u201d in IoT refers to?","Option A":"A. General device","Option B":"B. Information","Option C":"C. IoT devices","Option D":"D. Object","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":205,"Question":"Interconnection of Internet and computing devices embedded in everyday objects, enabling them to send and receive data is called_____________","Option A":"A. Internet of Things","Option B":"B. Network Interconnection","Option C":"C. Object Determination","Option D":"D. None of these","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":206,"Question":"_____________ is a computing concept that describes the idea of everyday physical objects being connected to the internet.","Option A":"A. IOT (Internet of Things)","Option B":"B. MQTT","Option C":"C. COAP","Option D":"D. SPI","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":207,"Question":"_____ devices may support a number of interoperable communication protocols and communicate with other device and also with infrastructure.","Option A":"A. Artificial Intelligence","Option B":"B. Machine Learning","Option C":"C. Internet of Things","Option D":"D. None of above","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":208,"Question":"Which one is not element of IOT?","Option A":"A. Process","Option B":"B. People","Option C":"C. Security","Option D":"D. Things","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":209,"Question":"IIOT stands for","Option A":"A. Information Internet of Things","Option B":"B. Industrial Internet of Things","Option C":"C. Inovative Internet of Things","Option D":"D. None of above","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":210,"Question":"Name of the IOT device which is first recognized?","Option A":"A. Smart Watch","Option B":"B. ATM","Option C":"C. Radio","Option D":"D. Video Game","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":211,"Question":"_____ is used by IOT","Option A":"A. Radio information technology","Option B":"B. Satellite","Option C":"C. Cable","Option D":"D. Broadband","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":212,"Question":"______ consists of communication protocols for electronic devices, typically a mobile device and a standard device.","Option A":"A. RFID","Option B":"B. MQTT","Option C":"C. NFC","Option D":"D. None of above","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":213,"Question":"_____________ refers to establish a proper connection between all the things of IOT.","Option A":"A. Connectivity","Option B":"B. Analyzing","Option C":"C. Sensing","Option D":"D. Active Engagement","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":214,"Question":"IOT devices which have unique identities and can perform ________________________.","Option A":"A. Remote sensing","Option B":"B. Actuating","Option C":"C. Monitoring capabilities","Option D":"D. All of the above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":215,"Question":"The sensed data communicated ___________________.","Option A":"A. Cloud-based servers\/storage.","Option B":"B. I\/O interfaces.","Option C":"C. Internet connectivity.","Option D":"D. None of the above","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":216,"Question":"IOT devices are various types, for instance______________.","Option A":"A. Wearable sensors.","Option B":"B. Smart watches.","Option C":"C. LED lights.","Option D":"D. All of the above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":217,"Question":"______________ is a collection of wired Ethernet standard for the link layer.","Option A":"A. IEEE 802.3","Option B":"B. IEEE 802.11","Option C":"C. IEEE 802.16","Option D":"D. IEEE 802.15.4","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":218,"Question":"______ is a collection of WLAN communication standards.","Option A":"A. IEEE 802.3","Option B":"B. IEEE 802.11","Option C":"C. IEEE 802.16","Option D":"D. IEEE 802.15.4","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":219,"Question":"____ is a collection of wireless broadband standards (WiMax).","Option A":"IEEE 802.3","Option B":"IEEE 802.11","Option C":"IEEE 802.16","Option D":"IEEE 802.15.4","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":220,"Question":"___ is a collection of standards for LR-WPANs.","Option A":"IEEE 802.3","Option B":"IEEE 802.11","Option C":"IEEE 802.16","Option D":"IEEE 802.15.4","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":221,"Question":"LR-WPANs standards from basis of specifications for high level communication protocol such as ___.","Option A":"Zigbee","Option B":"Allsean","Option C":"Tyrell","Option D":"Microsoft's Azure","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":222,"Question":"______ includes GSM and CDMA.","Option A":"2G","Option B":"3G","Option C":"4G","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":223,"Question":"______include UMTS and CDMA2000.","Option A":"2G","Option B":"3G","Option C":"4G","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":224,"Question":"______ include LTE.","Option A":"2G","Option B":"3G","Option C":"4G","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":225,"Question":"_____________ layer protocols determine how the data is physically sent over the network\u2019s physical layer or medium.","Option A":"Application layer","Option B":"Transport layer","Option C":"Network layer","Option D":"Link layer","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":226,"Question":"_______ layer is responsible for sending of IP datagrams from the source network to the destination network.","Option A":"Application layer","Option B":"Transport layer","Option C":"Network layer","Option D":"Link layer","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":227,"Question":"___ layer perform the host addressing and packet routing.","Option A":"Application layer","Option B":"Transport layer","Option C":"Network layer","Option D":"Link layer","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":228,"Question":"_____________ protocols provide end to end message transfer capability independent of the underlying network.","Option A":"Network layer","Option B":"Transport layer","Option C":"Application layer","Option D":"Link layer","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":229,"Question":"The ___ protocols define how the applications interface with the lower layer protocol to send the data over the network.","Option A":"Application layer","Option B":"Transport layer","Option C":"Network layer","Option D":"Link layer","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":230,"Question":"6LOWPAN stands for","Option A":"6 LOW Personal Area Network","Option B":"IPv6 LOW Personal Area Network","Option C":"IPv6 over Low power wireless personal area network","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":231,"Question":"802.3 is the standard for 10BASE5 Ethernet that uses ___________ cable as shared medium.","Option A":"Twisted pair cable","Option B":"Coaxial cable","Option C":"Fiber optic cable","Option D":"None of the above","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":232,"Question":"IEEE 802.11 standards provide data rates ______________","Option A":"10 Gbit\/s","Option B":"1 Gbit\/s","Option C":"1 Mb\/s to up to 6.75 Gb\/s","Option D":"250 Kb\/s","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":233,"Question":"________ of the following is a protocol related to IOT","Option A":"Zigbee","Option B":"6LoWPAN","Option C":"CoAP","Option D":"All of the above","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":234,"Question":"_______________ is useful for time-sensitive application that have very small data units to exchange and do not want the overhead of connection setup.","Option A":"TCP","Option B":"UDP","Option C":"Transport layer","Option D":"None of the above","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":235,"Question":"____________ protocol uses Universal Resource Identifiers (URIs) to identify HTTP resources.","Option A":"HTTP","Option B":"COAP","Option C":"WebSocket","Option D":"MQTT","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":236,"Question":"The 10\/100Mbit Ethernet support enables the board to connect to _________","Option A":"LAN","Option B":"MAN","Option C":"WAN","Option D":"WLAN","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":237,"Question":"Which one out of these is not a data link layer technology?","Option A":"Bluetooth","Option B":"UART","Option C":"Wi-Fi","Option D":"HTTP","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":238,"Question":"What is size of the IPv6 Address?","Option A":"32 bits","Option B":"64 bits","Option C":"128 bits","Option D":"256 bits","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":239,"Question":"MQTT stands for _____________","Option A":"MQ Telemetry Things","Option B":"MQ Transport Telemetry","Option C":"MQ Transport Things","Option D":"MQ Telemetry Transport","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":240,"Question":"MQTT is better than HTTP for sending and receiving data.","Option A":true,"Option B":false,"Option C":null,"Option D":null,"Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":241,"Question":"MQTT is _________ protocol.","Option A":"Machine to Machine","Option B":"Internet of Things","Option C":"Machine to Machine and Internet of Things","Option D":"Machine Things","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":242,"Question":"Which protocol is lightweight?","Option A":"MQTT","Option B":"HTTP","Option C":"CoAP","Option D":"SPI","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":243,"Question":"MQTT is:","Option A":"Based on client-server architecture","Option B":"Based on publish-subscribe architecture","Option C":"Based on both of the above","Option D":"Based on none of the above","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":244,"Question":"XMPP is used for streaming which type of elements?","Option A":"XPL","Option B":"XML","Option C":"XHL","Option D":"MPL","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":245,"Question":"XMPP creates _________ identity.","Option A":"Device","Option B":"Email","Option C":"Message","Option D":"Data","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":246,"Question":"XMPP uses ________ architecture.","Option A":"Decentralized client-server","Option B":"Centralized client-server","Option C":"Message","Option D":"Public\/subscriber","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":247,"Question":"What does HTTP do?","Option A":"Enables network resources and reduces perception of latency","Option B":"Reduces perception of latency and allows multiple concurrency exchange","Option C":"Allows multiple concurrent exchange and enables network resources","Option D":"Enables network resources and reduces perception of latency and Allows multiple concurrent exchange.","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":248,"Question":"HTTP expands?","Option A":"Hyper Text Transfer Protocol","Option B":"Hyper Terminal Transfer Protocol","Option C":"Hyper Text Terminal Protocol","Option D":"Hyper Terminal Text Protocol","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":249,"Question":"CoAP is specialized in ___________","Option A":"Internet applications","Option B":"Device applications","Option C":"Wireless applications","Option D":"Wired applications","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":250,"Question":"Which protocol is used to link all the devices in the IoT?","Option A":"TCP\/IP","Option B":"Network","Option C":"UDP","Option D":"HTTP","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":251,"Question":"Data in network layer is transferred in the form of ____________","Option A":"Layers","Option B":"Packets","Option C":"Bytes","Option D":"Bits","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":252,"Question":"Services provided by application layer?","Option A":"Web chat","Option B":"Error control","Option C":"Connection services","Option D":"Congestion control","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":253,"Question":"TCP and UDP are called?","Option A":"Application protocols","Option B":"Session protocols","Option C":"Transport protocols","Option D":"Network protocols","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":254,"Question":"Security based connection is provided by which layer?","Option A":"Application layer","Option B":"Transport layer","Option C":"Session layer","Option D":"Network layer","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":255,"Question":"Using which layer in transport layer data integrity can be assured?","Option A":"Checksum","Option B":"Repetition codes","Option C":"Cyclic redundancy checks","Option D":"Error correction codes","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":256,"Question":"Transport layer receives data in the form of?","Option A":"Packets","Option B":"Byte streams","Option C":"Bits stream","Option D":"both packet and Byte stream","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":257,"Question":"The network layer is considered as the _______?","Option A":"Backbone","Option B":"packets","Option C":"Bytes","Option D":"bits","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":258,"Question":"The network layer consists of which hardware devices?","Option A":"Router","Option B":"Bridges","Option C":"Switches","Option D":"All of the above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":259,"Question":"Network layer protocol exits in_____?","Option A":"Host","Option B":"Switches","Option C":"Packets","Option D":"Bridges","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":260,"Question":"Which protocol has a quality of service?","Option A":"XMPP","Option B":"HTTP","Option C":"CoAP","Option D":"MQTT","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":261,"Question":"_____ is a data-centric middleware standard for device-to-device and machine-to-machine communication.","Option A":"Data Distribution Serviced (DDS)","Option B":"Advance Message Queuing Protocol (AMQP)","Option C":"Extensible Messaging and Presence Protocol (XMPP)","Option D":"Message Queue Telemetry Transport (MQTT)","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":262,"Question":"_____ is a bi-directional, fully duplex communication model that uses a persistent connection between client and server.","Option A":"Request-Response","Option B":"Publish-Subscriber","Option C":"Push-Pull","Option D":"Exclusive Pair","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":263,"Question":"___ is a stateful communication model and server is aware of all open connection.","Option A":"Request-Response","Option B":"Publish-Subscriber","Option C":"Push-Pull","Option D":"Exclusive Pair","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":264,"Question":"Which is not an IoT communication model.","Option A":"Request-Response","Option B":"Publish-Subscribe","Option C":"Push-Producer","Option D":"Exclusive Pair","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":265,"Question":"In Node MCU, MCU stands for_____.","Option A":"Micro Control Unit","Option B":"Micro Controller Unit","Option C":"Macro Control Unit","Option D":"Macro Controller Unit","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":266,"Question":"REST is acronym for________","Option A":"Representational State Transfer","Option B":"Represent State Transfer","Option C":"Representational State Transmit","Option D":"Representational Store Transfer","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":267,"Question":"WSN stands for","Option A":"Wide Sensor Network","Option B":"Wireless Sensor Network","Option C":"Wired Sensor Network","Option D":"None of these","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":268,"Question":"Benefit of cloud computing services","Option A":"Fast","Option B":"Anywhere access","Option C":"Higher utilization","Option D":"All of the above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":269,"Question":"PaaS stands for_____","Option A":"Platform as a Service","Option B":"Platform as a Survey","Option C":"People as a Service","Option D":"Platform as a Survey","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":270,"Question":"_________ as a Service is a cloud computing infrastructure that creates a development environment upon which applications may be built.","Option A":"Infrastructure","Option B":"Service","Option C":"Platform","Option D":"All of the mentioned","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":271,"Question":"_________ is a cloud computing service model in which hardware is virtualized in the cloud.","Option A":"IaaS","Option B":"CaaS","Option C":"PaaS","Option D":"None of the mentioned","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":272,"Question":"Which of the following is the fundamental unit of virtualized client in an IaaS deployment?","Option A":"workunit","Option B":"workspace","Option C":"workload","Option D":"all of the mentioned","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":273,"Question":"______ offering provides the tools and development environment to deploy applications on another vendor\u2019s application.","Option A":"PaaS","Option B":"IaaS","Option C":"CaaS","Option D":"All of the mentioned","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":274,"Question":"_________ is the most refined and restrictive service model.","Option A":"IaaS","Option B":"CaaS","Option C":"PaaS","Option D":"All of the mentioned","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":275,"Question":"_____ is suitable for IOT applications to have low latency or high throughput requirements.","Option A":"REST","Option B":"Publish-Subscriber","Option C":"Push-Pull","Option D":"WebSocket","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":276,"Question":"____ is one of the most popular wireless technologies used by WSNs.","Option A":"Zigbee","Option B":"AllSean","Option C":"Tyrell","Option D":"Z-Wave","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":277,"Question":"Zigbee specifications are based on ______.","Option A":802.3,"Option B":802.11,"Option C":802.16,"Option D":"802.15.4","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":278,"Question":"____ is a transformative computing paradigm that involves delivering applications and services over the internet.","Option A":"WSN","Option B":"Cloud Computing","Option C":"Big Data","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":279,"Question":"The process of collecting, organizing and collecting large sets of data called as","Option A":"WSN","Option B":"Cloud Computing","Option C":"Big Data","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":280,"Question":"Does Raspberry Pi need external hardware?","Option A":true,"Option B":false,"Option C":null,"Option D":null,"Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":281,"Question":"Does RPi have an internal memory?","Option A":true,"Option B":false,"Option C":null,"Option D":null,"Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":282,"Question":"What do we use to connect TV to RPi?","Option A":"Male HDMI","Option B":"Female HDMI","Option C":"Male HDMI and Adapter","Option D":"Female HDMI and Adapter","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":283,"Question":"How power supply is done to RPi?","Option A":"USB connection","Option B":"Internal battery","Option C":"Charger","Option D":"Adapter","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":284,"Question":"What is the Ethernet\/LAN cable used in RPi?","Option A":"Cat5","Option B":"Cat5e","Option C":"Cat6","Option D":"RJ45","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":285,"Question":"Which instruction set architecture is used in Raspberry Pi?","Option A":"X86","Option B":"MSP","Option C":"AVR","Option D":"ARM","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":286,"Question":"Does micro SD card present in all modules?","Option A":true,"Option B":false,"Option C":null,"Option D":null,"Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":287,"Question":"Which characteristics involve the facility for things to respond in an intelligent way to a particular situation?","Option A":"Intelligence","Option B":"Connectivity","Option C":"Dynamic Nature","Option D":"Enormous Scale","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":288,"Question":"________ empowers IoT by bringing together everyday objects.","Option A":"Intelligence","Option B":"Connectivity","Option C":"Dynamic Nature","Option D":"Enormous Scale","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":289,"Question":"The collection of data is achieved with ________ changes.","Option A":"Intelligence","Option B":"Connectivity","Option C":"Dynamic Nature","Option D":"Enormous Scale","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":290,"Question":"The number of devices that need to be managed and that communicate with each other will be much larger.","Option A":"Intelligence","Option B":"Connectivity","Option C":"Dynamic Nature","Option D":"Enormous Scale","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":291,"Question":"________ in IoT as one of the key characteristics, devices have different hardware platforms and networks.","Option A":"Sensors","Option B":"Heterogeneity","Option C":"Security","Option D":"Connectivity","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":292,"Question":"Devices that transform electrical signals into physical movements","Option A":"Sensors","Option B":"Actuators","Option C":"Switches","Option D":"Display","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":293,"Question":"Stepper motors are_____","Option A":"AC motors","Option B":"DC motors","Option C":"Electromagnets","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":294,"Question":"DC motors convert electrical into ___ energy.","Option A":"Mechanical","Option B":"Wind","Option C":"Electric","Option D":null,"Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":295,"Question":"Linear actuators are used in________","Option A":"Machine tools","Option B":"Industrial machinery","Option C":"Both A and B","Option D":null,"Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":296,"Question":"Solenoid is a specially designed ________","Option A":"Actuator","Option B":"Machine","Option C":"Electromagnet","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":297,"Question":"Stepper motors are_____","Option A":"AC motors","Option B":"DC motors","Option C":"Electromagnets","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":298,"Question":"Accelerometer sensors are used in______","Option A":"Smartphones","Option B":"Aircrafts","Option C":"Both","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":299,"Question":"Image sensors are found in_______","Option A":"Cameras","Option B":"Night-vision equipment","Option C":"Sonars","Option D":"All of above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":300,"Question":"Gas sensors are used to detect _____gases.","Option A":"Toxic","Option B":"Natural","Option C":"Oxygen","Option D":"Hydrogen","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":301,"Question":"Properties of Arduino are:","Option A":"Inexpensive","Option B":"Independent","Option C":"Simple","Option D":"Both A and C","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":302,"Question":"Properties of IoT devices.","Option A":"Sense","Option B":"Send and receive data","Option C":"Both A and B","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":303,"Question":"IoT devices are ____","Option A":"Standard","Option B":"Non-standard","Option C":"Both","Option D":null,"Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":304,"Question":"What is the microcontroller used in Arduino UNO?","Option A":"ATmega328p","Option B":"ATmega2560","Option C":"ATmega32114","Option D":"AT91SAM3x8E","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":305,"Question":"___ is an open source electronic platform based on easy to use hardware and software.","Option A":"Arduino","Option B":"Uno","Option C":"Raspberry Pi","Option D":"Node","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":306,"Question":"____ is used for latching, locking, triggering.","Option A":"Solenoid","Option B":"Relay","Option C":"Linear Actuator","Option D":"Servo motors","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":307,"Question":"____ detects the presence or absence of nearby object without any physical contact.","Option A":"Smoke Sensor","Option B":"Pressure Sensor","Option C":"IR Sensor","Option D":"Proximity Sensor","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":308,"Question":"____ sensors include thermocouples, thermistors, resistor temperature detectors (RTDs) and integrated circuits (ICs).","Option A":"Smoke Sensor","Option B":"Temperature Sensor","Option C":"IR Sensor","Option D":"Proximity Sensor","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":309,"Question":"The measurement of humidity is","Option A":"RH","Option B":"PH","Option C":"IC","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":310,"Question":"____ sensor is used for automatic door controls, automatic parking system, automated sinks, automated toilet flushers, hand dryers.","Option A":"Smoke Sensor","Option B":"Temperature Sensor","Option C":"IR Sensor","Option D":"Motion Sensor","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":311,"Question":"____ sensor measures heat emitted by objects.","Option A":"Smoke Sensor","Option B":"Temperature Sensor","Option C":"IR Sensor","Option D":"Proximity Sensor","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":312,"Question":"Digital forensics is all of them except:","Option A":"Extraction of computer data.","Option B":"Preservation of computer data.","Option C":"Interpretation of computer data.","Option D":"Manipulation of computer data.","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":313,"Question":"IDIP stands for","Option A":"Integrated Digital Investigation Process.","Option B":"Integrated Data Investigator Process.","Option C":"Integrated Digital Investigator Process.","Option D":"Independent Digital Investigator Process.","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":314,"Question":"Who proposed Road Map for Digital Forensic Research (RMDFR)","Option A":"G.Gunsh.","Option B":"S.Ciardhuain","Option C":"J.Korn","Option D":"G.Palmar","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":315,"Question":"Investigator should satisfy following points:","Option A":"Contribute to society and human being.","Option B":"Avoid harm to others.","Option C":"Honest and trustworthy.","Option D":"All of the above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":316,"Question":"In the past, the method for expressing an opinion has been to frame a ____ question based on available factual evidence.","Option A":"Hypothetical","Option B":"Nested","Option C":"Challenging","Option D":"Contradictory","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":317,"Question":"More subtle because you are not aware that you are running these macros (the document opens and the application automatically runs); spread via email","Option A":"The purpose of copyright","Option B":"Danger of macro viruses","Option C":"Derivative works","Option D":"computer-specific crime","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":318,"Question":"There are three c's in computer forensics. Which is one of the three?","Option A":"Control","Option B":"Chance","Option C":"Chains","Option D":"Core","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":319,"Question":"When Federal Bureau Investigation program was created?","Option A":1979,"Option B":1984,"Option C":1995,"Option D":1989,"Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":320,"Question":"When the field of PC forensics began?","Option A":"1960's","Option B":"1970's","Option C":"1980's","Option D":"1990's","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":321,"Question":"What is Digital Forensic?","Option A":"Process of using scientific knowledge in analysis and presentation of evidence in court","Option B":"The application of computer science and investigative procedures for a legal purpose involving the analysis of digital evidence after proper search authority, chain of custody, validation with mathematics, use of validated tools, repeatability, reporting, and possible expert presentation","Option C":"Process where we develop and test hypotheses that answer questions about digital events","Option D":"Use of science or technology in the investigation and establishment of the facts or evidence in a court of law","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":322,"Question":"Digital Forensics entails _____.","Option A":"Accessing the system's directories viewing mode and navigating through the various systems files and folders","Option B":"Undeleting and recovering lost files","Option C":"Identifying and solving computer crimes","Option D":"The identification, preservation, recovery, restoration and presentation of digital evidence from systems and devices","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":323,"Question":"Which of the following is FALSE?","Option A":"The digital forensic investigator must maintain absolute objectivity","Option B":"It is the investigator\u2019s job to determine someone\u2019s guilt or innocence.","Option C":"It is the investigator\u2019s responsibility to accurately report the relevant facts of a case.","Option D":"The investigator must maintain strict confidentiality, discussing the results of an investigation on only a \u201cneed to know\u201d","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":324,"Question":"What is the most significant legal issue in computer forensics?","Option A":"Preserving Evidence","Option B":"Seizing Evidence","Option C":"Admissibility of Evidence","Option D":"Discovery of Evidence","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":325,"Question":"_______phase includes putting the pieces of a digital puzzle together and developing investigative hypotheses","Option A":"Preservation phase","Option B":"Survey phase","Option C":"Documentation phase","Option D":"Reconstruction phase","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":326,"Question":"In _______phase investigator transfers the relevant data from a venue out of physical or administrative control of the investigator to a controlled location","Option A":"Preservation phase","Option B":"Survey phase","Option C":"Documentation phase","Option D":"Reconstruction phase","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":327,"Question":"In _______phase investigator transfers the relevant data from a venue out of physical or administrative control of the investigator to a controlled location","Option A":"Preservation phase","Option B":"Survey phase","Option C":"Documentation phase","Option D":"Reconstruction phase","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":328,"Question":"Computer forensics do not involve_____activity.","Option A":"Preservation of computer data.","Option B":"Exraction of computer data.","Option C":"Manipulation of computer data.","Option D":"Interpretation of computer data.","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":329,"Question":"A set of instruction compiled into a program that perform a particular task is known as:","Option A":"Hardware","Option B":"CPU","Option C":"Motherboard","Option D":"Software","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":330,"Question":"Which of following is not a rule of digital forensics?","Option A":"An examination should be performed on the original data","Option B":"A copy is made onto forensically sterile media. New media should always be used if available.","Option C":"The copy of the evidence must be an exact, bit-by-bit copy","Option D":"The examination must be conducted in such a way as to prevent any modification of the evidence.","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":331,"Question":"To collect and analyze the digital evidence that was obtained from the physical investigation phase, is the goal of which phase?","Option A":"Physical crime investigation","Option B":"Digital crime investigation","Option C":"Review phase","Option D":"Deployment phase","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":332,"Question":"To provide mechanism to an incident to be detected and confirmed is purpose of which phase?","Option A":"Physical crime investigation","Option B":"Digital crime investigation","Option C":"Review phase","Option D":"Deployment phase","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":333,"Question":"Which phase entails a review of the whole investigation and identifies area of improvement?","Option A":"Physical crime investigation","Option B":"Digital crime investigation","Option C":"Review phase","Option D":"Deployment phase","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":334,"Question":"____________is known as father of computer forensic.","Option A":"G. Palmar","Option B":"J. Korn","Option C":"Michael Anderson","Option D":"S.Ciardhuain","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":335,"Question":"___________is well established science where various contribution have been made","Option A":"Forensic","Option B":"Crime","Option C":"Cyber Crime","Option D":"Evidence","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":336,"Question":"Who proposed End to End Digital Investigation Process (EEDIP)?","Option A":"G. Palmar","Option B":"Stephenson","Option C":"Michael Anderson","Option D":"S.Ciardhuain","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":337,"Question":"Which model of Investigation proposed by Carrier and Safford?","Option A":"Extended Model of Cybercrime Investigation (EMCI)","Option B":"Integrated Digital Investigation Process(IDIP)","Option C":"Road Map for Digital Forensic Research (RMDFR)","Option D":"Abstract Digital Forensic Model (ADFM)","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":338,"Question":"Which of the following is not a property of computer evidence?","Option A":"Authentic and Accurate.","Option B":"Complete and Convincing.","Option C":"Duplicated and Preserved.","Option D":"Conform and Human Readable.","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":339,"Question":"_______can makes or breaks investigation.","Option A":"Crime","Option B":"Security","Option C":"Digital Forensic","Option D":"Evidence","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":340,"Question":"__________ is software that blocks unauthorized users from connecting to your computer.","Option A":"Firewall","Option B":"Quick lauch","Option C":"OneLogin","Option D":"Centrify","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":341,"Question":"Which of following are general Ethical norms for Investigator?","Option A":"To contribute to society and human being.","Option B":"To avoid harm to others.","Option C":"To be honest and trustworthy.","Option D":"All of above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":342,"Question":"Which of following are Unethical norms for Investigator?","Option A":"Uphold any relevant evidence.","Option B":"Declare any confidential matters or knowledge.","Option C":"Distort or falsify education, training, credentials.","Option D":"All of above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":343,"Question":"Which of following is not general ethical norm for Investigator?","Option A":"To contribute to society and human being.","Option B":"Uphold any relevant Evidence.","Option C":"To be honest and trustworthy.","Option D":"To honor confidentially.","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":344,"Question":"Which of following is a not unethical norm for Digital Forensics Investigation?","Option A":"Uphold any relevant evidence.","Option B":"Declare any confidential matters or knowledge.","Option C":"Distort or falsify education, training, credentials.","Option D":"To respect the privacy of others.","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":345,"Question":"What is called as the process of creation a duplicate of digital media for purpose of examining it?","Option A":"Acquisition","Option B":"Steganography","Option C":"Live analysis","Option D":"Hashing","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":346,"Question":"Which term refers for modifying a computer in a way which was not originally intended to view Information?","Option A":"Metadata","Option B":"Live analysis","Option C":"Hacking","Option D":"Bit Copy","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":347,"Question":"The ability to recover and read deleted or damaged files from a criminal\u2019s computer is an example of a law enforcement specialty called?","Option A":"Robotics","Option B":"Simulation","Option C":"Computer Forensics","Option D":"Animation","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":348,"Question":"What are the important parts of the mobile device which used in Digital forensic?","Option A":"SIM","Option B":"RAM","Option C":"ROM","Option D":"EMMC chip","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":349,"Question":"Using what, data hiding in encrypted images be carried out in digital forensics?","Option A":"Acquisition","Option B":"Steganography","Option C":"Live analysis","Option D":"Hashing","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":350,"Question":"Which of this is not a computer crime?","Option A":"e-mail harassment","Option B":"Falsification of data.","Option C":"Sabotage","Option D":"Identification of data","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":351,"Question":"Which file is used to store the user entered password?","Option A":".exe","Option B":".txt","Option C":".iso","Option D":".sam","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":352,"Question":"__________is the process of recording as much data as possible to create reports and analysis on user input","Option A":"Data mining","Option B":"Data carving","Option C":"Meta data","Option D":"Data Spoofing","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":353,"Question":"________searches through raw data on a hard drive without using a file system.","Option A":"Data mining","Option B":"Data carving","Option C":"Meta data","Option D":"Data Spoofing","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":354,"Question":"What is first step to Handle Retrieving Data from an Encrypted Hard Drive?","Option A":"Formatting disk","Option B":"Storing data","Option C":"Finding configuration files.","Option D":"Deleting files","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":355,"Question":"Tool(s) used by ethical hacker_____","Option A":"A. Scanner","Option B":"B. Decoder","Option C":"C. Proxy","Option D":"D. All of these.","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":356,"Question":"Vulnerability scanning in Ethical hacking finds_____","Option A":"A. Strengths.","Option B":"B. Weakness.","Option C":"C. A & B","Option D":"D. None of these.","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":357,"Question":"___________ has now evolved to be one of the most popular automated tools for unethical hacking.","Option A":"A. Automated apps","Option B":"B. Database software","Option C":"C. Malware","Option D":"D. Worms","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":358,"Question":"Leaking your company data to the outside network without prior permission of senior authority is a crime.","Option A":"A. True","Option B":"B. False","Option C":null,"Option D":null,"Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":359,"Question":"A penetration tester must identify and keep in mind the ___________ & ___________ requirements of a firm while evaluating the security postures.","Option A":"A. privacy and security","Option B":"B. rules and regulations","Option C":"C. hacking techniques","Option D":"D. ethics to talk to seniors","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":360,"Question":"The legal risks of ethical hacking include lawsuits due to __________ of personal data.","Option A":"A. stealing","Option B":"B. disclosure","Option C":"C. deleting","Option D":"D. hacking","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":361,"Question":"Before performing any penetration test, through legal procedure, which key points listed below is not mandatory?","Option A":"A. Know the nature of the organization","Option B":"B. Characteristics of work done in the firm","Option C":"C. System and network","Option D":"D. Type of broadband company used by the firm","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":362,"Question":"SNMP stands for_____","Option A":"Simple Network Messaging Protocol","Option B":"Simple Network Mailing Protocol","Option C":"Simple Network Management Protocol","Option D":"Simple Network Master Protocol","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":363,"Question":"Which of the following tool is used for Network Testing and port Scanning______","Option A":"NetCat","Option B":"SuperScan","Option C":"NetScan","Option D":"All of above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":364,"Question":"Banner grabbing is used for","Option A":"White Hat Hacking","Option B":"Black Hat Hacking","Option C":"Grey Hat Hacking","Option D":"Script Kiddies","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":365,"Question":"An attacker can create an________attack by sending hundreds or thousands of e-mails a with very large attachments.","Option A":"Connection Attack","Option B":"Auto responder Attack","Option C":"Attachment Overloading Attack","Option D":"All the above","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":366,"Question":"Which of the following tool is used for Windows for network queries from DNS lookups to trace routes?","Option A":"Sam Spade","Option B":"SuperScan","Option C":"NetScan","Option D":"Netcat","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":367,"Question":"Which tool is used for ping sweeps and port scanning?","Option A":"Netcat","Option B":"SamSpade","Option C":"SuperScan","Option D":"All the above","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":368,"Question":"Which of the following tool is used for security checks as port scanning and firewall testing?","Option A":"Netcat","Option B":"Nmap","Option C":"Data communication","Option D":"Netscan","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":369,"Question":"What is the most important activity in system cracking?","Option A":"Information gathering","Option B":"Cracking password","Option C":"Escalating privileges","Option D":"Covering tracks","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":370,"Question":"Which Nmap scan is does not completely open a TCP connection?","Option A":"SYN stealth scan","Option B":"TCP scan","Option C":"XMAS tree scan","Option D":"ACK scan","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":371,"Question":"Key loggers are form of","Option A":"Spyware","Option B":"Shoulder surfing","Option C":"Trojan","Option D":"Social engineering","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":372,"Question":"Nmap is abbreviated as Network Mapper.","Option A":true,"Option B":false,"Option C":"-","Option D":"-","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":373,"Question":"_________is a popular tool used for discovering network as well as security auditing.","Option A":"Ettercap","Option B":"Metasploit","Option C":"Nmap","Option D":"Burp Suit","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":374,"Question":"Which of this Nmap do not check?","Option A":"Services different hosts are offering","Option B":"On what OS they are running.","Option C":"What kind of firewall in use?","Option D":"What type of antivirus in use?","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":375,"Question":"What is purpose of Denial of Service attacks?","Option A":"Exploit weakness in TCP\/IP attack.","Option B":"To execute a trojan horse on a system.","Option C":"To overload a system so it is no longer operational.","Option D":"To shutdown services by turning them off.","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":376,"Question":"What are the some of the most common vulnerabilities that exist in a network system?","Option A":"Changing manufacturer, or recommended settings of newly installed application.","Option B":"Additional unused feature on commercial software package.","Option C":"Utilizing open source application code.","Option D":"Balancing security and ease of use of system.","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":377,"Question":"Which of the following is not a characteristic of ethical hacker?","Option A":"Excellent knowledge of Windows.","Option B":"Understands the process of exploiting network vulnerabilities.","Option C":"Patience, persistence and perseverance.","Option D":"Has the highest level of security for the organization.","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":378,"Question":"Attempting to gain access to a network using an employee\u2019s credentials is called the _____________ mode of ethical hacking.","Option A":"Local networking","Option B":"Social engineering","Option C":"Physical entry","Option D":"Remote networking","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":379,"Question":"The first phase of hacking an IT system is compromise of which foundation of security?","Option A":"Availability","Option B":"Confidentiality","Option C":"Integrity","Option D":"Authentication","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":380,"Question":"Why would a ping sweep be used?","Option A":"To identify live systems","Option B":"To locate live systems","Option C":"To identify open ports","Option D":"To locate firewalls","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":381,"Question":"What are the port states determined by Nmap?","Option A":"Active, inactive, standby","Option B":"Open, half-open, closed","Option C":"Open, filtered, unfiltered","Option D":"Active, closed, unused","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":382,"Question":"What port does Telnet use?","Option A":22,"Option B":80,"Option C":20,"Option D":23,"Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":383,"Question":"Which of the following will allow foot printing to be conducted without detection?","Option A":"PingSweep","Option B":"Traceroute","Option C":"War Dialers","Option D":"ARIN","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":384,"Question":"Why would a hacker use a proxy server?","Option A":"To create a stronger connection with the target.","Option B":"To create a ghost server on the network.","Option C":"To obtain a remote access connection","Option D":"To hide malicious activity on the network","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":385,"Question":"Which phase of hacking performs actual attack on a network or system?","Option A":"Reconnaissance","Option B":"Maintaining Access","Option C":"Scanning","Option D":"Gaining Access","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":386,"Question":"Sniffing is used to perform ______________ fingerprinting.","Option A":"Passive stack","Option B":"Active stack","Option C":"Passive banner grabbing","Option D":"Scanned","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":387,"Question":"Services running on a system are determined by _____________.","Option A":"The system\u2019s IP address","Option B":"The Active Directory","Option C":"The system\u2019s network name","Option D":"The port assigned","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":388,"Question":"What are the types of scanning?","Option A":"Port, network, and services","Option B":"Network, vulnerability, and port","Option C":"Passive, active, and interactive","Option D":"Server, client, and network","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":389,"Question":"Enumeration is part of what phase of ethical hacking?","Option A":"Reconnaissance","Option B":"Maintaining Access","Option C":"Gaining Access","Option D":"Scanning","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":390,"Question":"________ is a popular IP address and port scanner.","Option A":"Cain and Abel","Option B":"Snort","Option C":"Angry IP Scanner","Option D":"Ettercap","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":391,"Question":"________ is a popular tool used for network analysis in multiprotocol diverse network","Option A":"Snort","Option B":"SuperScan","Option C":"Burp Suit","Option D":"EtterPeak","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":392,"Question":"___________ scans TCP ports and resolves different hostnames.","Option A":"SuperScan","Option B":"Snort","Option C":"Ettercap","Option D":"QualysGuard","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":393,"Question":"What tool can be used to perform SNMP enumeration?","Option A":"DNSlookup","Option B":"Whois","Option C":"Nslookup","Option D":"IP Network Browser","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":394,"Question":"Wireshark is a ____________ tool.","Option A":"network protocol analysis","Option B":"network connection security","Option C":"connection analysis","Option D":"defending malicious packet-filtering","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":395,"Question":"Aircrack-ng is used for ____________","Option A":"Firewall bypassing","Option B":"Wi-Fi attacks","Option C":"Packet filtering","Option D":"System password cracking","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":396,"Question":"What is the primary goal of an ethical hacker?","Option A":"avoiding detection","Option B":"testing security controls","Option C":"resolving security vulnerabilities","Option D":"determining return on investment for security measures","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":397,"Question":"Which type of hacker represents the highest risk to your network?","Option A":"black-hat hackers","Option B":"grey-hat hackers","Option C":"script kiddies","Option D":"disgruntled employees","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":398,"Question":"Hacking for a cause is called______","Option A":"hacktivism","Option B":"black-hat hacking","Option C":"active hacking","Option D":"activism","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":399,"Question":"When a hacker attempts to attack a host via the internet it is known as what type of attack?","Option A":"local access","Option B":"remote attack","Option C":"internal attack","Option D":"physical access","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":400,"Question":"A type of attack that overloads the resources of a single system to cause it to crash or hang.","Option A":"Resource Starvation","Option B":"Active Sniffing","Option C":"Passive Sniffing","Option D":"Session Hijacking","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":401,"Question":"In computer networking, ____ is any technical effort to manipulate the normal behavior of network connections and connected systems.","Option A":"Hacking","Option B":"Evidence","Option C":"Tracing","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":402,"Question":"We can eliminate many well-known network vulnerabilities by simply patching your network hosts with their latest and.","Option A":"Hackers and Crackers","Option B":"Vendor software and firmware patches","Option C":"Software and Hardware","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":403,"Question":"Network consists of devices such as routers, firewalls, hosts that you must assess as a part of ______ process.","Option A":"Crackers","Option B":"Black hat hacking","Option C":"Grey hat hacking process","Option D":"Ethical hacking process","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":404,"Question":"____ attack, which can take down your Internet connection or your entire network.","Option A":"MAC","Option B":"DOS","Option C":"IDS","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":405,"Question":"Which of the following is not a typical characteristic of an ethical hacker?","Option A":"Excellent knowledge of Windows","Option B":"Understands the process of exploiting network vulnerabilities","Option C":"Patience, persistence, and perseverance","Option D":"Has the highest level of security for the organization","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":406,"Question":"What is the sequence of a TCP connection?","Option A":"SYN-ACK-FIN","Option B":"SYN-SYN ACK-ACK","Option C":"SYN-ACK","Option D":"SYN-SYN-ACK","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":407,"Question":"A packet with no flags set is which type of scan?","Option A":"TCP","Option B":"XMAS","Option C":"IDLE","Option D":null,"Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":408,"Question":"Strong Artificial Intelligence is","Option A":"the embodiment of human intellectual capabilities within a computer","Option B":"a set of computer programs that produce output that would be considered to reflect intelligence if it were generated by humans","Option C":"the study of mental faculties through the use of mental models implemented on a computer cognitive science","Option D":"-","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":409,"Question":"These machines only focus on current scenarios and react on it as per possible best action","Option A":"Limited Memory","Option B":"Reactive Machines","Option C":"Theory of Mind","Option D":"Self-Awareness","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":410,"Question":"is the graphical representation of information and data.","Option A":"Data visualization","Option B":"Data Analytics","Option C":"Data mapping","Option D":"Data storytelling","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":411,"Question":"What is the foremost objective of data visualization?","Option A":"To convey complex data","Option B":"To convey incomplete data","Option C":"To convey data correctly","Option D":"To make data more complex","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":412,"Question":"is a methodology for communicating information, tailored to a specific audience, with a compelling narrative.","Option A":"Data visualization","Option B":"Data Analytics","Option C":"Data storytelling","Option D":"Data mapping","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":413,"Question":"What is true about Data Visualization?","Option A":"Data Visualization is used to communicate information clearly and efficiently to users by the usage of information graphics such as tables and charts.","Option B":"Data Visualization helps users in analyzing a large amount of data in a simpler way.","Option C":"Data Visualization makes complex data more accessible, understandable, and usable","Option D":"All of the above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":414,"Question":"The combination of a set of position scales and their relative geometric arrangement is called a\u2026\u2026\u2026\u2026\u2026\u2026\u2026...","Option A":"Cartesian system","Option B":"Curved axes","Option C":"Nonlinear axes","Option D":"Coordinate system","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":415,"Question":"Sequential color scale is used when .","Option A":"colors are used to distinguish discrete items.","Option B":"colors are used to represent data values.","Option C":"colors are used to highlight.","Option D":"colors are used to represent descriptive data","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":416,"Question":"Which coordinate system can be useful for data of a periodic nature, such that data values at one end of the scale can be logically joined to data values at the other end.","Option A":"Cartesian coordinates","Option B":"Curved axes","Option C":"Nonlinear axes","Option D":"Polar coordinates","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":417,"Question":"The scale is a monochromatic scale that varies from dark to light blue","Option A":"The ColorBrewer Blues","Option B":"Sequential color scales","Option C":"Accent color scales","Option D":"Ggplot2","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":418,"Question":"sensor is used for automatic door controls, automatic parking system, automated sinks, automated toilet flushers, hand dryers.","Option A":"Smoke Sensor","Option B":"Motion Sensor","Option C":"Temperature Sensor","Option D":"IR Sensor","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":419,"Question":"Who first proposed a blockchain-like protocol?","Option A":"David Chaum","Option B":"Dave Bayer","Option C":"W. Scott Stornetta","Option D":"Stephan Const","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":420,"Question":"The provide the connectivity for all components and physically separated functions within the NGN","Option A":"Access network functions","Option B":"Transport functions","Option C":"Gateway functions","Option D":"Resource and admission control function RACF","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":421,"Question":"The take care of end-user\u2019s access to the network as well as collecting and aggregating the traffic coming from these accesses towards the core network.","Option A":"Transport functions","Option B":"Access network functions","Option C":"Gateway functions","Option D":"Resource and admission control function RACF","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":422,"Question":"With the FCC, defines how WLANs should operate from a regulatory perspective, such as operating frequencies, antenna gain, and transmission power.","Option A":"FCC","Option B":"IEEE","Option C":"ETSI","Option D":"ITU-R","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":423,"Question":"LR-WPANs standards from basis of specifications for high level communication protocol such as.","Option A":"Zigbee","Option B":"Allsean","Option C":"Tyrell","Option D":"Microsoft's Azure","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":424,"Question":"MQTT is protocol.","Option A":"Machine to Machine","Option B":"Internet of Things","Option C":"Machine to Machine and Internet of Things","Option D":"Machine Things","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":425,"Question":"CoAP uses model","Option A":"Request-Response","Option B":"Publish-Subscriber","Option C":"Push-Pull","Option D":"Exclusive Pair","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":426,"Question":"The blockchain technology was defined in 1991 by the research scientist.","Option A":"Stuart Haber and W. Scott Stornetta","Option B":"Philip Moynagh","Option C":"Prof. Brian Mac Craith","Option D":"Stefan Konst","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":427,"Question":"Block chain system is developed using the concept of","Option A":"Cryptographically Secured chain","Option B":"Demanding","Option C":"Secure","Option D":"Popular","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":428,"Question":"The has previous hash value set to 0 to indicate no data was processed before the Genesis Block.","Option A":"Genesis Block","Option B":"Hash of Block","Option C":"Pointer of block","Option D":"IP of block","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":429,"Question":"Blockchain is an append-only database and cannot be changed or altered.","Option A":"ledger database","Option B":"relational database","Option C":"responsive database","Option D":"all of the above","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":430,"Question":"The blockchain technology is made of a architecture","Option A":"Chain architecture","Option B":"Layered architecture","Option C":"Vertical architecture","Option D":"Horizontal architecture","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":431,"Question":"Every node on the blockchain network has an","Option A":"Identical copy","Option B":"Different copy","Option C":"Parallel copy","Option D":"Opposite copy","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":432,"Question":"Application Layer acts as the tool of the blockchain.","Option A":"Back end","Option B":"Database","Option C":"Front end","Option D":"Network","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":433,"Question":"What is a blockchain","Option A":"A Currency","Option B":"A centralized ledger","Option C":"A type of cryptocurrency","Option D":"A distributed ledger on a peer-to-peer network","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":434,"Question":"Linking of block need to be defined on","Option A":"Execution Layer","Option B":"Application Layer","Option C":"Semantic Layer","Option D":"Propagation Layer","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":435,"Question":"Consensus layer also deals with the of the blockchain","Option A":"Safety and security","Option B":"Sending and receiving","Option C":"Uploading and downloading","Option D":"Cost and time factor of transaction","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":436,"Question":"A valid definition of digital evidence is................","Option A":"Data stored or transmitted using a computer","Option B":"Digital data of probative value","Option C":"Information of probative value","Option D":"Any digital evidence on a computer","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":437,"Question":"What are thethree general categories of computer systems that systems that can contain digital evidence?","Option A":"Desktop,laptop, server","Option B":"Personal computer, Internet,mobile, telephone","Option C":"Hardware, software, networks","Option D":"Open computer systems, communication systems, and embedded systems","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":438,"Question":"In terms of digital evidence, a hard drive is an example of:","Option A":"Open computer systems","Option B":"Communicatio n systems","Option C":"Embedded computer systems","Option D":"None of the above","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":439,"Question":"In terms of digital evidence, a mobile telephone is an example of:","Option A":"Open computer systems","Option B":"Communicatio n systems","Option C":"Embedded computer systems","Option D":"None of the above","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":440,"Question":"In terms of digital evidence, a Smart Card is an example of:","Option A":"Open computer systems","Option B":"Communicatio n systems","Option C":"Embedded computer systems","Option D":"None of the above","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":441,"Question":"Computers can be involved in which of the following types of crime?","Option A":"Homicide and sexual assault","Option B":"Computer intrusions and intellectual property theft","Option C":"Civil disputes","Option D":"All of  the above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":442,"Question":"A logon record tells us that, at a specific time:","Option A":"An unknown person logged into the system using the account","Option B":"The owner of a specific account logged into the system","Option C":"The account was used to log into the system","Option D":"None of the above","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":443,"Question":"Email, hard drives are examples of","Option A":"Illustrative evidence","Option B":"Electronic evidence","Option C":"Documented evidence","Option D":"Explainable evidence","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":444,"Question":"Blood, fingerprints, DNA these are \"examples\nof                        \"\n_","Option A":"Illustrative evidence","Option B":"Electronic evidence","Option C":"Documented evidence","Option D":"Substantial evidence","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":445,"Question":"Which is example of non- volatile memory.","Option A":"Flash memory","Option B":"Registers and Cache","Option C":"Process table","Option D":"Arp cache","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":446,"Question":"The process of ensuring that providing or obtaining the data that you have collected is similar to the data provided or presented in a court is known\nas\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0","Option A":"Evidence validation","Option B":"Relative evidence","Option C":"Best evidence","Option D":"Illustrative evidence","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":447,"Question":"Photographs, videos, sound recordings,\nX-rays, maps drawing, graphs, charts is a a type of\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0","Option A":"Illustrative evidence","Option B":"Electronic evidence","Option C":"Documented evidence","Option D":"Explainable evidence","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":448,"Question":"The evidence must be usable in the court which is called\nas\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0","Option A":"Admissible","Option B":"Authentic","Option C":"Complete","Option D":"Reliable","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":449,"Question":"Which of the following is not a type of volatile evidence?","Option A":"Routing tables","Option B":"Main memory","Option C":"Log files","Option D":"Cached data","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":450,"Question":"The evidences or proof can be obtained from the electronic source is called the","Option A":"digital evidence","Option B":"demonstrative evidence","Option C":"Explainable evidence","Option D":"substantial evidence","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":451,"Question":"From the two given statements 1\nand 2, select the correct option a.\nOriginal media can be used to carry out digital investigation process.  b. By default, every part of the\nvictim\u2019s computer is considered as unreliable.","Option A":"a and b both are true","Option B":"a is true and b is false","Option C":"a and b both are false","Option D":"a is false and b is true","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":452,"Question":"Digital evidences must follow the\nrequirements of the","Option A":"Ideal Evidence rule","Option B":"Best Evidence rule","Option C":"Exchange rule","Option D":"All the mentioned","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":453,"Question":"The digital evidence are used to establish a credible link\nbetween\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0","Option A":"Attacker and victim and the crime scene","Option B":"Attacker and the crime scene","Option C":"Victim and the crime scene","Option D":"Attacker and Information","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":454,"Question":"The criminological principle which states that, when anyone, or anything, enters a crime scene he\/she takes something of the scene with him\/her, and leaves something of himself\/herself behind, is:","Option A":"Locard\u2019s Exchange Principle","Option B":"Differential Association Theory","Option C":"Beccaria\u2019s Social Contract","Option D":"None of the above","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":455,"Question":"Due to caseload and budget constraints, often computer security professionals attempt to limit the damage and close each investigation as quickly as possible.\nWhich of the following is NOT a significant drawback to this approach?","Option A":"Each unreported incident robs attorneys and law enforcement personnel of an opportunity to learn about the basics of computer-relat ed crime.","Option B":"Responsibility for incident resolution frequently does not reside with the security professional, but with management.","Option C":"This approach results in under- reportin g of criminal activity, deflating statistics that are used to allocate corporate and government spending on combating computer-relat ed crime.","Option D":"Computer security professionals develop loose evidence processing habits that can make it more difficult for law enforcement personnel and attorneys to prosecute an offender.","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":456,"Question":"The author of a series of threatening\ne-mails consistently uses \u201cim\u201d instead of \u201cI\u2019m.\u201d This is an example of:","Option A":"An individual characteristic","Option B":"An incidental characteristic","Option C":"A class characteristic","Option D":"An indeterminate characteristic","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":457,"Question":"The digital evidence are used to establish a credible link\nbetween\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0","Option A":"Attacker and victim and the crime scen","Option B":"Attacker and the crime scene","Option C":"Victim and the crime scene","Option D":"Attacker and Information","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":458,"Question":"Blood, fingerprints, DNA these are examples\nof\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\n_","Option A":"Illustrative evidence","Option B":"Electronic evidence","Option C":"Documented evidence","Option D":"Substantial evidence","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":459,"Question":"\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0is known as testimonial.","Option A":"Oath affidavit","Option B":"DNA samples","Option C":"Fingerprint","Option D":"Dried blood","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":460,"Question":"Rule of evidence is also known as","Option A":". Law of witness","Option B":"Law of litigation","Option C":"Law of evidence","Option D":"All of the above","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":461,"Question":"Digital evidence is only useful in a court of law.","Option A":true,"Option B":false,"Option C":null,"Option D":null,"Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":462,"Question":"Ethical Hacking is also known as \u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0","Option A":"Black Hat Hacking","Option B":"White Hat Hacker","Option C":"Encryption.","Option D":"Combination of White and black hat hackers","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":463,"Question":"Tool(s) used by ethical\nhacker\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0.","Option A":"Scanner","Option B":"Decoder","Option C":"Proxy","Option D":"All of these","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":464,"Question":"Vulnerability scanning in Ethical hacking finds\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0.","Option A":"Strengths.","Option B":"Weakness.","Option C":"Proxy","Option D":"None of these","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":465,"Question":"Ethical hacking will allow\nto\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0all the massive\nsecurity breaches","Option A":"Remove.","Option B":"Measure.","Option C":"Reject.","Option D":"None of these","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":466,"Question":". Sequential step hackers use are: _ _ _\n_.\nA. Maintaining Access. B.\nReconnaissanc e C. Scanning\nD. Gaining Access.","Option A":"B, C, D, A","Option B":"B, A, C, D","Option C":"A, B, C, D","Option D":"D, C, B, A","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":467,"Question":"\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0is the art of exploiting the human elements to gain access to the authorized user.","Option A":".Social Engineering","Option B":"IT Engineering.","Option C":"Ethical Hacking","Option D":"None of the above.","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":468,"Question":"The term cracker refers to\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0","Option A":"Black hat hacker.","Option B":"White hat hacker.","Option C":"Grey hat hacker.","Option D":"None of the above.","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":469,"Question":". Who described a dissertation on fundamentals of hacker\u2019s attitude?","Option A":"G. Palma.","Option B":"Raymond.","Option C":"Either","Option D":"Jhon Browman.","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":470,"Question":"Computer Hackers have been in existence for more than\na\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0","Option A":"Decade.","Option B":"Year","Option C":"Century","Option D":"Era","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":471,"Question":"Hackers do hack for?","Option A":"Fame.","Option B":"Profit.","Option C":"Revenge.","Option D":"All the above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":472,"Question":"The intent of ethical hacker is to discover vulnerabilities from\na\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\npoint of view to better secure system","Option A":"Victims.","Option B":"Attackers.","Option C":"Revenge.","Option D":"None of these","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":473,"Question":"Security audits are usually based on\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0","Option A":"Entries.","Option B":"Checklists.","Option C":"Both A & B","Option D":"None of the above.","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":474,"Question":"Ethical hacking consist of","Option A":"Penetration testing","Option B":"Intrusion testing.","Option C":"Red teaming.","Option D":"All of the above.","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":475,"Question":".\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0is a person who find and exploits the weakness in computer system.","Option A":"Victim","Option B":"Hacker","Option C":"Developer","Option D":"None of the above.","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":476,"Question":"A white hat hacker is the one who \u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0","Option A":"Fix identifies weakness","Option B":"Steal the data","Option C":"Identifies the weakness and leave message to owner","Option D":"None of the above","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":477,"Question":".A black hat hacker is the one who","Option A":"Fix identifies weakness","Option B":"Steal the data","Option C":"Identifies the weakness and leave message to owner","Option D":"None of the above","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":478,"Question":"A grey hat hacker is the one\nwho\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0","Option A":"Fix identifies weakness","Option B":"Steal the data","Option C":"Identifies the weakness and leave message to owner","Option D":"None of the above","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":479,"Question":"To catch a thief, think like \u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0","Option A":"Police","Option B":"Forensics","Option C":"Thief","Option D":"Hacker","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":480,"Question":"\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0can create false feeling of safety","Option A":"Firewall","Option B":"Encryption","Option C":"VNPs","Option D":"All the above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":481,"Question":"\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0exploits that involves manipulating people and user even your self are the greatest\nvulnerability within any computer","Option A":"Nontechnical attacks","Option B":"Network infrastructure attack","Option C":"Operating system attack","Option D":"Application and other specialized attack","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":482,"Question":"Connecting into network through a rogue modem attached to computer behind a firewall is an example of\n\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0-","Option A":"Nontechnical attacks","Option B":"Network infrastructure attack","Option C":"Operating system attack","Option D":"Application and other specialized attack","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":483,"Question":".\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0comprise of large portion of hacker attacks simply because every computer has one and so well know exploits can be used against them","Option A":"Nontechnical attacks","Option B":"Network infrastructure attack","Option C":"Operating system attack","Option D":"Application and other specialized attack","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":484,"Question":".\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0should be done before ethical hacking process","Option A":"Data gathering.","Option B":"Attacking","Option C":"Planning","Option D":"Research","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":485,"Question":"Which permission is necessary before ethical hacking?","Option A":"Written permission","Option B":"Decision maker permission","Option C":"Privacy permission","Option D":"Risk permission","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":486,"Question":"Which tool is used to crack the password?","Option A":"Nmap","Option B":"LC4","Option C":"ToneLOC","Option D":"Nessus","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":487,"Question":"Which tool is used for depth analysis of a web application?","Option A":"Whisker","Option B":"Super scan","Option C":"Nikto","Option D":"Kismet","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":488,"Question":"Which tool is used to encrypt Email?","Option A":"WebInspect","Option B":"QualyGuard","Option C":"PGP (pretty good privacy)","Option D":"None of the above.","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":489,"Question":"Malicious attacker often think like?","Option A":"Thieves","Option B":"phreaker","Option C":"both A&B","Option D":"None of the above.","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":490,"Question":"Which hacker try to distribute political or social message through their work?","Option A":"Black hat hacker","Option B":"Hactivist","Option C":"Script kiddes","Option D":"White hat hacker","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":491,"Question":"\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0are part of organized crime on internet","Option A":"Criminal","Option B":"Antinationalist","Option C":"Hacker for hire","Option D":"None of the above","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":492,"Question":"Which magazines releases the latest hacking methods?","Option A":2600,"Option B":"Hackin9","Option C":"PHRACK","Option D":"All of the above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":493,"Question":"Performing a shoulder surfing in order to check other\u2019s password is\nethical practice.","Option A":"a good","Option B":"not so good","Option C":"very good social engineering practice","Option D":"a bad","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":494,"Question":"has now evolved to be one of the most popular automated tools for unethical hacking","Option A":"Automated apps","Option B":"Database software","Option C":"Malware","Option D":"Worms","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":495,"Question":"A penetration tester must identify and keep in mind the\n\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0& requirements of a firm while evaluating the security postures.","Option A":"privacy and security","Option B":"rules and regulations","Option C":"hacking techniques","Option D":"ethics to talk to seniors","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":496,"Question":"The legal risks of ethical hacking include lawsuits due to\n\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0of personal data.","Option A":"stealing","Option B":"disclosure","Option C":"deleting","Option D":"hacking","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":497,"Question":"Before performing any penetration test, through legal procedure, which key points listed below\nis not mandatory?","Option A":"Know the nature of the organization","Option B":"Characteristics of work done in the firm","Option C":"System and network","Option D":"Type of broadband company used by the firm","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":498,"Question":"The amateur or newbie in the field of hacking who don\u2019t have many skills about\ncoding and in-depth working of security and hacking tools are called","Option A":"Sponsored Hackers","Option B":"Hactivists","Option C":"Script Kiddies","Option D":"Whistle Blowers","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":499,"Question":"Criminal minded individuals who work for terrorist organizations and steal information of nations and other secret intelligence are","Option A":"State sponsored hackers","Option B":"Cyber Terrorists","Option C":"Hactivists","Option D":"Script Kiddies","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":500,"Question":"These types of hackers are the most skilled hackers in the hackers\u2019 community.\nWho are \u201cthey\u201d referred to?","Option A":"White hat Hackers","Option B":"Elite Hackers","Option C":"Red Hat Hackers","Option D":"Cyber Terrorists","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":501,"Question":"The offense \u201cReceiving stolen computer or communication device\u201d comes under\n\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0of Cyber security Act 2000.","Option A":"66B","Option B":"67A","Option C":"66E","Option D":"66C","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":502,"Question":"\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0is similar to a backup, but it is a complete image of a protected system, including data and system files.","Option A":"Replication","Option B":"Backup","Option C":"Snapshots","Option D":"DPLR","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":503,"Question":"Data subjects can ask data controllers to \u201cforget\u201d their personal data is\n\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0.","Option A":"Right to erasure","Option B":"Automated decision making","Option C":"Transferring data outside the EU","Option D":"Right to Control","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":504,"Question":"The offense of Tampering with computer source documents","Option A":"66B","Option B":65,"Option C":"66E","Option D":"66C","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":505,"Question":"The offense of Receiving stolen computer or communication device","Option A":"66B","Option B":65,"Option C":"66E","Option D":"66C","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":506,"Question":"The offense of Using password of another person","Option A":65,"Option B":66,"Option C":"66B","Option D":"66C","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":507,"Question":"The offense of Cheating using computer resource","Option A":"66D","Option B":66,"Option C":"66B","Option D":"66C","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":508,"Question":"The offense of Publishing private images of others","Option A":"66B","Option B":65,"Option C":"66E","Option D":"66C","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":509,"Question":"The offense of Publication for fraudulent purpose","Option A":74,"Option B":72,"Option C":"72A","Option D":73,"Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":510,"Question":"The offense of Publishing electronic signature certificate false in certain particulars","Option A":74,"Option B":72,"Option C":"72A","Option D":73,"Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":511,"Question":"The offense of Disclosure of information in breach of\nlawful contract","Option A":74,"Option B":72,"Option C":"72A","Option D":73,"Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":512,"Question":"The offense of Breach of confidentiality and privacy","Option A":69,"Option B":70,"Option C":71,"Option D":72,"Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":513,"Question":"The offense of Misrepresentat ion","Option A":69,"Option B":70,"Option C":71,"Option D":72,"Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":514,"Question":"The offense of Securing access or attempting to secure access to a protected system","Option A":"67C","Option B":68,"Option C":69,"Option D":70,"Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":515,"Question":"The offense of Failure\/refusal to decrypt data","Option A":"67C","Option B":68,"Option C":69,"Option D":70,"Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":516,"Question":"The offense of Failure\/refusal to comply with orders","Option A":"67C","Option B":68,"Option C":69,"Option D":70,"Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":517,"Question":"The offense of Failure to maintain records","Option A":67,"Option B":"67A","Option C":"67B","Option D":"67C","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":518,"Question":"The offense of Publishing images containing sexual acts","Option A":67,"Option B":"67A","Option C":"67B","Option D":"67C","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":519,"Question":"The offense of Publishing information which is obscene in electronic form.","Option A":67,"Option B":"67A","Option C":"67B","Option D":"67C","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":520,"Question":"The offense of Acts of cyberterrorism","Option A":66,"Option B":"66C","Option C":"66F","Option D":"66E","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":521,"Question":"The offense of Publishing private images of others","Option A":66,"Option B":"66C","Option C":"66F","Option D":"66E","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":522,"Question":"The offense of Cheating using computer resource","Option A":66,"Option B":"66D","Option C":"66F","Option D":"66E","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":523,"Question":"SNMP stands for\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0","Option A":"Simple Network Messaging Protocol","Option B":"Simple Network Mailing Protocol","Option C":"Simple Network Management Protoco","Option D":"Simple Network Master Protocol","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":524,"Question":"Which of the following tool is used for Network Testing and port\nScanning\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\n_","Option A":"NetCat","Option B":"SuperScan","Option C":"NetScan","Option D":"All of above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":525,"Question":"Banner grabbing is used for","Option A":"White Hat HackinG","Option B":"Black Hat Hacking","Option C":"Grey Hat Hacking","Option D":"Script Kiddies","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":526,"Question":"An attacker can create an\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0att ack by sending hundreds or thousands of\ne-mails a with very large attachments.","Option A":"Connection Attack","Option B":"Auto responder Attack","Option C":"Attachment Overloading Attack","Option D":"All the above","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":527,"Question":"Which of the following tool is used for Windows for network queries from DNS lookups to trace routes?","Option A":"Sam Spade","Option B":"SuperScan","Option C":"NetScan","Option D":"Netcat","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":528,"Question":"Which tool is used for ping sweeps and port scanning?","Option A":"Netcat","Option B":"SamSpade","Option C":"SuperScan","Option D":"All the above","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":529,"Question":"Which of the following tool is used for security checks as port scanning and firewall testing?","Option A":"Netcat","Option B":"Nmap","Option C":"Data communication","Option D":". Netscan","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":530,"Question":"What is the most important activity in system cracking?","Option A":"Information gathering","Option B":"Cracking password","Option C":"Escalating privileges","Option D":"Covering tracks","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":531,"Question":"Which Nmap scan is does not completely open a TCP connection?","Option A":"SYN stealth scan","Option B":"TCP scan","Option C":"XMAS tree scan","Option D":"ACK scan","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":532,"Question":"Key loggers are form of","Option A":"Spyware","Option B":"Shoulder surfing","Option C":"Trojan","Option D":"Social engineering","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":533,"Question":". \u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0is a popular tool used for discovering network as well as security auditing.","Option A":"Ettercap","Option B":"Metasploit","Option C":"Nmap","Option D":"Burp Suit","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":534,"Question":"Which of this Nmap do not check?","Option A":"Services different hosts are offering","Option B":"On what OS they are running.","Option C":"What kind of firewall in use?","Option D":"What type of antivirus in use?","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":535,"Question":"What is purpose of Denial of Service attacks?","Option A":"Exploit weakness in TCP\/IP attack","Option B":"To execute a trojan horse on a system.","Option C":"To overload a system so it is no longer operational.","Option D":"To shutdown services by turning them off.","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":536,"Question":"What are the some of the most common vulnerabilities that exist in a network system?","Option A":"Changing manufacturer, or recommended settings of newly installed application.","Option B":"Additional unused feature on commercial software packag","Option C":"Utilizing open source application code.","Option D":"Balancing security and ease of use of system.","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":537,"Question":". Which of the following is not a characteristic of ethical hacker?","Option A":"Excellent knowledge of Windows.","Option B":"Understands the process of exploiting network vulnerabilities.","Option C":"Patience, persistence and perseverance","Option D":"Has the highest level of security for the organization.","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":538,"Question":"Attempting to gain access to a network using an employee\u2019s credentials is called the\n_ mode of ethical hacking.","Option A":"Local networking","Option B":"Social engineering","Option C":"Physical entry","Option D":"Remote networking","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":539,"Question":"The first phase of hacking an IT system is compromise of which foundation of security?","Option A":"Availability","Option B":"Confidentiality","Option C":"Integrity","Option D":"Authentication","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":540,"Question":"Why would a ping sweep be used?","Option A":"To identify live systems","Option B":"To locate live systems","Option C":"To identify open ports","Option D":"To locate firewalls","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":541,"Question":"What are the port states determined by Nmap?","Option A":"Active, inactive, standby","Option B":"Open, half-open, closed","Option C":"Open, filtered, unfiltered","Option D":"Active, closed, unused","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":542,"Question":"What port does Telnet use?","Option A":22,"Option B":20,"Option C":80,"Option D":23,"Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":543,"Question":"Which of the following will allow foot printing to be conducted without detection?","Option A":"PingSweep","Option B":"Traceroute","Option C":"War Dialers","Option D":"ARIN","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":544,"Question":"Performing hacking activities with the intent on gaining visibility for an unfair situation is\ncalled\n\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0.","Option A":"Cracking","Option B":"Analysis","Option C":"Hacktivism","Option D":"Exploitation","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":545,"Question":"Why would a hacker use a proxy server?","Option A":"To create a stronger connection with the target.","Option B":"To create a ghost server on the network.","Option C":"To obtain a remote access connection","Option D":"To hide malicious activity on the network","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":546,"Question":"Which phase of hacking performs actual attack on a network or system?","Option A":"Reconnaissanc e","Option B":"Maintaining Access","Option C":"Scanning","Option D":"Gaining Access","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":547,"Question":"Sniffing is used to perform fingerprinting.","Option A":"Passive stack","Option B":"Active stack","Option C":"Passive banner grabbing","Option D":"Scanned","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":548,"Question":"Services running on a system are determined by\n_.","Option A":"The system\u2019s IP address","Option B":"The Active Directory","Option C":"The system\u2019s network name","Option D":"The port assigned","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":549,"Question":"What are the types of scanning?","Option A":"Port, network, and services","Option B":"Network, vulnerability, and port","Option C":"Passive, active, and interactive","Option D":"Server, client, and network","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":550,"Question":"Enumeration is part of what phase of ethical hacking","Option A":"Reconnaissanc e","Option B":"Maintaining Access","Option C":"Gaining Access","Option D":"Scanning","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":551,"Question":"\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0framework made cracking of vulnerabilities easy like point and click","Option A":"Net","Option B":"Metasploit","Option C":"Zeus","Option D":"Ettercap","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":552,"Question":"\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0is a popular IP address and port scanner.","Option A":"Snort","Option B":". SuperScan","Option C":"Angry IP Scanner","Option D":"Ettercap","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":553,"Question":"\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0is a popular tool used for network analysis in multiprotocol diverse network","Option A":"Snort","Option B":". SuperScan","Option C":"Angry IP Scanner","Option D":"Ettercap","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":554,"Question":"scans TCP ports and resolves different hostnames.","Option A":"Snort","Option B":". SuperScan","Option C":"Angry IP Scanner","Option D":"Ettercap","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":555,"Question":"What tool can be used to perform SNMP enumeration?","Option A":"DNSlookup","Option B":"Whois","Option C":"Nslookup","Option D":". IP Network Browser","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":556,"Question":"Wireshark is a tool.","Option A":"network protocol analysis","Option B":"network connection security","Option C":"connection analysis","Option D":"defending malicious packet-filtering","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":557,"Question":"Aircrack-ng is used for","Option A":"Firewall bypassing","Option B":"Wi-Fi attacks","Option C":"Packet filtering","Option D":"System password cracking","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":558,"Question":"Phishing is a form of\n\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0.","Option A":"Spamming","Option B":"Identify Theft","Option C":"Impersonation","Option D":"Scanning","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":559,"Question":"\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0is used for searching of multiple hosts in order to target just one specific open port.","Option A":"Ping Sweep","Option B":"Port scan","Option C":"Ipconfig","Option D":"Spamming","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":560,"Question":"ARP spoofing is often referred to as\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0","Option A":"Man-in-the-Mi ddle attack","Option B":"Denial-of-Servi ce attack","Option C":"Sniffing","Option D":"Spoofing","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":561,"Question":"\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0is a tool that allows you to look into network and analyze data going across the wire for network optimization, security and troubleshootin g purposes.","Option A":"Network analyzer","Option B":"Crypt tool","Option C":"John-the\n-Rippe","Option D":"Back track","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":562,"Question":"\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0is not a function of network analyzer tool","Option A":"Captures all network traffic","Option B":"Interprets or decodes what is found into a human-readabl e format.","Option C":"Displays it all in chronological order.","Option D":"Banner grabbing","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":563,"Question":"\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0protocol is used for network monitoring","Option A":"FTP","Option B":"SNMP","Option C":"RELNET","Option D":"ARP","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":564,"Question":"What is the attack called \u201cevil twin\u201d?","Option A":"rouge access poin","Option B":"ARP poisoning","Option C":"session hijacking","Option D":"MAC spoofing","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":565,"Question":"What are the forms of password cracking technique?","Option A":"Attack syllable","Option B":"Attack brute forcing","Option C":"Attacks hybrid","Option D":"All the above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":566,"Question":"We can eliminate many well-known network vulnerabilities by simply patch-ing your network\nhosts with their latest\n\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0and\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\n\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0.","Option A":"Hckers and Prackers","Option B":"Vendor software and firmware patches","Option C":"Software amd Hardware","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":567,"Question":"Network infrastructure vulnerabilities are the foundation for most technical security issues in\nyour information systems","Option A":"Operating system vulnerabilities","Option B":"Web vulnerabilities","Option C":"Wireless network vulnerabilities","Option D":"Network infrastructure vulnerabilities","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":568,"Question":".\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0attack, which can take down your Internet connection or your entire network","Option A":"MAC","Option B":"DOS","Option C":"IDS","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":569,"Question":"DOS stands for","Option A":"Detection of system","Option B":"Denial of Service","Option C":"Detection of servic","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":570,"Question":"IDS stands for","Option A":"Intrusion detection system","Option B":"Information documentation service","Option C":"Intrusion documentation system","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":571,"Question":"Which protocols are in use is vulnerable","Option A":". TCL","Option B":". SSL","Option C":"FTP","Option D":"SMTP","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":572,"Question":". SSL stands\nfor\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0A. Secure Sockets Layer","Option A":"Software Security Layer","Option B":"Socket security layer","Option C":"Secure Sockets Layer","Option D":"System software layer","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":573,"Question":"\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0include phishing, SQL injection, hacking, social engineering, spamming, denial of service attacks, Trojans, virus and worm attacks.","Option A":"Operating system vulnerabilities","Option B":"Web vulnerabilities","Option C":"Wireless network vulnerabilities","Option D":"Network infrastructure vulnerabilities","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":574,"Question":"Who invent worm attack\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0","Option A":"Brightn Godfrey","Option B":"Alan yeung","Option C":"Robert Morris","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":575,"Question":"A packet with no flags set is which type of scan?","Option A":"TCP","Option B":"XMAS","Option C":"IDLE","Option D":null,"Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":576,"Question":"Which is example of non-volatile memory.","Option A":"Flash memory","Option B":"Registers and Cache","Option C":"Process table","Option D":"Arp cache","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":577,"Question":"Blood, fingerprints, DNA these are examples\nof\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\n_","Option A":"Illustrative evidence","Option B":"Electronic evidence","Option C":"Documented evidence","Option D":"Substantial evidence","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":578,"Question":". Which of the following is not a characteristic of ethical hacker?","Option A":"Excellent knowledge of Windows.","Option B":"Understands the process of exploiting network vulnerabilities.","Option C":"Patience, persistence and perseverance","Option D":"Has the highest level of security for the organization.","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":579,"Question":"Attempting to gain access to a network using an employee\u2019s credentials is called the\n_ mode of ethical hacking.","Option A":"Local networking","Option B":"Social engineering","Option C":"Physical entry","Option D":"Remote networking","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":580,"Question":"The first phase of hacking an IT system is compromise of which foundation of security?","Option A":"Availability","Option B":"Confidentiality","Option C":"Integrity","Option D":"Authentication","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":581,"Question":"What is the purpose of a Denial of Service attack?","Option A":"Exploit a weakness in the TCP\/IP stack","Option B":"To execute a Trojan on a system","Option C":"To overload a system so it is no longer operational","Option D":"To shutdown services by turning them off","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":582,"Question":"What are some of the most common vulnerabilities that exist in a network or system?","Option A":"Changing manufacturer, or recommended, settings of a newly installed application.","Option B":"Additional unused features on commercial software packages.","Option C":"Utilizing open source application code","Option D":"Balancing security concerns with functionality and ease of use of a system.","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":583,"Question":"Why would a ping sweep be used?","Option A":"To identify live systems","Option B":"To locate live systems","Option C":"To identify open ports","Option D":"To locate firewalls","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":584,"Question":"A packet with no flags set is which type of scan?","Option A":"TCP","Option B":"XMAS","Option C":"IDLE","Option D":null,"Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":585,"Question":"Hackers use resources as","Option A":"Public computers at Libraries or kiosks","Option B":"Registered website","Option C":"Authorized computer at reception","Option D":"None of these","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":586,"Question":"Deep learning is subfield of","Option A":"Human Learning","Option B":"Machine Learning","Option C":"Source Learning","Option D":"None of these","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":587,"Question":"To determine what evidence to collect first, you should access evidences in order of volatility.","Option A":"Increasing","Option B":"Decreasing","Option C":"Any","Option D":"None of these","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":588,"Question":"Which of the following is not a best practice for minimizing security risk","Option A":"Use of encrypted msg","Option B":"Disable unused protocol","Option C":"Use of right software","Option D":"Injection of malware in system","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":589,"Question":"Unix is","Option A":"Uniplexed Information and computing service","Option B":"Unique information and computing service","Option C":"User information and computing service","Option D":"Universal information and computing service","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":590,"Question":"Most of the wireless vulnerability are in","Option A":"802.09 protocol","Option B":"802.01 protocol","Option C":"802.11 protocol","Option D":"802.10 protocol","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":591,"Question":"A ___ is a device that alters the physical quantity as it can cause a mechanical component to move after getting some input from sensor.","Option A":"Sensors","Option B":"Actuators","Option C":"Both a and b","Option D":"None of the above","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":592,"Question":"Encrypted data can be impossible to view without the","Option A":"Key","Option B":"Password","Option C":"Evidence","Option D":"None of the mentioned","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":593,"Question":"In EMCI Model, ___ is the phase during which crime is reported to some authority","Option A":"Awareness","Option B":"Planning","Option C":"Storage","Option D":"Collection","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":594,"Question":"When Accessing security and responding to security incidents a network analyser can help you","Option A":"View anomalous networking traffic","Option B":"Develop baseline of network activity","Option C":"Track down a intruder","Option D":"All of above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":595,"Question":"___ data is a data that is lost if the power is switched off.","Option A":"Non-volatile","Option B":"Volatile","Option C":"Primary","Option D":"Secondary","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":596,"Question":"An EMCI model follows as every activity occurs in sequence.","Option A":"Agile model","Option B":"Spiral model","Option C":"Waterfall model","Option D":"None of these","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":597,"Question":"Vulnerability is nothing but","Option A":"Weakness of a system","Option B":"Strong points of a system","Option C":"Both a & b","Option D":null,"Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":598,"Question":"Guidelines selecting hacking tools may consists of","Option A":"Study of user guide for commercial tools","Option B":"Detailed reports on the discovered vulnerabilities","Option C":"Updated and supported when needed","Option D":"All of these","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":599,"Question":"Digital Evidences must follow the requirements of the","Option A":"Ideal Evidence rule","Option B":"Best Evidence rule","Option C":"Exchange rule","Option D":"All of the mentioned","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":600,"Question":"Use of Ping sweep is","Option A":"Identify live systems","Option B":"Locate live systems","Option C":"Identify open ports","Option D":"Locate firewall","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":601,"Question":"Enemies of information security are","Option A":"Security researchers","Option B":"Hacktivists","Option C":"Cyber Terrorists","Option D":"All of these","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":602,"Question":"Network analyzer performs","Option A":"Capture all networking traffic","Option B":"Display it all in chronological order","Option C":"Decode what is found in human readable format","Option D":"All of these","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":603,"Question":"DMZ Stands for","Option A":"DeMiliterized Zone","Option B":"DeMail Zone","Option C":"DoMain Zone","Option D":null,"Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":604,"Question":"Device that transforms electrical signals into physical movements","Option A":"Sensors","Option B":"Actuators","Option C":"Switches","Option D":"Display","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":605,"Question":"Which obstacle will be handled by Investigation while achieving the goal of DFI","Option A":"Handle & Locate valid data from large storage","Option B":"If file is secured, investigator must find way to read the protected data in an unauthorized manner","Option C":"Every case is different, Identifying the techniques and tools will take long time","Option D":"All","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":606,"Question":"Ethical hacker does not require for effective operation.","Option A":"Assets to be protected","Option B":"Potential Threat source","Option C":"Support by organization","Option D":"Development life cycle","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":607,"Question":"___ jack allows connection of analog TVs and other similar output devices.","Option A":"RCA","Option B":"Audio out","Option C":"USB","Option D":"HDMI","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":608,"Question":"___ is competitor OS for Microsoft","Option A":"Linux","Option B":"Windows","Option C":"Symbian","Option D":"All of above","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":609,"Question":"Which of the following is not community hacked port number","Option A":18,"Option B":19,"Option C":20,"Option D":21,"Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":610,"Question":"Forest Fire Detection is an example of","Option A":"IOT Level 5","Option B":"IOT Level 6","Option C":"IOT Level 2","Option D":"IOT Level 1","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":611,"Question":"Keeping the software up to date is sign of","Option A":"Good security","Option B":"Bad security","Option C":"A and B","Option D":null,"Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":612,"Question":"Key criteria for handling of digital evidence is:","Option A":"Proper protocol should be followed for acquisition of evidence","Option B":"All material should be date and time stamped","Option C":"All Artifacts physical and digital should be collected and retained","Option D":"All","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":613,"Question":"Which of the following is a part of social engineering life cycle?","Option A":"Gaining information","Option B":"User Identification","Option C":"System monitoring","Option D":"Shoulder Surfing","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":614,"Question":"A chain of custody form is used to document which of the following?","Option A":"Investigator who has been in contact with evidence in a case","Option B":"Anyone who has not been in contact with evidence in a case","Option C":"Anyone who has been in contact with evidence in an case","Option D":null,"Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":615,"Question":"___ is one with very little knowledge about hacking but uses free tools and internet to perform malicious act.","Option A":"Ex Employee","Option B":"Script kiddies","Option C":"Malicious Users","Option D":"Gray Hat","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":616,"Question":"Web server provide as security mechanism.","Option A":"ACL","Option B":"Root directory","Option C":"Both A and B","Option D":null,"Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":617,"Question":"___ tool is most versatile security tool for such security checks as port scanning and firewall testing","Option A":"Ether peek","Option B":"Ettercap","Option C":"Net cat","Option D":"Nmap","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":618,"Question":"Which of the following term suits more to White Hat Hackers?","Option A":"Former Black Hat","Option B":"Former Gray Hat","Option C":"Fame Gainer","Option D":"Security Professional","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":619,"Question":"IOT stands for","Option A":"Internet of Technology","Option B":"Intranet of Things","Option C":"Internet of Things","Option D":"Information of Things","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":620,"Question":"TCP is most widely used protocol, that is used by web browsers (along with HTTP, HTTPS application layer protocols), email programs (SMTP application layer protocol) and file transfer (FTP).","Option A":"Application Layer","Option B":"Transport Layer","Option C":"Network Layer","Option D":"Link Layer","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":621,"Question":"The correct Procedure followed according to the chain of custody for electronic evidence is:","Option A":"A-b-c-e-d-f","Option B":"A-c-b-d-e-f","Option C":"C-a-d-f-e-b","Option D":"C-a-d-e-f-b","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":622,"Question":"One of the example of hackers on the basis of their work and mind set is","Option A":"Evading an intrusion prevention system","Option B":"Supporting security","Option C":"Promoting pollution in environment","Option D":"None of these","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":623,"Question":"IEEE 802.11 is a collection of wireless local area network (WLAN) communication standards, including extensive description of the","Option A":"Link layer","Option B":"Application layer","Option C":"Transport layer","Option D":"Network layer","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":624,"Question":"SQLMap supports","Option A":"Open source and cross platforms","Option B":"Supports database engines","Option C":"Sniffing networks","Option D":"All of these","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":625,"Question":"What is rootkit?","Option A":"A simple tool to gain access to the root of the windows system","Option B":"An invasive program that affects file, including the kernel and libraries.","Option C":"Tool to perform a buffer overflow","Option D":null,"Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":626,"Question":"Computer programs that mimic the way of human brain processes information is called","Option A":"Computer networks","Option B":"Circuits Network","Option C":"Neural Network","Option D":"Human Network","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":627,"Question":"Apache Mahout is used for training","Option A":"Support Vector Machines (SVMs)","Option B":"Self-organizing maps","Option C":"Hierarchical clustering","Option D":"Naive Bayes Classifier","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":628,"Question":"Which of the following application are hacking targets on your network","Option A":"Messaging application","Option B":"Email","Option C":"A and B","Option D":null,"Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":629,"Question":"Ethical behind training how to hack a system","Option A":"Think like hacker","Option B":"Hacking system without permission","Option C":"To hack vulnerable networking","Option D":"To corrupt software using malware","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":630,"Question":"Hacking for a cause is called","Option A":"Active Hacking","Option B":"Hacktivism","Option C":"Activism","Option D":"Black hat hacking","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":631,"Question":"___ belong to Email Attack","Option A":"Email Bomb","Option B":"Banner","Option C":"Both A and B","Option D":null,"Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":632,"Question":"Which of the following is not community hacked port number","Option A":18,"Option B":19,"Option C":20,"Option D":21,"Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":633,"Question":"A proof that is introduced in the form of physical object is referred as","Option A":"Electronic evidence","Option B":"Documented evidence","Option C":"Substantial evidence","Option D":"Physical evidence","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":634,"Question":"Illustrative evidence is also called as","Option A":"Demonstrative Evidence","Option B":"Explainable Evidence","Option C":"Substantial Evidence","Option D":"Documented Evidence","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":635,"Question":"Planning and reconnaissance phase of penetration testing in hacking","Option A":"Defines salary if hacker for testing","Option B":"Defines test goals and intelligence is gathered","Option C":"Avoids inspection in testing phase","Option D":"Implements random process in penetration testing","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":636,"Question":"Guidelines selecting hacking tools may consists of","Option A":"Study the user guide for commercial tools","Option B":"Detailed reports on the discovered vulnerabilities","Option C":"Updated and supports when needed","Option D":"All of these","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":637,"Question":"Which of the following is not a computer networking device.","Option A":"Router","Option B":"Firewall","Option C":"Generic Host","Option D":null,"Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":638,"Question":"Which is not the type of tool that is used by Ethical Hackers?","Option A":"Nmap","Option B":".NET Framework","Option C":"Superscan","Option D":"ToneLoc","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":639,"Question":"The message transfer capability can be set up on connections, either using handshakes such as ___ or without handshakes\/acknowledgments such as","Option A":"TCP, UDP","Option B":"UDP, TCP","Option C":"HTTP, CoAP","Option D":"CoAP, HTTP","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":640,"Question":"Piggybacking onto a network through an insecure wireless configuration is a","Option A":"Default windows OS configuration","Option B":"Weak SQL server administrator password","Option C":"Operating system attack","Option D":"Network infrastructure attack","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":641,"Question":"When assessing the reliability of digital evidence, the investigator is concerned with whether the computer that generated the evidence was functioning normally and:","Option A":"Whether chain of custody was maintained","Option B":"Whether there are indications that the actual digital evidence was tampered with","Option C":"Whether the evidence was properly secured in transmit","Option D":"Whether the evidence media compatible with forensic machines","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":642,"Question":"In forensic investigation, in which format the computer and data would be, during the acquisition of the media","Option A":"Protected","Option B":"Non protected","Option C":"Partially protected","Option D":"Hidden","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":643,"Question":"In an e-mail harassment case, the act of sending threatening messages via a web-based e-mail service can leave a number of traces. Investigator can obtain information from","Option A":"Offender\u2019s hard drive","Option B":"Web server access logs","Option C":"IP addresses","Option D":"All of the mentioned","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":644,"Question":"___ is executed through the searching of single host for open ports","Option A":"Port Scanning","Option B":"Network Scanning","Option C":"Vulnerability Scanning","Option D":null,"Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":645,"Question":"___ is not a commercial firewall","Option A":"Nmap","Option B":"EtherPeek","Option C":"Ethereal","Option D":"WebInspect","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":646,"Question":"Ethical hackers should:","Option A":"Stop and contact law enforcement whenever they detect a crime","Option B":"When their organization\u2019s policy specifies","Option C":"When the task is beyond their training and experience","Option D":"When they would be committing an offense by performing an action","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":647,"Question":"Which of the following statement is wrong?","Option A":"Investigator should not declare any confidential matters.","Option B":"Investigator should respect privacy of others","Option C":"Investigator should be honest and trustworthy","Option D":null,"Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":648,"Question":"In ___ system has a single node as well as data is stored and analyzed in the cloud application is cloud based.","Option A":"IOT Level 1","Option B":"IOT Level 2","Option C":"IOT Level 3","Option D":"IOT Level 4","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":649,"Question":"In ___ multiple large messages can quickly fill total storage capacity of an email server","Option A":"Storage overload","Option B":"Bandwidth blocking","Option C":"A & B","Option D":null,"Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":650,"Question":"___ and ___ supports methods such as GET, PUT, POST and DELETE.","Option A":"HTTP, CoAP","Option B":"Websocket, MQTT","Option C":"XMPP, AMQP","Option D":"None of these","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":651,"Question":"The ARM micro-controller architecture is","Option A":"Load-Store RISC Architecture","Option B":"Load Store CISC Architecture","Option C":"ROM Based Architecture","Option D":"Hardwired Architecture","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":652,"Question":"ZigBee is one of the most popular wireless technologies used by","Option A":"WSN","Option B":"MANET","Option C":"Both a and b","Option D":"None of the above","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":653,"Question":"___ form the basis of various applications.","Option A":"Algorithms","Option B":"Programs","Option C":"Code","Option D":"Testing","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":654,"Question":"Scanning is performed in which phase of a pen test?","Option A":"Pre-Attack","Option B":"Attack","Option C":"Post-Attack","Option D":"Reconnaissance","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":655,"Question":"802.15.4 also called as","Option A":"Ethernet","Option B":"Wifi","Option C":"WiMax","Option D":"LR-WPAN","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":656,"Question":"Which of the following are network analysing tools are supported by unix OS","Option A":"Ethereal","Option B":"Ettercap","Option C":"Dsniff","Option D":"All of above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":657,"Question":"Digital Evidences may be in the form of","Option A":"Email Messages","Option B":"Office file","Option C":"Registry","Option D":"All of the above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":658,"Question":"To access the security of the system one must understand ___ of the hacker.","Option A":"Nature","Option B":"Hobbies","Option C":"Mindset","Option D":"None of these","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":659,"Question":"Do not store old sensitive or otherwise non public files on your web server is countermeasure for","Option A":"Directory traversal attack","Option B":"XSS","Option C":"SQL injection","Option D":"All of above","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":660,"Question":"6LOWPAN provides data transfer rates of","Option A":"250Kb\/s","Option B":"1.5 Mb\/s","Option C":"100Mbit\/s","Option D":"1 Gbit\/s","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":661,"Question":"WebSocket APIs ___ network traffic and latency as there is no overhead for connection setup and termination requests for each messages.","Option A":"Reduce","Option B":"Increase","Option C":"Both a and b","Option D":"None of the above","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":662,"Question":"ALU of ARM Microcontroller is ___ bit","Option A":8,"Option B":32,"Option C":64,"Option D":10,"Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":663,"Question":"To determine what evidence to collect first, you should access evidences in order of volatility.","Option A":"Increasing","Option B":"Decreasing","Option C":"Any","Option D":"None of the above","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":664,"Question":"IBMs Watson supercomputer comes under","Option A":"General AI","Option B":"Super AI","Option C":"Narrow AI","Option D":"All of these","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":665,"Question":"SQL stands for","Option A":"Simple Query Language","Option B":"Structured Query Language","Option C":"Standard Query Language","Option D":null,"Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":666,"Question":"The most difficult task for an evidence handler is to substantiate the ___ at the judicial proceedings.","Option A":"Copied Evidences","Option B":"Persistent Evidence","Option C":"Collected Evidence","Option D":"Lost Evidence","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":667,"Question":"The amateur in the field of hacking who don\u2019t have many skills about coding and in-depth working of security and hacking tools are called","Option A":"Sponsored hackers","Option B":"Whistle hackers","Option C":"Hacktivists","Option D":"Script Kiddies","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":668,"Question":"Sensors are used in smartphones, vehicles, aircrafts and other applications to detect orientation of an object shake, tap, tilt, motion, positioning, shock or vibration.","Option A":"IR","Option B":"Accelerometer","Option C":"Image","Option D":"Proximity","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":669,"Question":"Ethical Hacking can be","Option A":"Technical","Option B":"Non-Technical","Option C":"Both A and B","Option D":"None of the above","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":670,"Question":"An IOT device can collect various types of data from the on-board or attached sensors, such as","Option A":"Temperature","Option B":"Humidity","Option C":"Motion","Option D":"All of the above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":671,"Question":"Hackers use a proxy server","Option A":"To create a stronger connection with target","Option B":"To create a ghost server on the network","Option C":"To obtain a remote access connection","Option D":"To hide malicious activity on the network","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":672,"Question":"Artificial Intelligence is the ability of a computer program to","Option A":"Learn and Earn","Option B":"Learn and Experience","Option C":"Learn and Think","Option D":"Learn and Teach","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":673,"Question":"Some AI Languages are","Option A":"PROLOG","Option B":"LISP","Option C":"NLP","Option D":"All of the above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":674,"Question":"Case Background: The accused in the case were working in BPO, that was handling the business of a multinational bank. The accused, during the course of their work hand obtained the personal identification numbers (PIN) and other confidential information of the bank\u2019s customers","Option A":"A-b-c-d-e","Option B":"E-d-c-b-a","Option C":"B-c-a-e-d","Option D":"D-b-c-e-A","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":675,"Question":"Which of the following tool cannot be use to crack password?","Option A":"LC4bs","Option B":"Pwdump","Option C":"John the Ripper","Option D":"SuperScan","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":676,"Question":"A couple of considerations are involved when dealing with digital evidence check, the incorrect consideration involved:","Option A":"Work with the original evidence to develop procedures","Option B":"Use clean Collecting media","Option C":"Document any extra scope","Option D":"Consider safety of personnel at the scene","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":677,"Question":"Criminal minded individuals who work for terrorist organizations and steal information of nations and other secret intelligence for economical and revenge type of gain are","Option A":"State sponsored hackers","Option B":"White hat hackers","Option C":"Cyber terrorists","Option D":"Red hat hackers","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":678,"Question":"What is the meaning of CART in forensics science?","Option A":"Statistical Application development Report Team","Option B":"Classification and Regression Tree","Option C":"Computer Analysis and Response team","Option D":"Computer Application Research team","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":679,"Question":"Following is not web application security vulnerability","Option A":"SQL injection","Option B":"Cross Site Scripting","Option C":"Firewall","Option D":"Directory traversal","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":680,"Question":"In Mobile communication, 4G includes ___","Option A":"LTE","Option B":"UMTS","Option C":"CDMA","Option D":"CDMA 2000","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":681,"Question":"WAF stands for","Option A":"Web Application Firewall","Option B":"Wireless Application Firewall","Option C":"Wired Application Firewall","Option D":"Wide Application Firewll","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":682,"Question":"Vulnerabilities in database management system are","Option A":"Loose access permissions","Option B":"Excessive retension of sensitive data","Option C":"Aggregation personly identifiable information","Option D":"All of above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":683,"Question":"Ethical behind training how to hack system","Option A":"Think like hacker","Option B":"Hacking system without permission","Option C":"To hack vulnerable networking","Option D":"To corrupt software using malware","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":684,"Question":"The Y dimension of AI philosophy in a 3 dimensional representation consits of ---","Option A":"Cognition","Option B":"Logic","Option C":"Interface","Option D":"Computation","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":685,"Question":"___ is a tool for ethical hacking web application","Option A":"Netsparker","Option B":"Bursuite","Option C":"Angry IP Scanner","Option D":"GFI LanGuard","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":686,"Question":"Which of the following is not network analyzer detection tool","Option A":"Sniffelet","Option B":"PromiscDetect","Option C":"NetFlow traffic Analyzer","Option D":"All of the above","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":687,"Question":"___ is a tool that scan vulnerability in web application","Option A":"GFI LanGuard","Option B":"Probely","Option C":"Bursuite","Option D":"Angry IP Scanner","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":688,"Question":"Which of the following hold the highest value of evidence in the court?","Option A":"Documentary","Option B":"Demonstrative","Option C":"Testimonial","Option D":"Real","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":689,"Question":"Obstacles(s) to protect from hackers attacks","Option A":"Wide spread use of networking and internet connectivity","Option B":"Greater number and availability of hacking tools","Option C":"A and B","Option D":"None of these","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":690,"Question":"Banners are intended for","Option A":"Networking administration","Option B":"White hat hacking","Option C":"A & B","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":691,"Question":"Is not one of the following different stages of hacking","Option A":"Reconnaissance","Option B":"Scanning","Option C":"Compiling","Option D":"Maintaining Access","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":692,"Question":"___ tool is used for ping sweeps and port scanning","Option A":"Sam spade","Option B":"SuperScan","Option C":"Both a & b","Option D":null,"Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":693,"Question":"___ Foot Printing is","Option A":"Measuring the shoe size of an ethical hacker","Option B":"Accumulation of data by gathering information on a target","Option C":"Scanning a target network to detect operating system types","Option D":null,"Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":694,"Question":"To examine intelligently while gathering information about the target is","Option A":"Investigation","Option B":"Scanning","Option C":"Tracing","Option D":"Intelligent","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":695,"Question":"In 1995, on which topic the International organization was found?","Option A":"Computer security","Option B":"Computer Evidence","Option C":"Computer Network","Option D":"Computer Graphics","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":696,"Question":"Hosting Obscene profiles and creating fake profiles comes under section ___ of law","Option A":"66 of Information Technology act","Option B":"67 of Information Technology act","Option C":"68 of Information Technology act","Option D":"None of the above","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":697,"Question":"The Evidence or proof that is obtained from the electronic source is called as","Option A":"Digital Evidence","Option B":"Explainable Evidence","Option C":"Demonstrative Evidence","Option D":"Substantial Evidence","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":698,"Question":"When assessing security and responding to security incidents a network analyzer can help you","Option A":"View anomalous networking traffic","Option B":"Develop baseline of network activity","Option C":"Track down a intruder","Option D":"All of above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":699,"Question":"___ norms should not satisfy by Investigator.","Option A":"To be Honest and Trustworthy","Option B":"Avoid harm to others","Option C":"To declare any confidential matters or knowledge","Option D":"To respect privacy of others","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":700,"Question":"Which one is the characteristic of digital evidence rule","Option A":"Admissible","Option B":"Complete","Option C":"Authentic","Option D":"All of the above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":701,"Question":"Hash test analysis on digital evidence ensures that the data obtained from bit-by-bit copy procedure is ___ and reflects the nature of original evidence","Option A":"Not corrupt","Option B":"Not correct","Option C":"Admissible","Option D":"Reliable","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":702,"Question":"In term of digital evidence, the internet is an example of:","Option A":"Open computer systems","Option B":"Communication systems","Option C":"Embedded computer systems","Option D":"None of the above","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":703,"Question":"The criminological principle states that contact between two items will result in an exchange, is:","Option A":"Locards exchange principle","Option B":"Differential Association Theory","Option C":"Beccaria\u2019s Social Contract","Option D":"None of the above","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":704,"Question":"How many models of Digital Forensics?","Option A":6,"Option B":4,"Option C":5,"Option D":3,"Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":705,"Question":"Use of Port Scanning is","Option A":"Scanning network to check who is there","Option B":"Identify network to check who is there","Option C":"Scanning network who is not there","Option D":null,"Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":706,"Question":"Which of the following is not a email bomb attack","Option A":"Attachment overloading attack","Option B":"Connection attack","Option C":"DoS","Option D":"Autoresponder attack","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":707,"Question":"A Branch of Science that deals with helping machines find solutions to complex problems in human like fashion is called","Option A":"Embedded system","Option B":"Cyber security","Option C":"Artificial Intelligence","Option D":"Internet of things","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":708,"Question":"On which things the forensic science is applied?","Option A":"Big Data","Option B":"Hacking","Option C":"Criminal and civil action","Option D":"Security","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":709,"Question":"Home automation is an example of","Option A":"IOT Level 2","Option B":"IOT Level 1","Option C":"IOT Level 4","Option D":"IOT Level 3","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":710,"Question":"MQTT Topics are","Option A":"Simple floating point","Option B":"Simple Integer","Option C":"Simple symbol","Option D":"Simple string","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":711,"Question":"Protocols are 802.3. Ethernet, 802.16 WiMax, 2G\/3G\/LTE-Cellular, 802.11 Wifi, 802.15.4-LRWPAN","Option A":"Application Layer","Option B":"Transport Layer","Option C":"Network layer","Option D":"Link Layer","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":712,"Question":"The AI technique that allows computers to understand relationship between objects and events is called","Option A":"Heuristic processing","Option B":"Cognitive science","Option C":"Relative Symbolism","Option D":"Pattern Matching","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":713,"Question":"___ uses Natural language processing for photo tagging.","Option A":"Facebook","Option B":"Whatsapp","Option C":"Gmail","Option D":"All of these","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":714,"Question":"Although crime scenes are typically photographed, it is good idea to create diagrams of the crime scene because:","Option A":"Diagramming is a common crime scene technician\u2019s skill, however, it requires continual practice.","Option B":"The process of creating a diagram can result in a digital investigator noticing an important item of evidence that would otherwise have been missed.","Option C":null,"Option D":null,"Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":715,"Question":"Social Engineering is the art of","Option A":"Making online friends","Option B":"Exploiting the human elements to gain access to unauthorized resources","Option C":"Searching on internet for various things.","Option D":null,"Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":716,"Question":"Malicious software(malware) attack is among the type of","Option A":"Application based attack","Option B":"Operating system attack","Option C":"Network infrastructure attack","Option D":"Non-technical attack","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":717,"Question":"Knowledge of ethical hacker for evaluating results may consists of","Option A":"Evaluating result","Option B":"Corelating specific vulnerabilities","Option C":"Simple evaluation process","Option D":"All of these","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":718,"Question":"UDP Stands for","Option A":"User Datagram protocol","Option B":"Usage datagram protocol","Option C":"Usecase datagram protocol","Option D":null,"Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":719,"Question":"DOS Denial of Service attack means","Option A":"Breaking file-system security","Option B":"Flooding a network with too many requests","Option C":"Access to malicious software(s) from internet","Option D":"Exploiting specific protocol","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":720,"Question":"AVR full form is","Option A":"Action virtual RAM","Option B":"Advance Visible Risk","Option C":"Advanced Virtual RISC","Option D":"None of the above","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":721,"Question":"Pushed the logical formalism to integrate reasoning with knowledge","Option A":"Bertrand Russel","Option B":"Marvin Minsky","Option C":"Charles Babbage","Option D":"Aristotle","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":722,"Question":"Concept of DMZ is used in","Option A":"Firewall","Option B":"Antivirus","Option C":"A & B","Option D":null,"Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":723,"Question":"Ping sweeping, port scanning, grabbing, banners etc. comes under","Option A":"Application Hacking","Option B":"Network Hacking","Option C":"A & B","Option D":null,"Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":724,"Question":"In Nmap tool sP command is used for","Option A":"Ping Scan","Option B":"Port scan","Option C":"Ping Sweep","Option D":"All of the above","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":725,"Question":"SNMP Stands for","Option A":"Single Network Management Protocol","Option B":"Simple Network mobile protocol","Option C":"Simple Network management protocol","Option D":null,"Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":726,"Question":"Flooding a network with too many requests this type of attack comes under which category?","Option A":"Non-technical attack","Option B":"Operating system attacks","Option C":"Network infrastructure attacks","Option D":"Application and other specialized attacks","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":727,"Question":"A Hacker who identifies and exploits weaknesses in telephone instead of computer is","Option A":"Script kiddies","Option B":"Hacktivist","Option C":"Phreaker","Option D":"Cracker","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":728,"Question":"The most skilled hackers in the hackers community are","Option A":"White hat hackers","Option B":"Elite hackers","Option C":"Licensed Penetration Testers","Option D":"Red hat hackers","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":729,"Question":"Which statement of the following is incorrect in view of ethical hacker?","Option A":"They are hired professions to penetrate in system","Option B":"They find system vulnerabilities without proper authorization","Option C":"They help making system secure and better.","Option D":null,"Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":730,"Question":"Case: The complaint received an obscene email from an unknown email id. The complaint also noticed that obscene profiles along with photographs of his daughter had been uploaded on matrimonial sites.","Option A":"A-b-c-d","Option B":"B-a-d-c","Option C":"B-a-c-d","Option D":"D-b-a-c","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":731,"Question":"Case Background: The complaint stated that some unknown person had created an email-id using her name and had used this id to post messages on five web pages describing her as a call-girl along with her contact numbers. As a result she started","Option A":"Creation of username to access and view web pages","Option B":"The investigating team obtained the access logs of the public group and the message to identify the IP Addresses used to post the messages.","Option C":"The ISP was identified with the help of publicly available internet sites.","Option D":null,"Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":732,"Question":"In IDIP model, the goal of ___ phase is to ensure that operation and infrastructure are able to fully supports an investigation.","Option A":"Deployment","Option B":"Readiness","Option C":"Collection","Option D":"Examination","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":733,"Question":"EEDIP model contains some of following phases.","Option A":"Planning, search and collection","Option B":"Identification, Collection and examination","Option C":"Collect, report and evidence report","Option D":"Readiness, Deployment, Review","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":734,"Question":"An example of IOT Level 3 system is","Option A":"Home Automation","Option B":"Smart Irrigation","Option C":"Tracking Package Handling","Option D":"All of the above","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":735,"Question":"___ is the process of collection, Organizing and analysing large sets of data","Option A":"Infrastructure-as-a-service","Option B":"Platform-as-a-service","Option C":"Software-as-a-service","Option D":"Big data analytics","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":736,"Question":"___ uses a 32-bit address scheme that allows total of 232 or 4,294,967,296 addresses","Option A":"IPv4","Option B":"IPv6","Option C":"6LOWPAN","Option D":"None of the above","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":737,"Question":"Zigbee offers data rates upto ___ and range from ___ depending on the power output and environmental conditions.","Option A":"250KB\/s, 10 to 100m","Option B":"300KB\/s, 5 to 10m","Option C":"250KB\/s, 5 to 10 m","Option D":"300KB\/s, 10 to 100m","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":738,"Question":"In a Wireless sensor network a node which are unable to perform an operation because of power failure and environment effects is known as","Option A":"Normal node","Option B":"Selfish Node","Option C":"Failed node","Option D":"Badly failed node","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":739,"Question":"Natural language Understanding is used in","Option A":"Natural Language Interfaces","Option B":"System for understanding text","Option C":"Natural Language Front end","Option D":"All of the above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":740,"Question":"The term used for describing common sense part of problem solving is called","Option A":"Analytical","Option B":"Value based","Option C":"Heuristic","Option D":"Critical","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":741,"Question":"___ Malicious Hackers may search","Option A":"Organizer\u2019s name","Option B":"Computer network and systems names","Option C":"IP Address","Option D":"All of these","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":742,"Question":"State the purpose of Digital crime investigation phase in IDIP model?","Option A":"To ensure infrastructure should be supported for investigation","Option B":"To analyze physical evidence","Option C":"To review whole investigation","Option D":"To collect and analyze the digital evidence obtained from physical evidence","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":743,"Question":"EMIC model was proposed by","Option A":"Palmar","Option B":"Olivier","Option C":"Ciardhuian","Option D":"None of these","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":744,"Question":"A Procedure to find the digital evidence is called","Option A":"Investigation","Option B":"Process","Option C":"Authentication","Option D":"All of these","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":745,"Question":"Which of the following is\/are substantial Evidences?","Option A":"DNA samples","Option B":"Bill Invoice","Option C":"Casts of footprints","Option D":"Both DNA samples and casts of footprints","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":746,"Question":"Once you have collected the raw data from volatile sources you may be able to","Option A":"Delete the data","Option B":"Shutdown the system","Option C":"All of the above","Option D":"Restart the system","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":747,"Question":"How many phases in Road map for digital forensic research","Option A":5,"Option B":6,"Option C":4,"Option D":7,"Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":748,"Question":"Which is not a context involved in identifying a piece of digital evidence","Option A":"Physical","Option B":"Logical","Option C":"Electrical","Option D":"Legal","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":749,"Question":"Digital evidence report does contain","Option A":"Identity of the reporting agency","Option B":"Case Investigator","Option C":"Descriptive list of items submitted for examination","Option D":"All of the mentioned","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":750,"Question":"Having a member of the search team trained to handle digital evidence","Option A":"Can reduce the number of people who handle the evidence","Option B":"Can help in the presentation of the case","Option C":"Can help in the Integrity of the evidence","Option D":"All of the above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":751,"Question":"What is the primary of goal of Ethical hacker?","Option A":"Avoid detection","Option B":"Hacking","Option C":"Find Security weakness","Option D":"Testing","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":752,"Question":"Ethical hacker does not make user in finding system vulnerabilities?","Option A":"Penetrating testing","Option B":"Red teaming","Option C":"Shoulder surfing","Option D":"Intrusion testing","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":753,"Question":"What type of Ethical hack tests access to the physical infrastructure?","Option A":"Internal Network","Option B":"Remote Network","Option C":"External Network","Option D":"Physical access","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":754,"Question":"Knowledge of ethical hacker for evaluation results may consists of","Option A":"Evaluating result","Option B":"Corelating specific vulnerabilities","Option C":"Simple evaluation process","Option D":"All of these","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":755,"Question":"Which is the most secure operating system out of the following?","Option A":"Windows","Option B":"DOS","Option C":"Novell Netware","Option D":"Android","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":756,"Question":"Which of the following is likely to have highest knowledge about system vulnerabilities?","Option A":"Gray hat","Option B":"White hat","Option C":"Malicious users","Option D":"Script kiddies","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":757,"Question":"___ that sends social\/, political messages may be as rumors.","Option A":"Cracking","Option B":"Analysis","Option C":"Hactivism","Option D":"Exploitation","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":758,"Question":"The theory of mechanization was developed by","Option A":"Bertland Russel","Option B":"Turing","Option C":"Aristotle","Option D":"Charles Babbage","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":759,"Question":"If a security audit is conducted by network administrator on internal network then it is known as","Option A":"Security testing","Option B":"Gray Box testing","Option C":"Black Box testing","Option D":"White Box testing","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":760,"Question":"Ethical hacking means","Option A":"Identifying weaknesses in computer system and network","Option B":"Coming up with counter measures that protect the weaknesses","Option C":"Tests organization information system against a verity of attacks","Option D":"All of above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":761,"Question":"Hacker attacks against insecure web applications via HTTP make up the majority of all","Option A":"Internet related attack","Option B":"Message related attack","Option C":"A & B","Option D":null,"Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":762,"Question":"Cracking passwords and encryption mechanism","Option A":"Non-technical attack","Option B":"Application attack","Option C":"Network-infrastructure attack","Option D":"Operating system attack","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":763,"Question":"An Excessive amount of ARP request can not be sign of","Option A":"ARP poisoning attack","Option B":"ARP spoofing","Option C":"ARP tracking","Option D":"None of these","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":764,"Question":"___ is a common example of supervised learning","Option A":"Voice recognition","Option B":"Programming","Option C":"Coding","Option D":"None of these","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":765,"Question":"In Mobile communication, 3G includes ___ and ___","Option A":"UMTS and CDMA 2000","Option B":"GSM and CDMA","Option C":"GSM and UMTS","Option D":"GMS and CDMA 2000","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":766,"Question":"___ makes sense of unlabelled data without having any predefined dataset for its training.","Option A":"Unsupervised learning","Option B":"Supervised learning","Option C":"Human learning","Option D":"Machine learning","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":767,"Question":"RMDFR stands for","Option A":"Regional Marketing Director flood Retail","Option B":"Road Map for digital forensic Research","Option C":"Real managing Director for research","Option D":null,"Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":768,"Question":"___ analyses the training data and produces function, which can be used for mapping new examples.","Option A":"Unsupervised learning","Option B":"Deep learning Algorithm","Option C":"Supervised learning algorithm","Option D":"Neural network algorithm","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":769,"Question":"ARM handles all the computations that make a computer work (taking input, doing calculations and producing output)","Option A":"CPU","Option B":"GPU","Option C":"Both a and b","Option D":"None of these","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":770,"Question":"___ provides the users the ability to develop and deploy application in the cloud using the development tools, application programming interfaces (APIs), software libraries and services provided by the cloud service provider.","Option A":"IasS","Option B":"PasS","Option C":"SaaS","Option D":"All of these","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":771,"Question":"___ security mainly focuses on overall IOT system to identify different security challenges, to design different security frameworks and to provide proper security guidelines in order to maintain the security of a network.","Option A":"System","Option B":"Application","Option C":"Network","Option D":"All of these","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":772,"Question":"Which of the following is capable of making systems that can learn new tasks without human guidance but require prior training?","Option A":"Deep Learning","Option B":"Neural Networks","Option C":"Machine learning","Option D":"None of these","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":773,"Question":"Which is not IOT based home application","Option A":"Smoke detectors","Option B":"Intrusion Detection system","Option C":"Gas detectors","Option D":"Weather monitoring","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":774,"Question":"An IOT system comprises of ___ that provide sensing, actuation, monitoring and control functions.","Option A":"Communication","Option B":"Device","Option C":"Security","Option D":"Application","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":775,"Question":"Noise Monitoring is an example of","Option A":"IOT Level 3","Option B":"IOT Level 4","Option C":"IOT Level 5","Option D":"IOT Level 6","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":776,"Question":"IOT devices are usually integrated into the ___ that allows them to communicate and exchange data with other devices and systems","Option A":"Internet","Option B":"Intra network","Option C":"Inter network","Option D":"Information network","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":777,"Question":"The ___ layers are responsible for sending IP Datagram from the source network to the destination network.","Option A":"Network layer","Option B":"Application layer","Option C":"Transport layer","Option D":"Link layer","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":778,"Question":"___ is useful for time-sensitive applications that have very small data units to exchange and do not want the overhead of connection setup.","Option A":"TCP","Option B":"UDP","Option C":"CoAP","Option D":"HTTP","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":779,"Question":"The AI system that can interact with the computer and understand natural language spoken by human is called","Option A":"Gaming","Option B":"Natural Language Processing","Option C":"Expert Systems","Option D":"Speech Recognition systems","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":780,"Question":"___ is a data-centric middleware standard for device-to-device or machine to machine-to-machine communication.","Option A":"WebSocket","Option B":"Data Distribution Service","Option C":"Constrained Application protocol","Option D":"None of these","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":781,"Question":"___ Is based on TCP and allows streams of messages to be send back and forth between the client and server while keeping the TCP connection open.","Option A":"WebSocket","Option B":"MQTT","Option C":"DDS","Option D":"AMQP","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":782,"Question":"Power consumption of ASIC is","Option A":"High","Option B":"Low","Option C":"Zero","Option D":"None of these","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":783,"Question":"Which of the following is not involved in audit report of system security?","Option A":"Review Business Process","Option B":"Checklist","Option C":"Security Policies","Option D":"Measures to prevent attacks","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":784,"Question":"Information gathered by Netscan tool pro do not include","Option A":"Start IP Address","Option B":"No of target IP addresses","Option C":"Encryption key","Option D":"All of these","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":785,"Question":"Specialize in clustering information and recognizing complex patterns, giving computers the ability to use more sophisticated process to analyse data","Option A":"Artificial Intelligence","Option B":"Machine Learning","Option C":"Neural Network","Option D":"Deep Learning","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":786,"Question":"IOT Protocols in ___ are HTTP, CoAP, Websockets, MQTT, XMPP, DDS, AMQP","Option A":"Application layer","Option B":"Transport layer","Option C":"Network layer","Option D":"Link layer","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":787,"Question":"In which of the following, learning means recognizing and understanding the input data and making wise decision based on the supplied data.","Option A":"Actual learning","Option B":"Machine learning","Option C":"Virtual learning","Option D":"Deep Learning","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":788,"Question":"___ sensors detect the presence or absence of a nearby object without any physical contact","Option A":"Proximity","Option B":"Image","Option C":"Accelerometer","Option D":"IR","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":789,"Question":"___ is data-centric middleware standard for device-to-device or machine-to-machine communication","Option A":"DDS","Option B":"XMPP","Option C":"AMQP","Option D":"None of the above","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":790,"Question":"Like HTTP, ___ is a web transfer protocol and uses a request-response model, however it runs on top of UDP instead of TCP.","Option A":"MQTT","Option B":"CoAP","Option C":"XMPP","Option D":"AMQP","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":791,"Question":"To validate your evidence, you must have","Option A":"Education","Option B":"Trust","Option C":"Knowledge","Option D":"Power and skill","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":792,"Question":"REST architectural constraints are as follows:","Option A":"Client-server and stateless","Option B":"cacheable and uniform interface","Option C":"Layered system and code on demand","Option D":"All of these","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":793,"Question":"___ is a branch of science that deals with programming the systems in such way that they automatically learn and improve with experience","Option A":"Artificial Intelligence","Option B":"Machine learning","Option C":"Neural network","Option D":"Deep learning","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":794,"Question":"When assessing the reliability of digital evidence. The investigator is concerned with whether the computer that generated the evidence was functioning normally, and:","Option A":"Whether chain of custody was maintained","Option B":"Whether there are indications that the actual digital evidence was tampered with","Option C":"Whether the evidence was properly secured in transmit","Option D":null,"Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":795,"Question":"Forensic categories of devices where evidence can be found","Option A":"Internet-based","Option B":"Stand-alone computers or devices","Option C":"Mobile devices","Option D":"All of the mentioned","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":796,"Question":"Do not store old sensitive or otherwise non public files on your web server is countermeasure for","Option A":"Directory traversal attack","Option B":"XSS","Option C":"SQL injection","Option D":"All of above","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":797,"Question":"Which was the first FBI Regional computer laboratory was recognized in 2000?","Option A":"Multimedia Laboratory","Option B":"Programming Laboratory","Option C":"Forensic laboratory","Option D":"Software laboratory","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":798,"Question":"___ sensors are used in smartphones, vehicles, aircrafts and other applications to detected orientation of an object, shake, tap, tilt, motion, positioning, shock or vibration.","Option A":"IR","Option B":"Accelerometer","Option C":"Image","Option D":"Proximity","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":799,"Question":"Which of the following is not a characteristics of 5G?","Option A":"Low data transfer speed","Option B":"Low latency","Option C":"Higher download speeds","Option D":"Increased network coverage","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":800,"Question":"___ cause havoc on system availability and storage space.","Option A":"Inbox mails","Option B":"Bulk mail","Option C":"Draft mails","Option D":"Spam (Junk e-mail)","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":801,"Question":"___ sensors are used in IOT systems to monitor systems and devices that are driven by pressure signals.","Option A":"Smoke","Option B":"Pressure","Option C":"Gas","Option D":"Humidity","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":802,"Question":"P2P stands for","Option A":"Private to public","Option B":"Password to Password","Option C":"Peer to peer","Option D":"Process to product","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":803,"Question":"If your wireless LAN network is compromised, you can experience","Option A":"Loss of client server functions","Option B":"Loss of sensitive information, including passwords, customer data and intellectual property.","Option C":"Establishment of client with new server connection","Option D":"Only loss of network accessibility","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":804,"Question":"In Digital Evidence, According to which principle, Contact between two items will result in an exchange?","Option A":"Cyber forensic exchange principle","Option B":"Locard\u2019s exchange principle","Option C":"Best Evidence Principle","Option D":"Culley\u2019s principle","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":805,"Question":"Media Gateways are located in ___ of NGN","Option A":"Access layer","Option B":"Transport layer","Option C":"Control layer","Option D":"Service layer","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":806,"Question":"Running too many tests too quickly on a system causes","Option A":"Many system lockups","Option B":"Crashing of system","Option C":"Erasing of data","Option D":"Restarting a system","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":807,"Question":"In IDIP Model, which phase requires an investigator to walk through the physical crime scene and identify pieces of physical evidence?","Option A":"Documentation phase","Option B":"Survey phase","Option C":"Presentation phase","Option D":"Reconstruction phase","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":808,"Question":"A qualitative color scale is used when","Option A":"Colors are used to represent data values","Option B":"Colors are used to highlight","Option C":"Colors are used to distinguish discrete items","Option D":"Colors are used to represent descriptive data","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":809,"Question":"Blockchain 2.0 is born in the year","Option A":2009,"Option B":2014,"Option C":2017,"Option D":2018,"Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":810,"Question":"___ are the welcome screens that divulge software version numbers and other systems information on network hosts.","Option A":"Hoardings","Option B":"Posters","Option C":"Clusters","Option D":"Banners","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":811,"Question":"MQTT stands for","Option A":"Message Queue Telemetry Things","Option B":"Message Queue Transport Things","Option C":"Message Queue Telemetry Transport","Option D":"Message Queue Transport Telemetry","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":812,"Question":"Ethical hacking is","Option A":"Identifying weakness in computer systems and\/or computer networks and coming up with counter measure that protect the weaknesses.","Option B":"Identifying weakness in programmer and coming up with counter measure that protect the weaknesses.","Option C":null,"Option D":null,"Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":813,"Question":"The victim computers think they need to send traffic to the attackers computer, rather than the true destination computer, when communicating on the network this is often referred to as a","Option A":"Banner Grabbing","Option B":"Man-in-the-Middle (MiTM) attack","Option C":"Passive capturing","Option D":"Port sweeping action","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":814,"Question":"The block which has no previous block for reference is called as?","Option A":"Block 0","Option B":"Block 1","Option C":"Block 2","Option D":"Block 3","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":815,"Question":"WildPacketEtherPeek is used to for","Option A":"Dozens of network security assessment functions","Option B":"Including ping sweeps, port scanning and SMTP relay testing","Option C":"Ping seeps and port scanning","Option D":"Network analysis","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":816,"Question":"In the retail industry, ___ sensors are used to monitor customers visiting the store through IOT networks.","Option A":"Motion","Option B":"Gas","Option C":"IR","Option D":"Image","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":817,"Question":"Nmap is a","Option A":"Widely used paid, and licensed security tool","Option B":"Widely used commercial, freeware and open-source security tool","Option C":"General paid security tool","Option D":"Widely used commercial, freeware and open-source hacking tool","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":818,"Question":"Which type of attack is \u201cbreaking file system security\u201d?","Option A":"Operating system attack","Option B":"Network infrastructure attack","Option C":"Technical attack","Option D":"Application attack","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":819,"Question":"In section 65, Tampering with computer source documents leads to the penalty as:","Option A":"Imprisonment upto three years, or \/ and with fine upto a, \u2018200,000","Option B":"Imprisonment upto three years, or \/ and with fine upto a, \u2018100,000","Option C":"Imprisonment upto three years, or \/ and with fine upto a, \u2018500,000","Option D":"Imprisonment upto life.","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":820,"Question":"Which of the following is not a characteristics of IOT?","Option A":"Self configuring","Option B":"Unique identity","Option C":"Self-adapting","Option D":"Artificial-intelligence","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":821,"Question":"Contracts, wills, invoices are examples of?","Option A":"Illustrative evidence","Option B":"Documented evidence","Option C":"Explainable evidence","Option D":"Substantial Evidence","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":822,"Question":"The first block of blockchain is called as?","Option A":"Genesis block","Option B":"Transaction block","Option C":"Hash block","Option D":"Famous block","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":823,"Question":"Port-scan tests take time. The length of time depends on","Option A":"Only the number of users in the network","Option B":"Only the bandwidth of the network","Option C":"Only the number of port scanned","Option D":"The number of hosts in network, the number of ports scanned, the tools used, and the speed of network links.","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":824,"Question":"___ is a branch of forensic science encompassing the recovery and investigation of material found in digital evidence.","Option A":"Analog forensic","Option B":"Digital forensic","Option C":"Cyber forensic","Option D":"Computer forensic","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":825,"Question":"The intent of ethical hacking","Option A":"To discover the hacker who hacks the secure systems","Option B":"To promote the malicious attackers hack the to better secure systems","Option C":"To discover vulnerabilities from a malicious attackers viewpoint to better secure system","Option D":null,"Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":826,"Question":"___ try to compromise computers and sensitive information for ill-gotten-gains usually from the outside as an unauthorized user.","Option A":"Programmers","Option B":"Computer Engineers","Option C":"Hackers","Option D":"Breakers","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":827,"Question":"___ tool is used for windows and network queries from the DNS lookup to trace routes?","Option A":"SuperScan","Option B":"SamSpade","Option C":"NetCat","Option D":"NetScan","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":828,"Question":"___ is a light-weight messaging protocol based on the publish-subscribe model.","Option A":"Message Queue Telemetry Transport","Option B":"Extensible Messaging and presence Protocol","Option C":"Data Distribution Service","Option D":"Advanced message queuing protocol","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":829,"Question":"___ is the first step in creating a data storytelling presentation?","Option A":"Gathering and analyzing data","Option B":"Creating visualization","Option C":"Writing a script","Option D":"Rehearsing the presentation","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":830,"Question":"In which type of evidence, the objects like x-rays, maps are represented as form of proof?","Option A":"Electronic Evidence","Option B":"Documented Evidence","Option C":"Illustrative Evidence","Option D":"Testimonial","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":831,"Question":"Documented evidence is same as ___ where the proof is presented in writing?","Option A":"Demonstrative","Option B":"Destructive","Option C":"Testimonial","Option D":"Illustrative","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":832,"Question":"The ___ is located in the service providers network and is under the control of the MGC or application server, to provide announcements and tones and collect user information","Option A":"Media server","Option B":"Application server","Option C":"IP core Network","Option D":"Access network","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":833,"Question":"Graphical representation of data and information Is","Option A":"Data storytelling","Option B":"Data visualization","Option C":"Cartesian coordinate system","Option D":"Polar coordinate system","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":834,"Question":"___ occurs when the user input is sent to an interpreter as part of command or query and trick the interpreter into executing unintended commands and gives access to unauthorized data.","Option A":"SQL injection","Option B":"CSS","Option C":"Banner","Option D":"Google Dorking","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":835,"Question":"___ uses a network of sensors to monitor the vibration levels in the structures such as bridges and buildings.","Option A":"Smart roads","Option B":"Smart parking","Option C":"Structural Health Monitoring","Option D":"Fleet Tracking","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":836,"Question":"The ___ receive content from the application support functions and service support functions, process and deliver it to the end-user functions using the capabilities of the transport functions, under control of the service control functions.","Option A":"Service control functions (SCF)","Option B":"Content Delivery functions (CDF)","Option C":"Application support functions (ASF)","Option D":"End-user functions","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":837,"Question":"Which port is used for Telnet?","Option A":"Port 23","Option B":"Port 7","Option C":"Port 21","Option D":"Port 19","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":838,"Question":"___ provides functions which as error control, segmentation, flow control and congestion control.","Option A":"Link Layer","Option B":"Network Layer","Option C":"Transport Layer","Option D":"Application Layer","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":839,"Question":"___ protocol allows full duplex communication over a single socket connection for sending messages between client and server.","Option A":"Web Socket","Option B":"MQTT","Option C":"XMPP","Option D":"AMQP","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":840,"Question":"Blockchain is a?","Option A":"Centralized ledger","Option B":"Distributed ledger on a peer to peer network","Option C":"Currency","Option D":"Cryptocurrency","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":841,"Question":"___ is a software tool that basically scans the network to see how the network is laid out and helps to identify unauthorized hosts or applications.","Option A":"Piggybacking","Option B":"Network analysis","Option C":"Port Scanner","Option D":"Google Dorking","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":842,"Question":"Hypertext transfer protocol (HTTP) and Simple Mail Transfer protocol (SMTP) application are frequently attacked because:","Option A":"They are very simple","Option B":"Their security mechanisms are not configured to allow full access to these program from the internet","Option C":"More firewalls and other security mechanisms and configured to allow full access of these programs","Option D":null,"Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":843,"Question":"As an Ethical hacker, you should scan all ___ UDP and ___ TCP ports on each network host that\u2019s found by your scanner","Option A":"65535 65535","Option B":"65538 65538","Option C":"65530 65530","Option D":"65537 65537","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":844,"Question":"___ Protocols determine how the data is physically send over the networks physical layer or medium.","Option A":"Link layer","Option B":"Physical Layer","Option C":"Network Layer","Option D":"Transport Layer","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":845,"Question":"IDIP stands for","Option A":"Integrated digital investigation process","Option B":"Initial Digital Investigation Process","Option C":"Integrated Direct Investigation process","Option D":"Integrated Direct Internal Process","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":846,"Question":"Mobile apps face increasing attacks given their prevalence in business settings is categorised under ___ attack","Option A":"Operating system","Option B":"Network infrastructure","Option C":"Application and specialised","Option D":"Technical","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":847,"Question":"Which of the following is type of volatile evidence?","Option A":"Main Memory and temporary files","Option B":"Routing tables and process table","Option C":"Both option A and B","Option D":"None of these","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":848,"Question":"Classify the following type of attack: A DOS attack shuts down internet connection or entire network","Option A":"Operating system attack","Option B":"Network infrastructure attack","Option C":"Application specific attack","Option D":"Technical attack","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":849,"Question":"___ involves comparing a companys security policies to whats actually taking place.","Option A":"Security Auditing","Option B":"Business processes","Option C":"Software","Option D":"Client processes","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":850,"Question":"Which of the following are the considerations involved with digital evidence?","Option A":"Use clean collecting media","Option B":"Document any extra scope","Option C":"Consider safety of personnel at the scene","Option D":"All of the above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":851,"Question":"Authentication and Authorization is used","Option A":"For deleting data that is no longer needed","Option B":"To protect gateways to the network, including ports, routers, and connected devices","Option C":"To determine how an organization deals with a disaster, such as a cyber attack, natural disaster, or large-scale equipment failure.","Option D":null,"Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":852,"Question":"___ is a branch of science which deals with helping machine find solutions to complex problems in a more human-life fashion.","Option A":"IOT","Option B":"Embedded system","Option C":"Artificial Intelligence","Option D":"Cyber Security","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":853,"Question":"Identify the missing step in the following from executing the plan in the ethical hacking process. 1] start by getting adequate background information about you organization, you network system names and IO addresses. 2] Assess your results to get more-in-depth know-how on what you uncovered 3] a 4] Narrow your focus more, concentrate on a specific test, and execute scans and other detailed tests","Option A":null,"Option B":null,"Option C":"Proceed to the implementation of appropriate countermeasures mechanisms recommended from the findings.","Option D":null,"Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":854,"Question":"Systems use security cameras and sensors (PIR sensors and door sensors) to detect intrusion and raise alters.","Option A":"Smart Lighting","Option B":"Smoke\/Gas Detectors","Option C":"Intrusion Detection","Option D":"Smart Parking","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":855,"Question":"Data visualization tools provides an accessible way to see and understand ___ in data","Option A":"trends","Option B":"outliners","Option C":"patterns","Option D":"all of these","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":856,"Question":"The raw data collected from volatile sources belongs to","Option A":"Non-volatile Evidence","Option B":"Collection Evidence","Option C":"Volatile Evidence","Option D":"None of these","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":857,"Question":"___ are highly technical and publicly known security experts who not only monitor and track computer, network, and application vulnerabilities but also write the tool and other code to exploit them","Option A":"Security researchers","Option B":"Hacktivists","Option C":"Script kiddies","Option D":"Cyberterrorists","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":858,"Question":"Which one amongst the following is a network infrastructure vulnerability.","Option A":"Any unauthorized employee gaining access to the password of a system","Option B":"A malicious employee using a network analyzer can steal confidential information in emails and files sent over the network","Option C":"A malicious employee gaining authentication to enter into system files and making","Option D":null,"Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":859,"Question":"What is a dApp?","Option A":"Type of blockchain","Option B":"A type of Cryptocurrency","Option C":"A decentralized application","Option D":"Smart Contract","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":860,"Question":"The ___ is a computing concept that describes the idea of everyday physical objects being connected to the internet and being able to identify themselves to the devices","Option A":"Internet of things","Option B":"Embedded System","Option C":"Intranet of Things","Option D":"Microprocessor","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":861,"Question":"___ is most commonly used for clustering similar input into logical groups.","Option A":"Unsupervised learning","Option B":"Supervised learning","Option C":"Deep learning","Option D":"Human and Machine Learning","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":862,"Question":"In the 3 dimensional philosophy of AI, the X dimension is","Option A":"Reasoning","Option B":"Knowledge","Option C":"Computation","Option D":"Vision","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":863,"Question":"Systems are suitable for solutions where data are involved in big, however, the primary analysis requirement is not computationally intensive and can be done locally itself.","Option A":"IOT Level 1","Option B":"IOT Level 2","Option C":"IOT Level 3","Option D":"IOT Level 4","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":864,"Question":"___ is not a network hacking tool","Option A":"Telnet","Option B":"NetCat","Option C":"CleanlisLog","Option D":"A & B","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":865,"Question":"___ is DC motor that move in discrete steps.","Option A":"Servo motor","Option B":"Linear Actuator","Option C":"Induction Motor","Option D":"Stepper Motor","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":866,"Question":"IOT level which is used for smart irrigation system","Option A":"Level \u2014 1","Option B":"Level \u2014 2","Option C":"Level \u2014 3","Option D":"Level \u2014 4","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":867,"Question":"6LOWPAN works with the link layer protocol ___ and defines compression mechanisms for IPV6 datagrams over IEEE 802.15.4 based networks.","Option A":802.11,"Option B":802.3,"Option C":802.16,"Option D":"802.15.4","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":868,"Question":"___ can recognize the shape of the letters and convert it into editable text","Option A":"Handwriting recognition system","Option B":"Voice recognition system","Option C":"Text recognition system","Option D":"Speech recognition systems","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":869,"Question":"Most commonly used units for measurement are relative humidity (RH), dew\/frost point (D\/F PT) and parts million (PPM)","Option A":"Temperature","Option B":"Humidity","Option C":"motion","Option D":"All of these","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":870,"Question":"___ is a transaction oriented and stateless protocol","Option A":"HTTP","Option B":"CoAP","Option C":"UDP","Option D":"TCP","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":871,"Question":"___ is a program that simulated a psychotherapist interacting with a patient and successfully passed a turing test.","Option A":"MAYA","Option B":"ALEXA","Option C":"MALISKA","Option D":"ELIZA","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":872,"Question":"Need of Artificial Intelligence has grown because of","Option A":"Big data which is normally unstructured and vast for humans to comprehend","Option B":"Supervised learning has shown promising results","Option C":"Neural network which is algorithm used as replacement to human","Option D":null,"Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":873,"Question":"BMP 180 is a popular digital ___ sensor for use in mobile phones, PDAs, GPS navigation devices and outdoor equipment","Option A":"Pressure","Option B":"Gas","Option C":"Smoke","Option D":"Image","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":874,"Question":"ARM microcontrollers support for","Option A":"Low level programming language","Option B":"High level programming language","Option C":"Both a and b","Option D":"None of these","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":875,"Question":"The WSN nodes are prone to","Option A":"Malicious attacks","Option B":"Eavesdropping","Option C":"Interfaces","Option D":"All of these","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":876,"Question":"Web-socket based API allows ___ communication between client and server","Option A":"Bi-directional, full duplex","Option B":"Uni-directional, half duplex","Option C":"bi-directional, half duplex","Option D":"Uni-directional, full duplex","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":877,"Question":"___ ensures reliable transmission of packets in order and also provides error detection capability so that duplicate packets can be discarded and lost packets are retransmitted.","Option A":"UDP","Option B":"TCP","Option C":"HTTP","Option D":"CoAP","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":878,"Question":"IOT Level which is used for Tracking Package Handling.","Option A":"Level 1","Option B":"Level 2","Option C":"Level 3","Option D":"Level 4","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":879,"Question":"in UMDFPM, ___ phase is not there in this model","Option A":"Examine","Option B":"Hypothesis","Option C":"Analysis","Option D":"Report","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":880,"Question":"In EMIC model, ___ is the phase where nature of investigation has been identified.","Option A":"Awareness","Option B":"Authorization","Option C":"Planning","Option D":"Collection","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":881,"Question":"In IDIP model, the goal of ___ phase is to collect and analyze the digital evidence","Option A":"Hypothesis","Option B":"Deployment","Option C":"Digital crime investigation","Option D":"Review","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":882,"Question":"An information which has positive impact on the action occurred, such as the information supporting the incident is an","Option A":"Irrelevant evidence","Option B":"Relevant evidence","Option C":"Cannot say","Option D":"All of these","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":883,"Question":"Embedded system consists of","Option A":"Input device, Microcontroller, and output device","Option B":"Hardware and software device","Option C":"Transmitter and Receiver device","Option D":"Wifi and Bluetooth","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":884,"Question":"FBI stands for","Option A":"Federal Bureau of intelligence","Option B":"Federal Bureau of Investigation","Option C":"Feedback bureau of investigation","Option D":"Fabric building of integration","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":885,"Question":"Digital evidence are used establish credible link between","Option A":"Attacker and victim and crime scene","Option B":"Attacker and the crime scene","Option C":"victim and crime scene","Option D":"Attacker and information","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":886,"Question":"The application data typically data, typically in files, is embedded by the ___ protocol and encapsulated in the ___ protocol which provides connection or transaction oriented communication over the network.","Option A":"Application layer, Transport layer","Option B":"Transport layer, Application layer","Option C":"network layer, link layer","Option D":"Link layer, Network layer","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":887,"Question":"State the purpose of Presentation phase in EEDIP model?","Option A":"To obtain and study digital evidence","Option B":"To preserve the investigation and finding","Option C":"To summarize the evidence found in the process of investigation","Option D":"None of these","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":888,"Question":"___ forensic model follows waterfall model as every activity occurs in sequence.","Option A":"EMCI","Option B":"IDIP","Option C":"UMDFPM","Option D":"none of these","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":889,"Question":"A logon record tells us that, at a specific time","Option A":"An unknown person logged into the system using the account","Option B":"The owner of a specific account logged into the system","Option C":"The account was used to log into the system","Option D":null,"Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":890,"Question":"When accessing the reliability of digital evidence the investigator is concerned with whether the computer that generated the evidence was functioning normally and:","Option A":"Whether chain of custody was maintained","Option B":"Whether there are indications that the actual digital evidence was tampered with","Option C":"Whether the evidence was properly secured in transmit","Option D":"Whether the evidence media was ...","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":891,"Question":"Dried blood and fingerprints are type of evidence","Option A":"Substantial Evidence","Option B":"Illustrative Evidence","Option C":"Electronic Evidence","Option D":"Documented Evidence","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":892,"Question":"Select the basic questions raised by ethical hackers during penetration testing among the following a) what can an attacker do with available information b) What information\/locations\/systems can an attacker gain access c) what system notice","Option A":"a, b","Option B":"a, c","Option C":"b, d","Option D":"a, b, c, d","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":893,"Question":"Ethical hacking will allow to ___ all the massive security breaches.","Option A":"remove","Option B":"measure","Option C":"reject","Option D":"None of these","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":894,"Question":"Security assessments based around ethical hacking focus on","Option A":"System vulnerabilities","Option B":"Hacking processes","Option C":"Password cracking","Option D":"All of these","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":895,"Question":"___ is not one of the different stages of hacking.","Option A":"Reconnaissance","Option B":"Scanning","Option C":"Compiling","Option D":"Maintaining Access","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":896,"Question":"An examiner needs to access ___ immediately and extract that evidence before it is lost","Option A":"Disk","Option B":"The cache and register","Option C":"Archival Media","Option D":"Log files","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":897,"Question":"Examples of hackers on basis of work and mind is\/are","Option A":"Exploiting a physical security","Option B":"Bypassing web access controls","Option C":"using overly trusting colleague\u2019s user ID and password","Option D":"All of these","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":898,"Question":"___ ports are available in UDP","Option A":66535,"Option B":66545,"Option C":66555,"Option D":66565,"Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":899,"Question":"___ determines email server version information based on how the server responds to mail formed SMTP request.","Option A":"Nmap scan","Option B":"Tmap scan","Option C":"Smtp scan","Option D":null,"Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":900,"Question":"which of the following is a wireless network attack","Option A":"Encrypted traffic","Option B":"Vulnerabilities wireless workstation","Option C":"Rouge network","Option D":"All of these","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":901,"Question":"___ option tells Nmap to perform an faster scan","Option A":"T3","Option B":"T5","Option C":"T4","Option D":"T6","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":902,"Question":"Workstations have ton of security vulnerabilities like weak passwords to unpatched security holes to storage of WEP keys such workstations are","Option A":"Default Workstations","Option B":"Vulnerable Workstations","Option C":"Physical Workstations","Option D":null,"Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":903,"Question":"___ attack can create never ending loop that bounces thousands of messages back and forth between users","Option A":"Autoresponder","Option B":"Connection","Option C":"Attachment overloading","Option D":null,"Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":904,"Question":"An EMIC model is impacted by information from within and outside the organization that will affect the investigation","Option A":"Planning","Option B":"Awareness","Option C":"Authorization","Option D":"Transport","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":905,"Question":"Which of the following port no is vulnerable to hacker HTTPs using TCP protocol","Option A":441,"Option B":442,"Option C":443,"Option D":444,"Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":906,"Question":"POP3 stands for","Option A":"Post office program version 3","Option B":"Post office protocol version 3","Option C":"Post office process version 3","Option D":null,"Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":907,"Question":"Skills of ethical hackers may consists of","Option A":"Trained hacker","Option B":"Identify security problems with computer network","Option C":"Capable of breaching security","Option D":"All of these","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":908,"Question":"Which statement of the following is INCORRECT in view of ethical hacker?","Option A":"They are hired professional to penetrate in system","Option B":"They find system vulnerabilities without proper authorization","Option C":"They help making system secure and better","Option D":null,"Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":909,"Question":"___ standards form the basis of specifications for high level communication protocols such as ZigBee","Option A":"IEEE 802.15.4","Option B":"IEEE 802.3","Option C":"IEEE 802.11","Option D":"IEEE 802.16","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":910,"Question":"Although crime scenes are typically photographed, it is good idea to create diagrams of the crime scene because:","Option A":"Diagramming is a common crime scene technician\u2019s skill, however it requires continual practice.","Option B":"The process of creating a diagram can result in a digital investigator noticing an important item of evidence that would otherwise have been missed.","Option C":null,"Option D":null,"Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":911,"Question":"Some Arduino Board include ___ used for loading programs from the personal computer","Option A":"USB","Option B":"HDMI","Option C":"Rj45","Option D":"none of these","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":912,"Question":"___ is an actuator that creates motion in a straight line, in contrast to the circular motion of a conventional electric motor","Option A":"Relay","Option B":"Solenoid","Option C":"Linear Actuator","Option D":"None of these","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":913,"Question":"In which system the forensic science plays as important role?","Option A":"Criminal justice","Option B":"Artificial intelligence","Option C":"Machine learning","Option D":"Deep Learning","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":914,"Question":"Whether Monitoring, Air Pollution Monitoring, Noise pollution Monitoring, Forest fire Detection and River flood detection are belong to ___ domain specific IOT","Option A":"Cities","Option B":"Environment","Option C":"Retail","Option D":"Logistics","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":915,"Question":"The authentication, Authorization, Message and ___ content integrity and data security are functions of ___ functional block.","Option A":"Service","Option B":"Management","Option C":"Security","Option D":"Application","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":916,"Question":"___ is a bi-directional, fully duplex communication model that uses a persistent connection between the client and server.","Option A":"Request-response","Option B":"publish-subscribe","Option C":"Push-pull","Option D":"Exclusive pair","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":917,"Question":"The ARM architecture users a ___ architecture which support separate data ___ and instruction buses for memories","Option A":"Application","Option B":null,"Option C":"Data","Option D":null,"Answer":null,"Unnamed: 7":"A"},{"Q.No":918,"Question":"6LOWPAN operates in the ___ frequency range.","Option A":"5GHz","Option B":"2.4GHz","Option C":"60GHz","Option D":"10GHz","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":919,"Question":"___ does not guarantee delivery, ordering of messages and duplicate messages.","Option A":"CoAP","Option B":"HTTP","Option C":"TCP","Option D":"UDP","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":920,"Question":"Coordinator ___ acts as a gateway that connect the ___ to the internet.","Option A":"WSN","Option B":"Sensors","Option C":"Actuator","Option D":"TCP","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":921,"Question":"___ deals with learning a function from available training data.","Option A":"Artificial Intelligence","Option B":"Deep Learning","Option C":"Neural Network","Option D":"Supervised learning","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":922,"Question":"___ allows ___ bi-directional, full duplex communication between client and servers.","Option A":"Communication with REST APIs","Option B":"WebSocket APIs","Option C":"Both a and b","Option D":"None of these","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":923,"Question":"DDS uses ___ model where publishers (e.g., device that generate data) create topics ___ to which subscribers (e.g., devices that want to consume data) can subscribe.","Option A":"request-response","Option B":"publish-subscribe","Option C":"push-pull","Option D":"Exclusive pair","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":924,"Question":"Guaranteed delivery and data integrity are handled by the ___ protocols.","Option A":"TCP","Option B":"UDP","Option C":"CoAP","Option D":"HTTP","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":925,"Question":"The WSN nodes are prone to ___","Option A":"Malicious attacks","Option B":"Eavesdropping","Option C":"Interferences","Option D":"All of these","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":926,"Question":"___ is ___ through supervised learning or learning from labelled data and algorithms.","Option A":"Deep learning","Option B":"Machine Learning","Option C":"Human learning","Option D":"none","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":927,"Question":"How many important concepts are part of Artificial Intelligence","Option A":true,"Option B":2,"Option C":3,"Option D":4,"Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":928,"Question":"Which of the following has ability to Recognize, Understand and Act.","Option A":"Data","Option B":"Information","Option C":"Knowledge","Option D":"Intelligence","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":929,"Question":"Type 2 Artificial Intelligence machines are","Option A":"Super AI","Option B":"General AI","Option C":"Weak AI","Option D":"Limited Memory Machine","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":930,"Question":"IBMs Watson supercomputer comes under","Option A":"General AI","Option B":"Super AI","Option C":"Narrow AI","Option D":"All of them","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":931,"Question":"Security ___ works for IOT ___ application to handle security issues according to scenario requirement.","Option A":"System","Option B":"Application","Option C":"Network","Option D":"All of the above","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":932,"Question":"___ contains local and cloud-based observer nodes which can subscribe to and receive information classified in the cloud from IOT device.","Option A":"IOT Level 4","Option B":"IOT Level 3","Option C":"IOT Level 2","Option D":"IOT Level 1","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":933,"Question":"___ provides services to the user to manage computing and storage resources.","Option A":"IaaS","Option B":"PaaS","Option C":"SaaS","Option D":"All of the above","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":934,"Question":"802.16m provides data rates of 100 Mbit\/s for ___ and 1 Gbit\/s for ___","Option A":"Mobile station, fixed station","Option B":"Fixed station, mobile station","Option C":"Both a and b","Option D":"None of the above","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":935,"Question":"___ used to connect TV to Raspberry Pi.","Option A":"USB","Option B":"HDMI","Option C":"RJ45","Option D":"VGA","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":936,"Question":"Websocket APIs ___ model","Option A":"Request-Response Communication","Option B":"Publish Subscribe Communication","Option C":"Push-Pull Communication","Option D":"Exclusive Pair Communication","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":937,"Question":"WLAN stands for","Option A":"Wireless Local Area Network","Option B":"Wire Local Area Network","Option C":"Wide Local Area Network","Option D":"All of above","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":938,"Question":"The DAC converts","Option A":"Analog to Digital Converter","Option B":"Digital to Analog Converter","Option C":"Both A and B","Option D":"None of the above","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":939,"Question":"___ sensor used to detect nearby objects.","Option A":"Proximity Sensor","Option B":"Humidity Sensor","Option C":"Touch Sensor","Option D":"Pressure Sensor","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":940,"Question":"802.3 is the standard for ___ of Ethernet that uses coaxial cable as a shared medium.","Option A":"10BASE5","Option B":"10BASE-F","Option C":"10BASE-T","Option D":"All of the above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":941,"Question":"___ standards form the basis of specifications for high level communication protocols such as ZigBee","Option A":"IEEE 802.15.4","Option B":"IEEE 802.3","Option C":"IEEE 802.11","Option D":"IEEE 802.16","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":942,"Question":"who proposed IDIP model ?","Option A":"Palmar","Option B":"Carrier and Safford","Option C":"Stephenson","Option D":null,"Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":943,"Question":"Following are some phases of EMCI model.","Option A":"Awareness, Planning","Option B":"Maz","Option C":"Authorization, Notification","Option D":"Collection, Transport","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":944,"Question":"Digital forensic ___ includes the following ?","Option A":"Recovery","Option B":"Investigation","Option C":"Validation","Option D":"D","Answer":null,"Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":945,"Question":"How many phases are extra in ADFM as comparing with RMDFR ?","Option A":5,"Option B":4,"Option C":3,"Option D":8,"Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":946,"Question":"To meet the ___ validation challenge it is necessary to ensure that ___ original media matches by using ___ MD5 hashes.","Option A":"Forensic Duplication","Option B":"For identity","Option C":"For evidence","Option D":null,"Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":947,"Question":"Which of the following is not a type of volatile evidence ?","Option A":"Routing Tables","Option B":"Main Memory","Option C":"Log Files","Option D":"Cached Data","Answer":null,"Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":948,"Question":"To verify the ___ original drive with the forensic copy, you should use ___ by using ___.","Option A":"Password","Option B":"Hash Analysis","Option C":"Disk to disk","Option D":null,"Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":949,"Question":"Collection of evidence starts with ___","Option A":"From the most volatile to least volatile data.","Option B":"From the least volatile to most volatile data.","Option C":"To get only volatile data.","Option D":"To get only Non-volatile data","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":950,"Question":"Investigate the case a) Cyber cafes through which illegal transfers were made were identified. b) The System server logs of the BPO were collected. c) The IP addresses were traced to the ...","Option A":"a-b-c-d-e","Option B":"e-d-c-b-a","Option C":"b-c-a-e-d","Option D":"d-b-c-e-a","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":951,"Question":"Case: The accused was posing to be a genuine railway ticket agent and had been purchasing tickets online by using stolen credit cards of non residents. The accused created fraudulent electronic records\/ profiles. Which he used to carry out the a...","Option A":"Short list ___ persons at ___ when the ___ were made ___.","Option B":"Examine the ___ passengers who had ___ on those tickets.","Option C":"Logs ___ of ___ machines of cyber caf\u00e9 ___ examined ___.","Option D":"The ___ Ticket ___ ___ booking ___ service ___ provider ___ gave ___ the ___ IP ___ addresses ___ of ___ cyber ___ cafe ___ from ___ A.","Answer":"d c)","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":952,"Question":"May not crack password.","Option A":"Port scanner","Option B":"Vulnerability scanning","Option C":"CT-scan","Option D":"Network scanning","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":953,"Question":"Obstacles to protect from hackers attacks","Option A":"Wide spread use of networking and internet connectivity.","Option B":"Greater number and availability of hacking tools","Option C":"A and B","Option D":"None of these","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":954,"Question":"Ethical hacker must abide rule set by","Option A":"Certified Ethical Hacker (CEH)","Option B":"E-Commerce Consultants (EC-Council)","Option C":"Certified Information System (CIS)","Option D":"Computer Security Certification (CSC)","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":955,"Question":"What are the desired skill set require for Ethical Hacker?","Option A":"Analytical skills","Option B":"Problem-solving skills","Option C":"Communication Skills","Option D":"All of the above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":956,"Question":"What type of hacker represents the highest risk to your network?","Option A":"Black hat hacker","Option B":"Former Employees","Option C":"White hat hackers","Option D":"Script kiddies","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":957,"Question":"Hacking for cause is called","Option A":"Active hacking","Option B":"Hacktivism","Option C":"Activism","Option D":"Black hat hacking","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":958,"Question":"Select correct option which differentiate between White hat Hacker and Black Hat Hacker.","Option A":"Tools","Option B":"Methodology","Option C":"Good and bad intention","Option D":"Trick","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":959,"Question":"Which of the following is not role of Hacker.","Option A":"Gain Access Illegally","Option B":"Gain Fame","Option C":"Improve System Security","Option D":"Use system vulnerabilities","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":960,"Question":"Ethical hacker","Option A":"Works with high professional morals and principles.","Option B":"Posses low moral low principles.","Option C":"High principles, low morals","Option D":"Low professionals, low morals","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":961,"Question":"One of the common motive being hacking is","Option A":"Revenge","Option B":"Helping nature","Option C":"Ignore insult","Option D":"None of these","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":962,"Question":"Ethical hacking related carriers may be","Option A":"Back-end developer","Option B":"Computer networking specialist","Option C":"A and B","Option D":"None of these","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":963,"Question":"Installing\/ enabling a network analyzer on a computer network and capturing every packet that travels across it.","Option A":"Network related attacks","Option B":"Application attack","Option C":"Operating system attack","Option D":"Non-technical attack","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":964,"Question":"___ are those individuals who are appointed to maintain and handles IT security in any firm or organization.","Option A":"IT Security Engineer","Option B":"Black hat hackers","Option C":"Red hat hackers","Option D":"Blue hat hackers","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":965,"Question":"Attack can lead to complete server lockup or crash.","Option A":"Attachment overloading","Option B":"Autoresponder","Option C":"Connections","Option D":"All of the above","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":966,"Question":"Banner grabbing is done by using","Option A":"Plain old telnet","Option B":"Netcat","Option C":"A and B","Option D":null,"Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":967,"Question":"Which of the following is not a caveat for using network analyzer.","Option A":"Hun on network","Option B":"To capture all traffic","Option C":"Monitor port on switch","Option D":null,"Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":968,"Question":"Which of the following tool is used for network testing and port scanning.","Option A":"Netcat","Option B":"Superscan","Option C":"Netscan","Option D":"All of the above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":969,"Question":"___ is a program that acts as an interface between software & hardware.","Option A":"Service","Option B":"Operating System","Option C":"Network","Option D":"None of above","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":970,"Question":"For minimizing Database security risk backup should be","Option A":"Encrypted","Option B":"Decrypted","Option C":"Redundant","Option D":"None of the above","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":971,"Question":"Which of the following is not Hacker attacks against messaging system includes","Option A":"Transmitting malware","Option B":"Crashing servers","Option C":"Obtaining remote control of workstation","Option D":null,"Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":972,"Question":"___ can create DoS condition by filling either users individual disk space quota on email server.","Option A":"Connection","Option B":"Autoresponder","Option C":"Attachment overloading","Option D":"None of the above","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":973,"Question":"Crashing server, obtaining remote control of workstation etc. are the hacker attack against","Option A":"Messaging system","Option B":"Web Application","Option C":"A and B","Option D":null,"Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":974,"Question":"In ___ the goal is for the software to use what it has learned in one area to solve problems in other areas.","Option A":"Deep Learning","Option B":"Machine Learning","Option C":"Neural Network","Option D":"Artificial Intelligence","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":975,"Question":"___ is defined as symbols that represent properties of objects events and their environment.","Option A":"Data","Option B":"Information","Option C":"Knowledge","Option D":"Intelligence","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":976,"Question":"In ___ system has a single node as well as data is stored and analyzed in the cloud application is cloud based.","Option A":"IOT Level 1","Option B":"IOT Level 2","Option C":"IOT Level 3","Option D":"IOT Level 4","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":977,"Question":"The most common example of embedded operating system include","Option A":"Linux","Option B":"Palm OS","Option C":"IOS- Subset of Mac OS X","Option D":"All of above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":978,"Question":"IDE stands for","Option A":"In Deep Environment","Option B":"Integrated Development Environment","Option C":"Internal Deep Escape","Option D":"IDE","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":979,"Question":"An IOT device may consist of several interfaces for connections to other devices, both wired and wireless which includes","Option A":"I\/O interfaces for sensors","Option B":"Interfaces for Internet connectivity","Option C":"Memory and storage interfaces and audio\/video interfaces.","Option D":"All of above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":980,"Question":"Brokers in MQTT","Option A":"Connects publisher and subscribers","Option B":"Classify the sensor data into topics","Option C":"Both a and b","Option D":null,"Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":981,"Question":"EMCI stands for","Option A":"Enlarged Model of Computer Investigation","Option B":"Extended Model of CyberCrime Investigation","Option C":"Extended Media of Computer Indication","Option D":null,"Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":982,"Question":"Application of temperature sensors are","Option A":"Air-conditioners, refrigerators","Option B":"Manufacturing processes","Option C":"Agriculture and health industry","Option D":"All of above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":983,"Question":"REST is acronym for","Option A":"Regional State Transfer","Option B":"Representational Sensed Data Transfer","Option C":"Representational State Transfer","Option D":"None of these","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":984,"Question":"___ is a connectionless protocol.","Option A":"UDP","Option B":"TCP","Option C":"HTTP","Option D":"CoAP","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":985,"Question":"Resources used by hackers may be","Option A":"Open wireless network","Option B":"Internet Proxy severs","Option C":"Borrowed or stolen remote desktops","Option D":"All","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":986,"Question":"___ who helps in finding bugs and vulnerabilities in a system and don't intent to crack a system.","Option A":"Black hat hacker","Option B":"Red hat hacker","Option C":"Grey hat hacker","Option D":"White hat hacker","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":987,"Question":"WEP stands for","Option A":"Wired Equivalent privacy","Option B":"Wi-fi Equivalent privacy","Option C":"Wired equal privacy","Option D":null,"Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":988,"Question":"Which command-Line option is used for ping scan in Nmap tool","Option A":"sP","Option B":"Ps","Option C":"i","Option D":"Ns","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":989,"Question":"While performing digital investigation, in which media an examination should never be performed?","Option A":"Wireless","Option B":"Optic","Option C":"Magnetic","Option D":"Original","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":990,"Question":"Hackers useful in finding bugs and vulnerabilities in a system and don\u2019t intend to crime","Option A":"Black hat hackers","Option B":"White hat hackers","Option C":"Blue hat hackers","Option D":"Gray hat hackers","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":991,"Question":"___ layer determines how the packets are coded and signaled by the hardware device over the medium to which the host is attached.","Option A":"Link layer","Option B":"Network layer","Option C":"Transport layer","Option D":"Application layer","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":992,"Question":"How many phases are extra in ADFM as comparing with RMDFR","Option A":5,"Option B":4,"Option C":3,"Option D":8,"Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":993,"Question":"The Robots that have efficient processors, multiple sensors and huge memory are called","Option A":"Intelligent Robots","Option B":"Industrial Robots","Option C":"Military Robots","Option D":"Domestic Robots","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":994,"Question":"What is digital forensic science?","Option A":"Recovery and investigation of material found in digital devices","Option B":"Things are connected to internet","Option C":"Put intelligence to machine","Option D":"Search the data from internet","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":995,"Question":"HTTP port number is","Option A":80,"Option B":22,"Option C":64,"Option D":32,"Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":996,"Question":"___ is an object responsible for data distribution","Option A":"Publisher","Option B":"Subscriber","Option C":"Both a and b","Option D":"None of these","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":997,"Question":"The data transmission can be done through wireless media such as","Option A":"Bluetooth, zigbee","Option B":"Wifi, GPRS","Option C":"EDGE","Option D":"All of these","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":998,"Question":"___ sensors include thermocouple, thermistors, resistor temperature detectors (RTDs) and integrated circuits (ICs)","Option A":"Temperature","Option B":"Humidity","Option C":"Motion","Option D":"Gas","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":999,"Question":"A ___ comprises of distributed devices with sensors which are used to monitor the environmental and physical conditions","Option A":"Wireless Sensor Network","Option B":"Physical Network","Option C":"Intranet","Option D":"None of these","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":1000,"Question":"The ___ block handles the communication for the IOT System.","Option A":"Device","Option B":"Communication","Option C":"Service","Option D":"Management","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":1001,"Question":"Ethical hacking need to be planned","Option A":"After 1 year of installation of system","Option B":"During failure","Option C":"After failure","Option D":"In advance","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":1002,"Question":"Kernal statistics are moving back and forth between cache and main memory, which make them","Option A":"Non-volatile","Option B":"Static information","Option C":"Highly volatile","Option D":"Legal information","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":1003,"Question":"Who is the father of Computer Forensics, came into limelight during this period?","Option A":"John Macarthy","Option B":"Micheal Anderson","Option C":"Allen Turing","Option D":"Mary Shelley","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":1004,"Question":"The compound components built from core components of AI is are","Option A":"Knowledge","Option B":"Reasoning","Option C":"Search","Option D":"All of above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":1005,"Question":"What to do in following case \u201cif DB holds sensitive information\u201d","Option A":"Avoid usage of shared web server","Option B":"Avoid usage of unshared web server","Option C":"Avoid usage of private web server","Option D":null,"Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":1006,"Question":"Which of following factors can create weaknesses in messaging system","Option A":"Rarely integrated security in software development","Option B":"Messaging protocol without security","Option C":"A & B","Option D":null,"Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":1007,"Question":"___ standards provide low-cost and low-speed communication for power constrained devices.","Option A":802.3,"Option B":802.11,"Option C":"802.15.4","Option D":802.16,"Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":1008,"Question":"IOT devices may support a number of ___ protocols and can communicate with other devices and also with the infrastructure.","Option A":"Internet","Option B":"Interoperable communication","Option C":"Intra system","Option D":"Intranet","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":1009,"Question":"The Y dimension of AI philosophy in 3D representation consists of","Option A":"Logic","Option B":"Reasoning","Option C":"Language","Option D":"All of the above","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":1010,"Question":"___ is a communication model in which the client sends requests to the server and the server responds to the requests.","Option A":"Request-response","Option B":"Publish-subscribe","Option C":"Push-pull","Option D":"Exclusive pair","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":1011,"Question":"Most of processors designed by ARM are","Option A":"16 bit","Option B":"32 bit","Option C":"64 bit","Option D":"8 bit","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":1012,"Question":"___ is a message that contains relevant meaning, implication or input for decision and\/or action","Option A":"Data","Option B":"Information","Option C":"Knowledge","Option D":"Intelligence","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":1013,"Question":"___ will not be the type of scanning used in Ethical Hacking.","Option A":"Port Scanning","Option B":"Network Scanning","Option C":"CT-scan","Option D":"Vulnerability scanning","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":1014,"Question":"In digital forensic field, ___ are the set of moral principles that regulate the use of computers.","Option A":"Compliance with the law","Option B":"Handling the digital evidences carefully","Option C":"Honesty towards investigation","Option D":"All of above","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":1015,"Question":"An Ethical hacker is a security professional who applies their hacking skills for ___ purposes on behalf of the owners of information systems","Option A":"Destructive","Option B":"Defensive","Option C":"Attacking","Option D":"Analyzing","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":1016,"Question":"___ can create man-in-middle attacks by maliciously using a tool such as the WIFI pineapple","Option A":"Testers","Option B":"Hackers","Option C":"Programmer","Option D":"Developers","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":1017,"Question":"Identify the digital forensic model given in figure>","Option A":"ADFM Model","Option B":"EMCI Model","Option C":"IDIP Model","Option D":"None of these","Answer":null,"Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":1018,"Question":"___ is the kind of evidence spoken by the spectator under the oath.","Option A":"Substantial Evidence","Option B":"Testimonial Evidence","Option C":"Explainable Evidence","Option D":"Illustrative Evidence","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":1019,"Question":"___ only focus on current scenarios and react on it as per possible best action","Option A":"Reactive Machines","Option B":"Limited Memory","Option C":"Theory of Mind","Option D":"Self-Awareness","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":1020,"Question":"ARP means","Option A":"Address resolution protocol","Option B":"Address requesting protocol","Option C":"Another resolution protocol","Option D":"Address requesting promotion","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":1021,"Question":"Which of the following types of variables is categorical?","Option A":"Age","Option B":"Weight","Option C":"Gender","Option D":"Income","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":1022,"Question":"Write the correct sequence steps of procedure to establish the chain of custody? Save the original materials, Perform hash test analysis to further authenticate the working clone, Take screenshot of digital evidence content, Inject bit by bit clone of digital evidence content into our forensic computers","Option A":"Sequence of steps 1,2,3,4","Option B":"Sequence of steps 1,3,4,2","Option C":"Sequence of steps 2,3,4,1","Option D":"Sequence of Steps 3,4,2,1","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":1023,"Question":"What is the operation in the figure shown? (Finding MAC Address, Scanning local airwaves, Setting IP Address, Setting server address)","Option A":"Finding MAC Address","Option B":"Scanning local airwaves","Option C":"Setting IP Address","Option D":"Setting server address","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":1024,"Question":"The general ethical norms for investigator is","Option A":"To contribute to society and human being","Option B":"Uphold any relevant evidence","Option C":"Declare any confidential matter","Option D":"Distort or falsify education","Answer":"A","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":1025,"Question":"Smart contracts, dApps, UI and chain code can be found on ___ layer of blockchain architecture?","Option A":"Execution","Option B":"Semantic","Option C":"Consensus","Option D":"Application","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":1026,"Question":"___ Layer of blockchain deals in validation of the transactions done in the blockchain network and also validating the blocks being created in the network?","Option A":"Application","Option B":"Semantic","Option C":"Propagation","Option D":"Execution","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":1027,"Question":"Attackers can use ___ running on your network to make their systems appear as your systems","Option A":"Sniffdet","Option B":"PromiscDetect","Option C":"ARP(Address Resolution Protocol)","Option D":"FTP(File Transfer protocol)","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":1028,"Question":"___ is used for network analysis.","Option A":"WildPacketsEtherPeek","Option B":"NetCat","Option C":"Netscan","Option D":"Nmap","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":1029,"Question":"The DNS(Domain Name System) port belongs to","Option A":"FTP","Option B":"TCP","Option C":"WTP","Option D":"UDP","Answer":"D","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":1030,"Question":"Where is the Blockchains central server?","Option A":"Where the blockchain is created","Option B":"At First node","Option C":"There is no central server, it is distributed","Option D":"Located with owner of server","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":1031,"Question":"This symbol signifies: (White hat hackers, Gray hat hacker, Hacktivists)","Option A":"White hat hackers, a hacker who gains access to systems with a view to fix the identified weaknesses","Option B":"Gray hat hacker, a hacker who is in between ethical and black hat hackers. He\/she breaks into computer systems without authority","Option C":"Hacktivists, a hacker who use hacking to send social, religious, political, etc messages.","Option D":null,"Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":1032,"Question":"The skilled criminal experts who write some of the hacking tools, including the scripts and other programs that the script kiddies and security professionals use are known as","Option A":"Hacktivists","Option B":"Criminal Hackers","Option C":"Script Kiddies","Option D":"Security Professionals","Answer":"B","Unnamed: 7":null},{"Q.No":1033,"Question":"Which of the following chart types is best suited for showing proportions or percentages?","Option A":"Line chart","Option B":"Scatter chart","Option C":"Pie chart","Option D":"Histogram","Answer":"C","Unnamed: 7":null}]